The countless flowers,
enveloped in light...
...gaze at tomorrow
with unwavering eyes.
Everyone wishes for me to be pure...
...but what can I bring
with me to the frayed skies?
What I've made my own
by breaking off flowers in bloom...
All such sinful things...
Why did I stop making
promises with the future?
Because even if I try
to run far from all the pain...
...a cold wind rustles
my hair... Don't you see?
Where can I ever find the answer?
I have lived all this time
without ever making a decision.
This is my punishment.
I failed to become an eternal maiden.
And I failed to make my way to
that other world. I remained here.
Never to touch another.
Never to feel another's
embrace. And still...
I remain here.
But why?
Why did they do that to your body?
Because I refused to
choose a permanent gender...
...they sentenced me to become
the gatekeeper of the Spring.
Because you wouldn't choose?
So that no future maiden
would make the same mistake.
To stand here for all time...
That is my penance for
running away from reality.
Choices
Chor Tempest is to be
officially disbanded.
Sibyllae, we have decided that it is
now time for you to go to the Spring.
What?
Just a moment!
Why are we also being stripped
of our posts as sibyllae?
You will be ceding your duties
to the Plumbum priestesses.
No way!
Father!
They won't even let us be Simoun
sibyllae anymore? Then that means...
We'll have to leave the Arcus Prima!
Is that what you're saying?
Well, forcing them to make a
decision like that so suddenly...
We can hardly expect them to
choose on such short notice!
They need time to prepare.
We are out of time.
All we're asking for is a short period.
Compared to the long history
of Simulacrum Kyuukoku...
...it would only be a fleeting moment.
Sibylla Morinas...
You heard what's happening to us, right?
Yes.
Are you happy now?
Actually...
I'm going to be leaving
the Arcus Prima as well.
Kyuukoku won't be flying
the Simouns any longer.
And to prove it, the entire maintenance
crew is being moved to the highlands.
What?
It's all the same to us
no matter where we end up.
The Simouns are the
divine vessels of the gods.
And yet...
No matter how close I try to get...
No, the truth is that I've
discovered something about myself.
I no longer care about the Simouns!
As long as I know you're safe,
that's enough to make me happy.
Go ahead and despise me now.
They're getting smaller, aren't they?
I wanted to become a man and putter
around with you and the Simouns, but...
Which are you going to choose?
I guess you've always
wanted to become a man, huh?
You probably couldn't care less that
we're being forced to go to the Spring.
That's right. You've always...
That's so not true!
I'm scared too!
It scares me that we
have to grow up now!
I want to lean on someone else...
I want someone to protect me! But...
Alty...
Oh, shut up, you dummy!
What a dummy you are, Big Sister!
Dummy!
Dummy... dummy... dummy... dummy!
Picking a fight with your sister?
I mean, how immature is that?
You're still just kids. You're
both too young to become adults.
Hey, Vura, all the Chor Rubor girls
already picked their genders, right?
The ones who had a family
business to take over became male.
The others, well, it was pretty random.
Oh?
What about you, Floe?
Me? Whatever. I don't really
care which I end up being!
Of course, if I were in love, I would
be telling a different story, but...
Really? But everyone says that
you've got a thing for Aer.
Right, and I've told them over
and over that it's not true!
Oh, for heaven's sake.
What does it matter, anyway?
But I don't know...
For some reason I feel so lonely.
That's what growing up is all about.
So if you feel lonely,
it means you've grown up?
I just remembered something.
Alty was such a moron!
Darn it, didn't I tell
you not to tag along?
You're always slowing me down, Alty!
And you're such a dummy, Big Sister!
Who are you calling a dummy?
You clumsy slowpoke!
Dummy!
Whatever! You can find your
own way back then, you wimp!
Dummy!
You're such a dummy, Big Sister!
Even if we were in the
middle of a fight...
...she could never come up
with any names to call me.
She could never say
anything except, "Dummy!"
And the thing is she never learned.
She just kept following me.
I mean, really... What a
little moron of a sister I have!
I wonder when it was
that Alty stopped being...
...such a little wimp.
I'm going to protect you, Big Sister.
She got such an assertive look
in her eyes, and she grew so tall.
It was like she suddenly became
more of a grownup than me.
But because so much was
going on, I didn't even notice.
To me, Alty was still
the same little wimp.
And I've always averted my gaze from
her. I just didn't want to believe it.
Even so... I...
You'll be forgiven.
Even if you're no longer a sibylla, that
doesn't mean you can't do certain things.
Like forgiving one another...
To forgive someone for wronging you...
...and to be forgiven in return.
If we can manage to do that much...
...I think we can still call ourselves
sibyllae even after we choose our gender.
Listen...
I really do like you, Para-sama.
My feelings for you won't change
whether I become a man or a woman.
I don't think I'll ever
stop looking up to you!
Thank you.
They say that the high priestess
has been driven from the Arcus Prima.
Aer, we don't have much time. You...
What do you want me to say?
Never mind, don't answer
that. I already know.
But...
I'm never gonna do it!
Aer?
You just want to see Amuria again. That's
why you want to go to the other world!
I can't do a Ri Majon with you
if that's all you care about!
Why did Onasia show that to me?
Never to feel another's embrace.
And still...
...I remain here.
Onasia... Is she doomed
to stand there forever?
Never to know forgiveness?
Never to be saved?
Yun?
I thought that I should take
some of Mamina's things with me.
Oh. Her trunk is under her bed.
When I go home, I'll be
seeing Mamina's mother, so...
I thought I could give them to her then.
Still smells like Mamina!
It's not much...
...but I hope Mamina's mother
will find comfort in this.
I wonder... Is it even possible
for us to save anybody now?
I'm sure it will be very difficult.
We can barely take care
of ourselves as it is.
But if we try our utmost,
then maybe we can save...
...at least one person in this world.
One person...
Yun, is there someone in your life?
That one person?
Yun's gone?
Yes. I hear the highland soldiers
are looking for her, but...
Why, Yun?
Maybe she decided she
didn't want to grow up.
No, not Yun.
She...
She must have realized...
What?
Oh, nothing.
Oh, whatever! Being
such a stranger to us!
She just got up and left
without saying a word!
I know...
...but once Chor Tempest is disbanded,
we'll all be going our separate ways.
I have something to tell you all.
About another world...
No way! Who knew the Emerald Ri
Majon could do something like that!
Right, but that's precisely
what's going to save us.
Each of us is going to
choose a gender soon.
And our days on the Arcus
Prima will come to an end.
But those two won't be choosing a
gender and will stay the way they are...
Not choose a gender...
...and stay the way they are?
When the rest of us are all grown up...
...and the emotions we carry
inside us now have faded...
Those two will be
alive in another era...
...somewhere in a sparkling world,
looking just as they do now.
I need to talk to you.
I get it. So those two will always...
Right.
Even after we've all become adults...
...they'll stay the same
for us for all time, right?
The "eternal present"...
You don't have to go to the other
world with me if you don't want to.
But whatever it is we decide,
we really should tell the others.
That we're not going to the Spring...
I don't need you to tell me that!
I do want to know what
happened to Amuria.
I do want to see her again.
I can't lie to you about that.
But...
The one I'm in love with...
...is you.
The one who lives facing life, rather
than death... It's you whom I love.
The one who rescued me from the
darkness... It's you whom I love.
The thought of going to that
other world frightens me.
But if you and I are
together, then I'm sure...
Hold on.
It's not that I wanted you to tell
me all about your feelings for me!
You don't need to give me an answer.
I just thought that
I should let you know.
No...
I wanted to let you know. That's all.
Nothing more.
How am I supposed to take
that in all of a sudden?
I don't understand!
The one I'm in love with... is you.
Why is it...
...so painful?
To save the drifting spirits
of my fallen comrades...
That's the one thing I've
always had on my mind.
But deep down, I always knew the truth.
That it's not possible
to save the dead...
But still...
There's one who even I...
No...
What I realized was that there's one
person who can only be saved by me.
For some reason, I'd hoped...
...to hear those very words from you.
I never chose a gender for myself.
But...
I was not able to hold
on to my maiden's soul.
And now, once again,
I am trying to escape.
This time burdening you with
all my responsibilities...
No.
You're beautiful.
You're beautiful...
I can hear quite a commotion out there.
That voice... it must be Sibylla Floe.
Aer, were you planning
to stay in bed all day?
It's our last day on the Arcus Prima!
Wait for me, Alty!
Not gonna happen!
Please wait up!
Up here!
It's an amazing view!
Come on, dance with me, Aer!
Huh? Uh, I...
Don't tell me that's...
Please, let the Messis
transport you to the Spring.
Thanks, but it's all right.
I've always wanted to ride
on a helical-motor train.
I understand.
May I ask what's going on with
Sibylla Neviril and Sibylla Aer?
They have asked for a little more time.
Fine.
All right then.
Farewell.
We'll come back to say
hello when we're adults!
The mountains are getting closer!
It's almost time for lunch.
Oh, I almost forgot.
I had them pack us something to eat
before we left. Is anybody hungry?
Those look delicious!
Me too! Me too!
I'd like a vegetable sandwich.
What about you, Roatre?
A meat sandwich for me, please!
Same for me, please.
Oh boy, I'm starving!
This is so good!
Okay, this is for Roatre.
This one's yours, Paraietta.
Thanks.
Man, why didn't you tell us sooner...
...that you had sandwiches?
Come on, Floe!
But that's...
Yun!
It is played by my wounds...
the song of prayer.
Let it ring out over
the grieving universe.
Can we change tomorrow?
Don't be afraid.
I want to let you know
how my heart's overflowing.
I want to get closer to you.
I want to feel your pulse.
I was too defiant,
and I took the long way around.
The blue moon is swaying silently.
My true heart's desire is you.
I can't reach you.
My tears of pain trickle down.
Soar away into the sky, song of prayer.
Carrying my love that came too late.
What can I do to change tomorrow?
Just hold on to "now" the way it is...
To Be Continued
The girls embark on their
journey towards adulthood...
...as Neviril and Aer head
towards the "eternal present."
Next time on Simoun...
Pair
Pair.