Looks like we have 3 guests today.
No, that's 4 guests.
Meaning I'm a guest too?
Please call out the title of this show!
Monthly...
ADR...
Bulletin!
Simoun
Monthly! ADR Bulletin Special
Hello! I'm Mikako Takahashi,
and I play Roatreamon.
Yay!
How do you do. I'm Rika Morinaga,
the voice of Mamina.
Yo!
Hello. I'm Kaori Natsuka,
and I play Yun.
Hey!
It felt like we pretty much
had to do that or else, right?
Pretty much.
Not only that, but since
you were the third one...
...you had to be the grand finale!
Sorry, I wasn't much
of a grand finale.
With three guests instead of two,
it's pretty boisterous, isn't it?
Well, you're a lot more
boisterous than they are.
What did you say?
Three, two...
Simoun OX (TruelFalse) Talk!
All right.
Yes?
Time for the Simoun OX Quiz.
Okay.
That's what we're going to do.
Right, and it's self-explanatory.
Good job!
Really? Thanks.
Good.
Now then...
Okay!
...shall we begin?
Yeah.
Right. Here's the question!
You've changed somehow,
playing your current character...
Ready, set...
True!
Huh?
What?
False?
Huh?
What? I put up true.
I feel that compared
to myself today...
...I was much closer to
Roatreamon when I was younger.
It's not so much that I've changed,
but that I came to realize...
...that I might have been
more like her back then.
So I think, "You've
got to grow up!"...
...whenever I look at Roatreamon
more and more these days.
In my case, the reason
why I put up an X...
...is because Yun
really hates war.
And I've felt that
way for a long time.
"It would be best not to have
to go into battle at all."
That way of thinking hasn't
really changed for me.
So I can really relate to her.
It's not that I think, "I see..."
when Yun expresses her views...
...it's more like, "That's right."
So I feel that I can say my
lines straight from the heart.
I see.
How about you, Rika?
Nothing's changed at all.
I mean...
...I have the same kind
of personality as Mamina!
Really?
Yeah.
You mean like being mischievous?
That's you being mischievous?
I don't know if it's really mischief...
...but you know, like
playing little jokes.
Mamina-jokes?
Right, like playing Mamina-jokes.
Also, like when things aren't clear,
she turns around and explodes on you.
"Come on, you!" Like that.
You're right, Mamina's
the type who...
She always seems to be
crackling with emotion.
That's how she's
depicted in the show.
Mamina is the most
temperamental, don't you think?
She's a lot like Aer in that way...
Wait, you're probably right!
Yes, she does seem to be.
Right.
I'm convinced.
Yep.
All right, let's move on to
the next question. Drum roll...
You're 17 and you
must go to the Spring.
Would you choose to
become female after all?
Ready, set...
True!
This is interesting!
We're split...
This is interesting.
An X for you, Rika!
You're the only one.
I just want to see what it's like.
I mean, you can't go around
hitting on people if you're a girl.
But if you're a guy...
You want to hit on girls?
Don't you?
But why?
I don't want to hit on girls!
Come on, I want to go to the beach
and ask girls out like they do!
What the...
Why? Don't you mean you
want to be asked out?
No, I want to go up to an
easy-Iooking girl and pick her up!
Wouldn't that be awesome?
I mean, if you get
hit on like that...
...what do you do? Just bare
your fangs at the guy, right?
So I always wonder if there are
that many girls who do that...
...and I want to check
it out for myself.
You mean, girls who'd fall for your bait.
Right, right.
How many girls are there who'd
actually be like, "Ah, sure"?
You think there's that many?
I don't really want to check that out.
Question: Do you want me as your pair?
Hey, wait till I'm finished
asking the question!
Why, Oh Why!? Simoun.
All right!
All right then!
There's just too many of these...
...special, hard-to-memorize
Simoun terms.
So in this corner we're going to
try to refresh everyone's memory!
All right, Simoun-sama. If you please!
What in the world
is a helical motor?
Helical motor...
Helical motor is the one we always
disagree on where to put the accent.
Hey, that's right.
Is it helical MOtor
or is it helical moTOR?
And helical MOtor is the
correct way to say it?
Correct.
I think we just
reviewed the wrong thing.
Yeah, that wasn't it.
We need to go over its meaning.
Its meaning...
Meaning...
We have no idea, do we?
It's hard to actually
define something like that...
Isn't it like... the engine?
Engine?
The vehicle of the gods?
Um...
Vehicle of the gods?
It's part of the vehicle. Somewhere.
You mean the swirly thing?
The swirl...
That's not it?
Oh well, that's close enough.
What is the Helical Motor?
"An ancient system developed...
...in order to utilize the power
of the deity Tempus Spatium."
Even if you read the answer,
it doesn't really register.
It doesn't register at all for me!
And we've already been
through a lot of ADR sessions!
Oh, but I still haven't
uttered that line once yet.
Well, I've said it.
Really?
But I really, really
don't get it! I never have!
I'm just saying
whatever the script says!
The truth comes out!
You just confessed!
I've never had much to
do with all that, see.
The power of...
It's a system?
Meaning it's a system that
was built by somebody, right?
Long, long ago...
Oh, so it's like an Intel chip or
something? I mean, what do I know?
Am I wrong?
Well, I guess you could
say the nuance is the same.
Ah...
I see...
This one was a little hard to answer.
It was a hard question, wasn't it?
Are all the questions
going to be this difficult?
We're in for it...
I know...
Makes you nervous about
the next one, doesn't it?
What, you mean that's it?
Is it all right to
end it like this?
It seems all right. So we're
going to end this corner now.
So anyway, that's it for today.
Why, Oh Why!? Simoun.
Now then, time to
announce a Simoun product.
All right, time for a
product announcement.
You won't believe this, but...
...a Simoun game will be
coming out on the Playstation 2!
Game, game!
So tell us, what kind of
game is it going to be?
Right, the title is...
...Simoun: Battle of Thorns
- Seal by Ri M_a_jon.
It's a bit...
That's the title.
Sounds fierce.
Yes, for some reason it sounds fierce.
I've never even heard
of "sealing by Ri M_a_jon"!
I know!
Uh...
"The recording process
is on a marvelous roll!"
That's what it says here.
Right.
Is the recording going well?
Oh, sure! I'm at the top of my game!
It's going well for us too, right?
Yeah!
So anyway, we hope you're
looking forward to...
...the release of this new
Simoun Playstation 2 game!
Working with you has worn me out.
Those are my lines!
All right then...
Good job, everyone!
Good job!
So what did you think?
Mmm...
Kaori?
What, me?
I really caught you off guard!
Yeah, you did!
Well, we were told we could
start off in a laid-back way...
...but now I'm worried if
they can even use this...
I know. I'm really worried too.
For the most part, all we really
did was chat about stuff, right?
Yes. I think the editors have
their work cut out for them!
It was like we were
broadcasting the fact that...
...we had no knowledge of Simoun!
We came off like Simoun newbies!
Even though the three of us
have already done a lot of ADR.
So we should have a lot more
advance knowledge than everyone else!
But we ended up making a
lot of clueless comments!
But let's not dwell on that!
It was laid-back...
Yeah, it was a lot of fun!
Let's do a good job recording!
Oh, right, the ADR.
Let's do our best!
Right!
So, anyway, there are still a lot
of Simoun episodes coming up...
...so please keep watching Simoun!
Please continue to watch!
Don't miss the next episode!!