Hello, I'm your emcee, Simoun.
Excuse me, but I just said that I'm...
Excuse me, but I just
said that I'm the emcee!
Monthly!
ADR!
Bulletin!
Simoun
Monthly! ADR Bulletin
Hello, everybody! I'm Nana
Mizuki, and I play Morinas.
Hello, I'm Fumie Mizusawa,
and I play Wap_o_rif.
They said this is the fifth
installment.
I know!
That's what I heard.
Wonder what's in store for us?
We're standing here, but we
really don't have any idea.
I wonder what we're going to do?
Well, they did tell us to relax.
They said don't be nervous.
Yes, let's just be laid-back about
it and deliver a relaxed program.
You mean just act the way we
usually do?
What do you mean by that?
Oh, you be quiet!
Don't drag me into that...
And that's the way we usually are...
Why don't we proceed with
this "Monthly ADR Bulletin"?
Here we go.
By the way, do you know
what the word "Simoun" means?
What's that?
Simouns are...
I want to know Simoun!
Hello, hello...
In this corner, we'll be
talking about our partners...
Partners since we're not pairs.
But we are partners!
That's right, in
another way... Oh, my...
Go for it!
Anyway, we'll be talking about what
we
really want to know about our
partner.
In other words, we're
going to ask each other.
And by doing that...
How should I say it?
Our love will grow deeper!
Like making our bond stronger?
Would you like to try making it
deeper?
Want to do it?
So anyway, we gave this a
lot of thought, didn't we?
Who should go first?
You're always first, right?
Are you serious?
Really?
No, really, really.
All right then, we'll
start with Morinas.
Okay, ta-da!
In your opinion, what are
Wap_o_rif's selling points?
And please try to make
Morinas swoon with your answer!
Make me swoon like crazy!
Selling points?
All right, then. From the
front she looks feminine...
...but from behind you see
that reverse-triangle shape!
I'd say that's her "moe-point"!
Oh, that's a good point!
See, she's actually pretty muscular.
Right, really sturdy...
Not to mention, she's olive toned.
Love it!
That's her selling point, I think.
Okay, can I go now?
Ta-da!
What's the best technique for
making yourself look erotically
cool?
Please instruct us, Mizuki-sensei!
Come on!
Remember how surprised we were
when we read the background info?
We were surprised!
Because it actually said
to sound "erotically cool."
They even used that person's name.
It was like, "It's written here! K-
san!"
You had to be like "K-san's child."
I was like, what kind of child is that?
I've done a lot of animated shows...
...and read a lot of
character-background fact sheets...
But none were as shocking as this
one!
The one for this girl.
Because you were a K-girl,
basically!
And whenever we were doing a
scene
that had subtle, nuanced
moments...
...the recording
director would tell me...
..."In an erotically cool way! That's
where you've got to be erotically
cool!"
I was like, "Erotically cool?
Sensei, what do you mean by that?"
"Please tell me!" That's what
was going through my mind.
I was surprised too.
I was always thinking how
hard it must be for you.
Still, Morinas did turn
out to be erotically cool!
That makes me so happy!
You were very appealing.
I dug down deep and emotionally let
all the erotically cool vibes out.
You released them from within! In
front of the microphone? Hit that
mic!
Make those vibes hit that mic!
So I really didn't want
anyone to see my face.
No looking!
Please listen with your eyes closed!
That's what it was like for me.
I have something I'd like to ask you
too.
Next corner, please!
Why, Oh Why!? Simoun.
All right...
The question for this corner
will be asked by Simoun?
Okay, if you please!
What is "Sibylla Aurea"?
The thing is we can't just come
out with the answer, like boom!
We need to do it gradually.
It's hard to do this without warming
up.
It's easier if the answer comes to
us in the middle of the
conversation.
We can kind of get away
with scamming it that way.
We're thinking of that
word, right? That word?
All right, the answer is...
Ready?
Neviril!
Not bad, you two.
Congratulations!
The top-ranked Simoun sibylla.
"The Golden Priestess."
The Golden Priestess!
The one who sparkles
with a golden sheen!
The one we have to do this to!
On the way to the Spring,
everyone was doing this!
I see...
Sibylla Aurea? The one who
dazzles us with her golden sheen.
Goldie!
That's it.
Time to present our merchandise...
Ta-da!
So erotic!
What are we gonna do with this?
You should probably hide it
between other CDs when you buy it.
Simoun OST 2
Now, now, don't talk about it
like it's a really naughty item.
Because it isn't, really.
Guess what?
This CD includes Roatreamon's
Lullaby!
The one she sang to Rimone...
...and she sang it to Mamina too.
You could also hear the
melody during the show.
And this soundtrack
includes this lullaby.
I hope you all enjoy this CD!
By the way, who in the world are
you?
I'd like to ask that of you!
All right, good job!
And thank you all for watching!
What did you think?
We asked at the same time!
Our bond must have
gotten a little stronger!
Well, I have to say I got a
little nervous during the quiz.
So did I!
I was so worried we
wouldn't be able to answer!
If even the cast members can't
answer,
that would be so lame, wouldn't it?
I really think so!
I'm so glad I did my homework!
Yes, thank goodness!
We have to be thankful
for our intuition!
Right, Morinas?
Oh, please!
Anyway, I think we might have
made too much of a commotion...
...but thanks for putting up with us.
And please continue to watch
Simoun until the very end!
Thanks for your support!
For both the show and the DVDs as
well!
Please check out the DVDs!