The countless flowers,
enveloped in light...
...gaze at tomorrow
with unwavering eyes.
Everyone wishes for me to be pure...
...but what can I bring
with me to the frayed skies?
What I've made my own
by breaking off flowers in bloom...
All such sinful things...
Why did I stop making
promises with the future?
Because even if I try
to run far from all the pain...
...a cold wind rustles
my hair... Don't you see?
Where can I ever find the answer?
It's the enemy!
They've spotted us!
Retreat at full speed!
The fact that the enemy Simouns
showed up in battle today...
...was a taunt to let us know
they can attack us at any time.
And that's exactly
what they're capable of.
Eternal Maidens
So it's really over now?
The war, that is...
Yes.
So now we can finally devote our
lives to just offering prayers?
Yes.
Yeah, but...
Why is it that it doesn't
make us feel better?
I want to see that other world.
The one that Grandpa was
always yearning to see.
A different world than this one...
That's why I became a sibylla,
so I could get there!
But now...
Amuria...
What?
Then does that mean that Amuria
may also be alive somewhere?
That won't do.
Vice Chancellor?
Please don't call me that.
That is no longer my title.
Though its life may have ended...
...this flower can still
provide solace at least.
Didn't you attend the ceremony?
No.
The war has ended.
And that means it's all over now.
Still provide solace, did I say?
But I no longer have the power to do so.
I can no longer protect my Neviril.
What?
What did you say?
Those are the two conditions set by...
...Shoukoku and the Plumbum highlands
in exchange for the ceasefire.
Nobody ever thought to inform me!
We're to be treated as their
equals, if only on the surface.
And just whose doing would that be?
Think about it carefully.
"War is foolishness..."
Isn't that right, High Priestess?
The military governors from
Plumbum and Shoukoku have arrived.
Ah, we have been waiting for you...
Is this really how
things should turn out?
Yes.
I...
All I ever wanted was for the sibyllae
to continue praying to the skies.
Nothing more...
But with this change...
Anubituf...
The way the high priestess
was acting just now...
What?
Never mind.
Why are they still around when
the peace ceremony is over?
I heard that some of their forces
are staying on the Arcus Prima.
The more I think of it, the less I
understand what this "peace" is about.
There's nothing we can do about it.
Until they found the ancient Simouns,
it was their comrades who were dying.
So this is what they
look like in person.
Roatreamon...
All those faces that we
extinguished with our Ri Majons...
We never even knew
what they looked like.
I'm sure...
...they didn't know what
we looked like either.
Well, the food's
getting cold. Let's eat!
Here, Roatreamon, have some of my fish.
Excuse me?
You're getting too thin, you know!
You have to get more nourishment.
Right.
Thank you!
Vura, you sound like her mom!
Do I?
Your legs are in the way!
Get those filthy legs
of yours out of our way!
Yeah, I know you can't understand
a word I'm saying, but...
Foreign
Huh? I see that you
know I'm insulting you!
Foreign
You...
Please forgive us,
Sibylla Aurea Neviril!
We have committed an unspeakable sin!
Neviril?
I bless you. Go in peace...
Bless us?
I bless you all...
Neviril...
Hey, you're in the shower too?
Yes.
Can I borrow your soap?
Sure.
Wow, yours are pretty huge, aren't they?
What are?
They're always getting in my way.
Oh, right. Because you're
going to become a man, right?
I have to become a man, or...
I have to become strong, or...
I can never protect what's dear to me.
You know what? Neviril
told me something once...
To become strong by being held...
You're wrong about that, Alty.
It's only when you've
both become strong...
...that you can truly
hold each other close.
I see...
I see!
I always thought I wanted
to become a man too.
But now I think I can manage
without making that change.
Big Sister...
You should accept yourself as you
are. Your life will be easier then.
Onasia!
Onasia, how did you get here?
I know you were at the Ruins,
so how in the world...
If you believed that to be true,
then why did you come here?
Well...
This is an extremely
unstable place to be.
The Ruins served as the
training grounds for Chor Dextra.
So many abortive Emerald Ri Majons
exploded into oblivion there.
The helical motors...
...are believed to
manipulate time and space.
Yes.
And because of this, Space
and Time were distorted...
...causing the Spring to exist
simultaneously in two different places.
I find all of this hard to believe.
There are very few things that
people can actually believe...
...when they are unable
to believe in themselves.
It's as you say.
I wanted to be near my comrades
who had fallen in battle...
...yet I was also trying to flee
as far away from them as possible.
But how did you know that?
Because I was the same way.
I shied away from making a choice...
...and tried to run as far
away from reality as possible.
Perhaps I've been seeking
you out all this time.
Perhaps I wanted...
...to have someone hear my confession.
To hear...
...my sins...
One of the conditions of our peace
treaty with Plumbum and Shoukoku...
...calls for the
dissolution of Chor Tempest.
Where did Yun run off
to at a time like this?
I know...
I don't want any part of this!
Roatreamon?
Chor Tempest, disbanded?
After all the effort we
put into it until now?
The Plumbum priestesses will be
taking over our duties, right?
I'm confused. Is this what peace is?
We can never hope to be on equal terms.
But I don't understand!
One thing's for sure.
They have no use for
us anymore. That's all.
Just when we finally
started to understand...
...the true meaning of
our prayers as sibyllae.
Even after Chor Tempest
ceases to exist...
...nothing can change the fact
that we're all Simoun sibyllae.
And nobody will ever debase our prayers.
Nobody!
If Chor Tempest is disbanded...
Huh? What's this, all of a sudden?
...we won't be able to
fly the Simouns anymore.
The door to that other world...
...will be closed to us.
You've always longed to see
that other world, haven't you?
In that case...
I don't remember you being so talkative.
What?
Never mind.
Aer!
We haven't talked like
this in a long time.
No.
Neviril...
What?
Would you...
Would you give me your blessing too?
What?
Of course I will!
Neviril...
Aer?
What's going on? Sulking, are you?
Did you have a fight with Neviril?
Huh? Why are you
asking me about Neviril?
Right on the money, huh?
Neviril...
She's changed.
What do you mean?
She talks up a storm now.
Well, you can always use
your mouth to stop her!
Boy, kissing is all you
ever think about, Floe!
You told me it's when you really like
someone that you want to kiss them.
So don't you want to kiss her?
Not the way Neviril is now.
Don't you like her anymore?
Ha! You're just jealous.
No, I'm not! Huh?
What's going on? I feel hot all over!
Oh boy, you're in critical condition!
Hold up! What do you mean, critical?
It might not just be Neviril, you know?
It could be that you've
changed as well, Aer.
Sibylla Neviril!
Where is Sibylla Aer? Where is she?
High Priestess!
What is it, High Priestess?
I suppose you'll do, Sibylla
Paraietta. Come with me!
Follow me. Please. Hurry!
High Priestess?
You must take off now, Sibylla
Paraietta, Sibylla Neviril!
What?
There's no time to lose! You must
go at once! If you don't hurry...
...the door will close on us!
Never to open again!
The door?
A long time ago...
...I was a member of Chor Dextra.
What?
I dreamed of completing
the Emerald Ri Majon.
I dreamed of becoming an eternal maiden.
Eternal maiden?
A Simoun is much like a maiden herself.
A maiden vacillates...
The Simoun gem reflects
that vacillating soul.
A maiden drifts...
Escaping reality for all eternity...
Tracing the skies with
her everlasting beauty...
Please slow down, Your Eminence!
The Emerald Ri Majon!
You must change Kyuukoku's fate!
We cannot go on like this!
Unless we do something about it, we...
Foreign
Hurry! You must go now!
To the Land of Hope!
What?
Foreign
You're keeping something
from me, aren't you?
I want to know what it is.
But...
I want to hold you.
As your friend.
Paraietta...
Allow me to show you.
When one flees from reality...
...refusing to choose a gender...
...this is what becomes of you.
It is played by my wounds...
the song of prayer.
Let it ring out over
the grieving universe.
Can we change tomorrow?
Don't be afraid.
I want to let you know
how my heart's overflowing.
I want to get closer to you.
I want to feel your pulse.
I was too defiant,
and I took the long way around.
The blue moon is swaying silently.
My true heart's desire is you.
I can't reach you.
My tears of pain trickle down.
Soar away into the sky, song of prayer.
Carrying my love that came too late.
What can I do to change tomorrow?
Just hold on to "now" the way it is...
To Be Continued
Neviril bares her soul to Aer...
...and the other sibyllae make
their way towards the Spring.
Next time on Simoun...
Choices
Choices.