The countless flowers,
enveloped in light...
...gaze at tomorrow
with unwavering eyes.
Everyone wishes for me to be pure...
...but what can I bring
with me to the frayed skies?
What I've made my own
by breaking off flowers in bloom...
All such sinful things...
Why did I stop making
promises with the future?
Because even if I try
to run far from all the pain...
...a cold wind rustles
my hair... Don't you see?
Where can I ever find the answer?
The Door to a New World
I've never seen
such insubordination!
This is why I was against
disbanding Rubor and Caput!
We cannot afford to rely
solely on Chor Tempest!
Gather all our troops and Similes!
The patrol Similes and the
cruise Similes. I want them all!
Yes, sir!
What a fool.
Conflict will not
bring about a solution.
Onasia...
I told you not to do that!
Stop playing with the Simoun!
Huh? So how come?
How come?
Well, because...
Let's see...
What's that?
It's making a sound,
like it's humming!
No way!
Hey, you're right!
It's humming.
It sounds like a whistle!
You too, Rimone!
Well? Well?
I can hear a humming sound.
Right? Right?
I see...
So that day has finally come.
Please give us a little time.
Would you mind waiting
until we've finished eating?
Have negotiations
broken down then?
Onasia is the symbol
of Simulacrum Kyuukoku.
Undoubtedly it is to our
superiors' advantage that she...
...maintain her current silence.
Nevertheless, should Onasia
decide to make a move...
I certainly don't enjoy conflict.
Even so...
Bringing Onasia here
at a time like this...
I just don't understand what the
high priestess could be thinking.
Guragief...
Suppose I...
What?
Never mind...
Taking off in the Simouns
without authorization...
...is an unprecedented infraction!
Where is your sense
of responsibility?
Responsibility?
Do we recognize that we're Simoun
sibyllae and take pride in that?
Yes, I would say that's true
of each and every one of us!
Is that all you have to say to us?
If so, please excuse us.
You little brats!
Paraietta...
Vura...
And Roatreamon and Alty, too!
Just as we thought, Paraietta...
You couldn't sleep either, huh?
Neither could we.
Para-sama...
Hey, is the whole gang here then?
We shall send Onasia
back on the Messis.
Sibylla Neviril, Sibylla Aer...
May I ask you to join us?
Do you not want to know more
about that different world?
Me too...
Will you take me too?
Um...
No, we cannot go in
such great numbers.
Please.
Is it good?
Um...
I'm not sure...
...I'd call it good.
It's a little bitter, I think.
And it's also a little bit sweet.
But it's not that
I don't like it.
I think...
...I can finish it all.
"I don't know..."
What?
You've stopped saying
that all the time, Rimone.
Yes...
I'm starting to realize...
...that if you really think about it,
there's nothing you can't understand.
That's why...
I'm the opposite.
The more I think about
something, the more lost I get.
Dominüra...
All right, let's finish eating,
and then we're going.
Where?
I don't know.
The high priestess
has ordered us...
...to make this as smooth
a flight as possible.
Right.
I wonder where we're headed.
What do you want?
Um...
Onasia-sama is at rest now.
Let her in.
Onasia?
Why did she bring up
the "different world"?
That high priestess...
There's something about her.
Sure, the military councilor's
an annoying old man too...
...but that high priestess...
...I don't know...
What?
Your hands...
...they're so small.
Don't treat me like a kid!
War makes things that
should be obvious...
...so very hard
to see, doesn't it?
Onasia...
There is something
you wish to ask me.
You told me that you
could hear Mamina's voice.
So... what about my comrades?
Have their souls been released?
The one who really
wishes to be released...
...is you yourself.
By placing yourself at the
brink of your comrades' deaths...
...you are actually trying to flee
as far as possible from those deaths.
Onasia-sama...
We seem to have arrived.
Why the Ruins?
There it goes again.
The door to a new world!
The melody played
by that music box...
...as well as the unintended destination
of those who lost their lives here.
What?
That's right...
This was once the training
ground for Chor Dextra.
Chor Dextra?
Sibylla Aer...
...that was the chor your own
grandfather served as regina for.
Grandpa... a regina?
Can I ask you something?
Yes.
That day...
What happened that day?
What day?
On the Messis...
It all came surging back...
What?
The moment I looked into
the helical motors...
It was as if I was seeing...
Somebody's...
The memory of something...
What you see there is
nothing but a helix.
As it turns out, the only thing
we're capable of understanding is...
Sibylla Dominüra?
Dominüra...
And then we became enthralled
with Ri Majons... and the Simouns.
But that was because we had nothing
but the Simouns to cling to...
That's right...
If the Simouns had never
existed in the first place...
Or even if they had existed...
...but no one ever
discovered how to use them...
...then what would have happened?
Huh? Well...
Um...
I think...
We brought them here!
They're here!
Long, long ago, there was a
civilization far superior to ours.
And it is said that the Simouns
were in existence at that time.
But after a succession
of wars broke out...
...the country was left in ruins.
And once all of the lands
were rendered worthless...
...there was no longer
any reason to wage war.
The starving multitudes no
longer needed the Simouns...
...and eventually they
forgot how to use them.
The people...
...had no choice but to wait for
certain destruction at nature's hands.
It was then that something
broke through the sky...
...and a Simoun arrived
from a different world.
On board that Simoun
were two children of God.
These young girls...
These young girls announced
themselves as "Simoun sibyllae."
And...
They then shared the secret
of the Emerald Ri Majon!
The Emerald Ri Majon?
That's right.
To a different world...
No, that which transports one to a
different time, the ultimate Ri Majon!
It is a divine gift.
A magnificent "if."
What if during that era...
...they had told the people
that another war was coming?
If the Simouns hadn't existed...
...then I might never
have existed either.
If, during that era...
...they found a way to convince the
people of the need for Simouns...
But if I'd never existed...
...then this pain never
would've existed either.
This era so full of hardship
and strife might be changed.
To transcend time and space...
...and offer this
"if" to some other era.
That is precisely the purpose...
...of the Simouns and
of the Emerald Ri Majon.
Transcend time and space?
Unbelievable... How could that...
Wait a minute! Then what about this
Chor Dextra you say my grandpa led?
Chor Dextra...
...was created for the sole purpose
of completing the Emerald Ri Majon.
Someone you know very well was
also a former member of this chor.
Huh?
Sibylla Dominüra...
She is the last surviving
member of Chor Dextra.
Dominüra?
That's right.
I had the misfortune to find out...
That everything...
That everything that
happened started with me.
Just now...
What?
I thought about what
you just said, Dominüra.
You know, if the Simouns
had never existed...
If they hadn't?
Yes.
Then I never would've met
everyone in Chor Tempest.
And, Dominüra...
...I never would've met you.
Why are you crying?
I wonder why?
Well...
Um...
Because you're sad?
Because you're lonely?
Because it hurts?
What else...
Let's see...
Because you're happy?
That's right.
Because I'm happy.
Let's go.
You mean go without
knowing where again?
No.
I do know where.
Under the blue sky.
Beyond the white clouds.
It's as blue as a tear.
As white as a lily.
In the pitch-black darkness.
The light of a red flame.
Sibylla Dominüra most likely
completed the Emerald Ri Majon.
Then you mean...
She is alive in another time.
Sibylla Dominüra and Sibylla
Rimone are both alive.
I am certain that they are.
Then...
Amuria...
...does that mean that Amuria
may also be alive somewhere?
The Emerald Ri Majon was a
divine gift. Our only hope...
Whether it will take us into the
future or back into the past...
That is not for us to know.
However...
...it is by the will of the gods of
Tempus Spatium that the Simouns exist.
Therefore...
...the gods cannot be mistaken.
I am positive that they will
open the door to the correct era.
Sibylla Neviril...
Sibylla Aer...
I would like to...
...entrust this task to you.
The Emerald Ri Majon!
Get a move on!
You say it's a Simoun
from the Arcus Niger?
Military councilor!
What's the meaning of this?
The Arcus Niger...
...was shot down.
Wha?
Seven o'clock! Five ancient
Simouns approaching fast!
What in the world?
It is played by my wounds...
the song of prayer.
Let it ring out over
the grieving universe.
Can we change tomorrow?
Don't be afraid.
I want to let you know
how my heart's overflowing.
I want to get closer to you.
I want to feel your pulse.
I was too defiant,
and I took the long way around.
The blue moon is swaying silently.
My true heart's desire is you.
I can't reach you.
My tears of pain trickle down.
Soar away into the
sky, song of prayer.
Carrying my love that came too late.
What can I do to change tomorrow?
Just hold on to "now" the way it is...
To Be Continued
The Shoukoku-Plumbum highlands allied forces...
...have begun their
invasion of Kyuukoku...
...and the attacks are
increasing by the day.
Next time on Simoun...
Sortie
Sortie.