The countless flowers,
enveloped in light...
...gaze at tomorrow
with unwavering eyes.
Everyone wishes for me to be pure...
...but what can I bring
with me to the frayed skies?
What I've made my own
by breaking off flowers in bloom...
All such sinful things...
Why did I stop making
promises with the future?
Because even if I try
to run far from all the pain...
...a cold wind rustles
my hair... Don't you see?
Where can I ever find the answer?
As planned...
...with communication cables
intact, Chor Tempest...
...will descend as low as possible...
...and protect the Ruins from attack
by the Shoukoku-highland forces.
The enemy?
The Funeral
This sibylla's spirit is
bound by chains of sin.
Nevertheless, both the merciful
Tempus Spatium, as well as Kyuukoku...
...are prepared to
forgive and accept her.
But why the heck was Anglas lying
dead inside an ancient Simoun?
That day, there's no
question that she...
Aer!
They never found so much as
a bone fragment in the debris.
This sibylla has just received
the divine grace of Tempus Spatium.
Now that she is about to set off
on a new journey, let us pray.
She was a highland priestess.
Not only that, but a spy.
How can we hold a funeral
for her on the Arcus Prima?
The high priestess felt it
was the right thing to do.
And how did the
military council feel?
That since the Highlands and
Shoukoku are now allies...
...it wouldn't do to send
even the remains back to them.
And yet they're so full
of mutual animosity.
Yes, it seems they do agree
on the most unlikely thing.
And that's what
causes trouble for us.
You won't get a
breeze sitting here.
Neviril.
To think that you'd start a
conversation with me... Who knew?
What happened at the Ruins...
Yeah.
Huh?
What?
The Spring.
We found the Spring
inside the Ruins.
And Onasia was there.
This is...
...the Spring itself.
It's just like Grandpa said!
And then we found Anglas, who
surely perished in that explosion...
...inside an ancient Simoun.
I'm thinking that Anglas
went there herself.
What?
In that moment...
...the moment the Simoun exploded...
...she went to a different world.
A different...
...world?
Just when we thought we were
back home on the Arcus Prima...
...all these weird
things started happening!
At least give us a
little downtime, right?
There's no time to get comfortable.
We're to go to the maju
pool right after this.
I do like majus...
...but not if we're
being ordered to do them!
Wait, isn't that Neviril
and Aer over there?
Hey, so they managed to make up!
What do you mean, make up?
Neviril was just having
a hissy fit on her own!
W-Wait, Aer. What do you mean by...
It's something Grandpa told me once.
Hey, hurry up! This way!
Grandpa, come on! Hurry!
Aer!
This is as far as I can go.
Huh?
You go on ahead.
Getting old means making
more and more choices.
And with every choice you make...
...you erase all
other possibilities.
But I don't understand!
The Simoun will show
you where you're headed.
Where I'm headed?
To a different world!
What my grandpa meant by
that, I still don't know.
But Grandpa was
always yearning for it.
Aer, is that why you never
wanted to choose your gender?
The helical motors...
Said to manipulate
both time and space...
I thought it was
no more than a story...
...to strengthen the
mystery of the Simouns.
"Everywhere...
...and yet nowhere."
If that's true of Onasia...
...and true of Anglas...
...and true of the Simouns...
Then maybe...
...it's true of Rimone
and Dominüra as well.
What we just talked about...
Let's keep it between ourselves.
So we're going to share a secret!
Just the two of us!
Yes, we are.
Why didn't you attend
Anglas's funeral?
Those are the rules.
A priestess from a
lowly family like mine...
...has no right to
attend a holy ceremony.
B-But why?
You joined us the other time.
Things are different now.
Our leaders are in turmoil.
But they allowed an enemy
priestess's funeral to be held here.
You don't sound
like yourself at all.
I thought you
liked that Anglas girl.
But...
I knew I'd have to face at least
this level of discrimination.
What?
The only reason I got to the rank
of Simoun sibylla was because...
...I had the backing
of the vice chancellor.
Mamina.
But the vice chancellor has changed.
Hmph!
He's nothing but a
senile old geezer now.
W-Wait a minute, Mamina!
I enjoyed our time on the Messis,
especially that mouse stew I made.
Huh?
Watching all you oh-so-noble
priestesses taste that stew...
...I thought, "Hey, they're
just the same as me!"
That's right. We're the same!
Nope.
We're not the same after all.
Mamina...
Please wait a moment.
The maju pool is under the
jurisdiction of the chancellors.
Should you set foot in this area...
...the high priestess will...
It doesn't matter.
Military Councilor.
You must forgive us...
...but we can't have
so many observers.
It will disturb our prayers.
A maju is not a prayer.
What?
It is battle practice,
Sibylla Aurea.
I'd like to see for myself.
What Chor Tempest is
currently capable of...
The Ri Majon with the
most destructive power!
What a lovely wake
they're creating.
The Dandelion Ri Majon?
The one that harms no one...
...that leads no one astray...
...the one for ceremonies...
Hmph!
It's better this way.
I didn't make the
wrong choice after all.
Entrusting Aer to
become Neviril's pair...
Yes, it's all good
because of that.
You have no clue whatsoever!
Could the judgment of
someone who's been asleep...
...be less questionable
than your own?
Thinking someone
like you can protect her...
...is gross arrogance.
I...
...let Neviril...
I think...
...I might have made a mistake.
With you...
Don't say it.
I think...
...I might have made a mistake.
I want to pair up with you.
Yes.
After all, I'm the one who
should be protecting you.
Dismantle a Simoun...
I never thought I'd hear those
words from anyone else but you...
...Sibylla Dominüra.
Forget about that day, Waporif.
That's the last warning
I'll be giving you.
But how could I ever forget?
"Without something to believe in...
...none of us can even
plant our feet on the earth."
That's what you told me.
Have you found
something to believe in?
What am I supposed to do now?
What should I believe in?
I have ordered
the maintenance crew...
...to dismantle the ancient
Simoun as you instructed.
Dismantling a divine vessel.
How sacrilegious.
Which is more sacrilegious?
Allowing our holy Tempus Spatium
to be tainted by outsiders?
The topic for discussion today...
...is what to do about
that enemy air base.
As most of the ancient Simouns
are now in the enemy's hands...
...I believe it would be
dangerous to send Chor Tempest...
...out on a reconnaissance mission...
Then when would you deem it safe?
I understand your concern for
your daughter's well-being.
However, should another
incident occur...
...next time for sure, you won't have
a leg to stand on, Vice Chancellor.
Who is paired up with Sibylla Neviril?
That would be Sibylla Aer.
Out of all the members
of Chor Tempest...
...she has no parallel
as an auriga.
Sibylla Aer?
If I recall, her grandfather was...
Even so, she herself...
What is the meaning of this?
Oh, please forgive me.
Where are you taking her?
Sibylla Yun.
Anglas's funeral is long over.
Shouldn't she have been committed
to the earth as soon as possible?
This is an order from
the military councilor.
The military councilor?
How dare you debase a departed
spirit. I won't allow this to happen!
Once you've left the cockpit of a
Simoun, a woman is utterly powerless.
It would be too
dangerous to sit back...
...and do nothing about
that mobile air base.
We are hereby sending Chor Tempest
on a reconnaissance mission.
The Messis shall serve
as the relay point...
What? Just when we finally got away
from that musty, old rust bucket!
I am happy to welcome
you all back, Sibyllae!
Ugh...
And if we discover the base?
That will be left to
your discretion, but...
As for me...
...I do believe you have the
capacity to blow it up at this point.
As both Sibylla Dominüra and Sibylla
Rimone are missing in action...
...we will have to
readjust your pairings.
Sibylla Paraietta and Sibylla Kaim.
Sibylla Alty and Sibylla Floe.
Sibylla Roatreamon and Sibylla Morinas.
Sibylla Neviril...
...and Sibylla Mamina.
Sibylla Yun and Sibylla Aer...
It's been decided that you two will
sit out this particular mission.
What are you talking about?
Why am I being left behind?
Aer is my pair.
You'll have to convince me as well!
Neviril...
Please, don't cause
any more trouble for me.
What's the matter?
You can't sleep, Neviril?
No.
Your maju this afternoon.
It was magnificent.
Thank you.
How about... a dance?
I'm sorry. I'm not in the mood.
What?
I never thought you'd
stand up for Aer.
It's not that I've opened
up to her completely.
But by coming face
to face with Aer...
...I'm also coming face
to face with Amuria...
...meaning I'm facing
up to myself as well.
That may have been my
greatest fear all this time.
And I was just trying to avoid it.
I've allowed you all to
humor me far too long.
So let me humor you.
Paraietta.
You can go ahead
and lean on me.
But at this rate...
...I won't make it to a different world.
What?
Nothing, never mind
what I just said.
A different world, you say?
If it's a different
world you long for...
...then I'll show you one now!
Parai...
What is it?
You're awake?
Yun's fast asleep, I think.
I just thought you might
be too nervous to sleep.
Pairing up with Sibylla Aurea...
...I always saw that as the
fastest way to achieve my goals.
Right.
But I don't want you
to get the wrong idea.
What?
Deep down, I do want the rest
of you to see me as an equal.
But...
...not for the same
reasons as before.
It's because...
...I really want to be
friends with you all.
Mamina...
So stop saying things like,
"We're friends," will you?
It's just a matter of
how you feel about me.
Okay.
Mamina, do you want me
to sing you a lullaby?
You mean the one
you sang for Rimone?
Give me a break!
I'm not a child.
Hear the echo...
Sorry, not listening.
...of the swirling light...
...bringing us tales of joy.
Proof that an
eternal world exists...
...shall be revealed
by Tempus Spatium.
Rocking gently until
we awake tomorrow...
Why do you think they
took you off the mission?
I have a pretty good idea.
You do, huh?
What about you?
There's something that bothers me.
What's that?
I can't tell you...
...because I promised not to.
I see.
That's wise of you.
Promises are made
to be kept after all.
I've got to go now.
As do I.
It is played by my wounds...
the song of prayer.
Let it ring out over
the grieving universe.
Can we change tomorrow?
Don't be afraid.
I want to let you know
how my heart's overflowing.
I want to get closer to you.
I want to feel your pulse.
I was too defiant,
and I took the long way around.
The blue moon is swaying silently.
My true heart's desire is you.
I can't reach you.
My tears of pain trickle down.
Soar away into the
sky, song of prayer.
Carrying my love that came too late.
What can I do to change tomorrow?
Just hold on to "now" the way it is...
To Be Continued
Neviril's Simoun is shot down...
...and forced to make an emergency
landing on Shoukoku's aerial base.
Next time on Simoun...
Sibylla
Sibylla.