The countless flowers,
enveloped in light...
...gaze at tomorrow
with unwavering eyes.
Everyone wishes for me to be pure...
...but what can I bring
with me to the frayed skies?
What I've made my own
by breaking off flowers in bloom...
All such sinful things...
Why did I stop making
promises with the future?
Because even if I try
to run far from all the pain...
...a cold wind rustles
my hair... Don't you see?
Where can I ever find the answer?
Who are you? What are you doing?
Oh my.
How'd you get in here?
The Simouns really
are nothing like Similes.
I asked who you were.
Also, those clothes...
Sorry, Waporif!
She's one of our new recruits.
Forgive me.
I didn't know you were a sibylla.
Not at all.
I should be apologizing to you.
That's Morinas.
Yes.
The helical motors
were discovered like this...
...two spiral-shaped
devices always in pairs.
And so that humans could
board and control them...
...two cockpits and instrument
panels were added later.
The collective term we
use for convenience is Simoun.
Yes, that's right.
Most likely,
what's controlling this side is...
Most likely?
Right. Most likely,
what's controlling this side...
...first existed in space. Perhaps
we should call it the power of space.
And controlling the other side is what
we might call the power of time.
That's uncertain too?
Yes, it is.
Actually, we know almost
nothing about the helical motors...
...that were excavated
from the earth's depths.
All we know...
...is how to operate them.
We only maintain the sections
added on top of the helical motors.
That's the story.
I see.
But Simile Simouns were built based
on helical-motor research, right?
Yes, but riding them till now, you know
the Similes' capabilities best of all.
Compared to Simouns,
Similes are just low-quality knockoffs.
There's no comparison.
Oh, I've heard there's no conclusive
data on the Simouns as of yet.
It's not good to hold back.
Hold back?
Simouns are holy vessels offered up
to Tempus Spatium in sacred rituals.
We regard them accordingly.
Exactly, Morinas.
We are here to offer
the Ri Majon to Tempus Spatium.
As priestesses
serving Tempus Spatium.
I'm no priestess.
Then what are you?
I just want to fly a Simoun.
I'm not a priestess like you.
But...
But?
I'm no soldier.
You're not either, right, Paraietta?
Oh, Paraietta. And you are?
That's Morinas, Floe.
Oh, right.
It's Morinas, right? Morinas...
Good morning, Floe.
Jeez, I just can't remember names.
And besides...
Sorry. When I first saw you, I thought
you were Waporif's new girlfriend.
That couldn't be.
My windshield's twisted.
I want it looked at.
Understood!
In the afternoon, I want more details of
the Similes and Simouns' differences.
I'll be happy to.
Not just with the Simouns...
If you ever need to, you can
ask us anything about this ship.
Thank you.
Wait. I'll go with you.
So was that helpful, Morinas?
I wonder if I'll learn
something new this afternoon.
The Distant War
Neviril...
I am grateful that you've
returned from the Spring.
I assume this means you've chosen
to continue on as a Simoun sibylla?
I am still not certain. Besides...
Besides?
I am currently without a pair.
Still, you have returned.
Huh? What are you guys doing?
You're late, Aer.
Oh, right. Sorry, sorry.
For what?
Our ceremony where we gather
in the ballroom after breakfast.
Oh, the one from when
the chor was on graveyard shift?
Anyway, would you like to have
a maju session in the pool at 3 PM?
All of us?
This is compulsory?
Yes.
At 3 PM?
It's a good idea. Let's do it.
Since we're all a little...
We have lost three comrades.
And afterwards,
three more left for the Spring.
And in this emergency,
we've been relieved of night duties.
We were the elite.
As priestesses and as sibyllae.
We'll regain our glory.
I'd like to.
I just joined, so being in
a maju with an active chor is nice.
So you're saying to do this at 3 PM?
Hey, what's this
about 3 PM anyway?
That's when...
3 PM is always Neviril's maju time.
Sibylla Aurea Neviril.
I am honored to meet you.
And you're...
I just joined the most
powerful chor... Chor Tempest.
This is Morinas.
I see. Please try to get
along with the others.
Aer, you team up with Morinas.
I thought I was paired with you.
Don't be so arrogant just
because you were once.
First of all, no one thinks
you're capable of replacing Amuria...
That's enough, Paraietta.
Excuse me...
We're all gathering at
the pool at 3 PM for a maju.
Oh?
That's when you always have
a maju, right, Sibylla Aurea?
If your pair for that isn't
set yet, please choose me.
Morinas, maju pairs are always
determined by the natural flow.
It's not set in advance.
I would be honored to pair up
with you, Sibylla Aurea.
I see.
Don't worry. That won't inflict
any real damage to the Arcus Prima.
Y-Yes, ma'am.
You are proud candidates
for the Simoun sibylla post.
Hold your heads higher.
Yes, ma'am.
That's more than usual,
don't you think?
Maybe we should go out too...
I want to.
We're off combat duty right now.
They're showering more
greetings than usual today.
Such long-distance tactics
are just harassment...
...but the damage isn't zero.
I've been thinking
I'd like to take care of this.
Is Chor Tempest finished?
We can make up
for the losses somehow.
Neviril?
Yes. No matter what the remedy...
...unless she returns,
Chor Tempest will remain scattered.
You're early, Aer.
You too, Alty.
It's still a half hour till 3 PM!
So you're here, Big Sister.
I stopped by your room to pick you up.
If you're sisters,
why don't you fly a Simoun together?
Being sisters has nothing to do with
the chemistry of auriga and sagitta.
You tried?
It's clear enough without trying.
I shouldn't have asked.
When this ship was a private
cruiser for observing Ri Majons...
...it must've been a sight.
But now it's been overhauled into
a battle mother ship for Simoun chors.
No more gentlemen and
ladies coming and going...
Even on this beautiful
afternoon bathed in light...
...there's no one gathered before the
gigantic central ballroom except us.
Just the three of us.
I don't want it to change like this.
It looks so fun! I can't stand it!
Can't I fly this now?
Simouns can't fly with
one pilot, unlike Similes.
It needs one more
person aboard, your pair.
That's right.
Helical motors activate when they
receive Tempus Spatium's grace.
But if either the auriga or sagitta
is missing, it can't receive this grace.
Both members of
the pair must be aboard.
Hey, can I ask you something?
Sure, what is it?
When did you go
to the Spring, Waporif?
Two years and
four months ago, I think?
When I met Floe this morning, there
was a strange tension with you two.
Oh, actually, Floe and I
used to be in love.
I-In love?
Inappropriate with a Simoun sibylla,
the symbol of utmost respect, right?
No, that's not what I meant.
But it is a little awkward now.
You're going to the pool, aren't you?
I told you. I'm not
going to join in the maju.
I won't choose anyone.
But...
What?
What happened to Amuria was tragic.
She was a dear comrade to us too.
After that, I think I understand why
some of us headed for the Spring.
Neviril, more... More powerful, Neviril.
Neviril, don't look! You can't
kill them if you see their eyes!
Listen, Morinas.
Any pairing is allowed in the pool.
You don't have to think
about your battle partner.
So it's first come, first served.
Pair up with whomever you like...
Maybe Neviril won't
come if we're here.
A maju without Neviril
won't be much practice.
I'm sure...
I'm sure she'll come.
I guess that's too bad, Paraietta.
Maybe Neviril won't come after all?
Shall I call her?
You shouldn't say
things you're not capable of.
Even though she went to
the Spring, Neviril came back.
That means she decided to remain
a Simoun sibylla of her own will, right?
Yes, that's right.
Then she will come.
What are you doing?
Floe, concentrate harder!
Damn.
With these scattered emotions,
we can't achieve a maju.
Even us, Chor Tempest...
I don't know...
I think you're jumping
to conclusions a little too fast.
Neviril...
Are you there?
Are you?
Hurry!
No matter how hard
you try to protect them...
...this is the reality.
I'll... I'll get you out right now!
Fire unit, hurry!
It is played by my wounds...
the song of prayer.
Let it ring out over
the grieving universe.
Can we change tomorrow?
Don't be afraid.
I want to let you know
how my heart's overflowing.
"I want to get closer to you."
"I want to feel your pulse."
I was too defiant,
and I took the long way around.
The blue moon is swaying silently.
My true heart's desire is you.
I can't reach you.
My tears of pain trickle down.
Soar away into the sky, song of prayer.
Carrying my love that came too late.
What can I do to change tomorrow?
Just hold on to "now" the way it is...
To Be Continued
Rimone! Get a move on! Let's go!
Next time on Simoun...
The Nearby War
The Nearby War.