The countless flowers,
enveloped in light...
...gaze at tomorrow
with unwavering eyes.
Everyone wishes for me to be pure...
...but what can I bring
with me to the frayed skies?
What I've made my own
by breaking off flowers in bloom...
All such sinful things...
Why did I stop making
promises with the future?
Because even if I try
to run far from all the pain...
...a cold wind rustles
my hair... Don't you see?
Where can I ever find the answer?
I am Anubituf,
the captain of the Arcus Prima...
...one of the largest airships
in Simulacrum Kyuukoku's fleet.
Three air squadrons, Simoun chors,
are stationed on the Arcus Prima.
Chor Tempest,
Chor Caput, and Chor Rubor.
But Chor Tempest, once prided for
defense and flawless Ri Majons...
...has lost its high standing and is now
being relegated to reserve status.
And now, as we escort
the Plumbum highland delegation...
...to international waters, where
a peace conference is scheduled...
...tensions in Chor Tempest over its
new members have sparked a brawl.
Chor Tempest has been ordered to
disband as soon as we return to port.
For those with reasons for wanting
to continue flying the Simouns...
...it is a bitter sentence.
Either way, when it's time
to journey to the Spring...
...one can no longer fly a Simoun.
And now the peace
conference is about to begin.
Prayer
We understand that your priestesses
are all fluent in Kyuukoku's language.
But for translating purposes,
wouldn't just one suffice?
We are not mere interpreters.
We also watch over
this important conference.
And several are needed
for certain ceremonies.
That's fine.
We should have some of Tempus
Spatium's priestesses attend as well.
I think that's a good idea.
They are not merely priestesses...
...but soldiers too, no?
How long will you snivel?
Thanks to you, we've been disbanded.
We should be crying.
But at least now we can
finally stop flying Simouns.
Mamina, what have
you been doing since then?
You lived with your mother after
your father passed away, correct?
Tell me about it.
I've got to keep flying Simouns.
I have to remain a sibylla...
That's just like Aer.
You want to go on
being a sibylla too, right?
No way.
Why? As long as you're a sibylla,
you don't have to go to the Spring.
That's the problem.
We all want to go to the Spring,
but since becoming sibyllae...
...we have to take part in this war now
and are unable to go to the Spring.
It's not like it's forbidden.
Just quit being a sibylla, right?
After being finally
chosen after such toil?
I do have my pride as a priestess.
Avoiding the front line isn't an option.
We all have our reasons...
...but I've never seen anyone who
wanted to avoid going to the Spring.
Oh? If you want to see, be my guest.
Here.
What are you doing?
It's obvious.
This ballroom is where Chor Tempest
socializes. It's always been that way.
People like the captain
never decided that.
But it's always been
that way, remember?
You guys never used to come here.
You're on standby and might
scramble at any time, right?
Take it easy.
Oh, jeez, I can't stand this.
Big Sister, why don't
you come to my room?
Hey, everybody! Big news!
Big news! Big news!
She always seems to be having fun.
It's been decided that just two
of the highland priestesses...
...will be allowed
to attend the peace conference.
Meaning that this priestess here,
Anglas, will not be allowed to attend.
She'll stay with Chor Tempest
until the conference is over.
Because we're fellow priestesses?
We can leave it at that.
I'll be patrolling the conference site.
I hope everything's clear.
Make sure you don't offend our guest.
The only thing is we don't
speak the same language...
I am not fluent, but I can speak a little.
I've heard many highland priestesses
are from the border near Kyuukoku.
Right, speaking of which, that area's
tribes travel between the countries.
They say our god was once
the same deity that you worship here.
That's why, um...
You feel an affinity with us.
The little one is Rimone.
The two on the right are Alty and Kaim.
They're sisters, you know.
That's Morinas.
Rimone, Alty, Kaim, Morinas.
And there...
Starting from the right, Paraietta,
Dominüra, and Roatreamon.
Paraietta, Dominüra, Roatreamon.
What a lovely name.
It's a very noble name.
From a venerable family that's borne
generations of Simoun sibyllae.
And the girl who just spoke up
is Mamina. Next to her is...
I'm Yun.
And I wish for
a speedy end to the war.
I'm glad to know there will soon
be peace between our countries.
Mamina and Yun.
That's what I wish for too.
My name's Floe.
Floe.
Let's see... Who else?
The girl in the very back is Aer.
The only one missing is Neviril.
And that's everyone.
Pleased to meet you.
Now that introductions are done...
Hey, hold on!
You're the only one
she didn't call by name.
Yeah, she said
everyone's name but mine.
Does she have
to say every single name?
How tedious.
I know it is, but...
Say, what do you think about this?
We're priestesses.
But we turned the Simouns
into weapons of war.
To do that...
In the eyes of normal priestesses
like you, it's peculiar, isn't it?
It is very cold in the highlands.
We're blessed by
a compassionate god, but even so...
Every year, there is a cold snap,
resulting in many deaths.
I am a priestess...
...so I pray that those who have
perished may find bliss in God's arms.
I know what you mean.
When we first started as sibyllae...
...I thought we would fly Simouns
in divine ceremonies like that.
You're right. We should be flying
the Simouns in order to pray...
What a carefree attitude.
You take becoming a sibylla
for granted, so you can say that.
What do you mean by that, Mamina?
If it hadn't been for this war,
I never could have become a sibylla.
There were only a handful
of young girls in my village.
So it wasn't hard to serve the great
temple as a priestess in training.
But...
U-Um...
When I become a sibylla,
will you fly with me as my pair?
You? A sibylla?
Sibyllae are selected by Tempus
Spatium. People of humble birth...
And then that day came.
Plumbum highland's death squad...
...crossed the border and
took up position in our village.
Their goal was of course to steal
the Simouns from the great temple.
There was no time to lose.
We had to launch the Simouns
and repulse them from the skies.
The sibyllae said, "We are
priestesses. We can't go into battle."
The dux turned to
the trainees for volunteers.
Such a thing...
Tempus Spatium will never allow it.
One such as you
could never fly a Simoun...
And so I became a sibylla.
But only because I was
accomplished in battle.
Otherwise, being of low birth
and having no connections...
...I would've been stripped
of my post right away.
If only I could pair up
with Neviril... With Sibylla Aurea...
Then no one could ever
treat me like an upstart again.
And I could prove there's
no better sibylla in the world.
But now...
It's over.
That's enough.
That's not something one
should tell another land's priestess.
I don't mind.
But anyway, I'm sure keeping
me company is very dull.
Please go about your day freely.
Oh? You can take a tour of the ship
as long as it's not a restricted area.
I'd like that!
Then as my guide... Do you mind?
It's Aer, all right? Call me by name.
Is it all right to go into
another god's chapel?
As I mentioned earlier,
the recent theory is that our god...
...was once the same as your
own deity, Tempus Spatium.
Then does that mean your country
used to be a colony of ours?
Oh, no.
Before Tempus Spatium...
...there may have been
an even more ancient religion.
Aren't you going to...
I'm not a priestess.
How could that be?
Oh, forget her. She's just here since
she doesn't want to go to the Spring.
Praying to gods is trivial.
What do you mean? You haven't
picked a gender yet either, right?
Well, no, but...
If you're not sure, forcing an answer
would be even more ridiculous.
A Plumbum dictionary?
Go away.
What's the problem?
You and I are a pair.
No.
What's that?
I'll check on the conference.
Me too.
Hey, what do you think...
Those fireworks were a signal.
First, where's the priestess?
Aer-sama, Sibylla Aurea is...
She's got my sister!
Why would she...
Neviril, what's this?
It's as it seems.
This is how they do things.
The conference was
a diversion for their infiltration.
To take a Simoun?
You can't fly that Simoun, you know!
She's a priestess, right? If there
were two, it might be possible to fly it.
If she does, what are those people
in the conference planning to do?
Waporif, block the maintenance
hangar off from the conference room.
Don't let two highland
priestesses rendezvous!
Didn't you hear her? Move it!
We're blocking all access!
Do you really think
you're going to pull this off?
Give it up.
Big Sister!
Alty! Watch out!
Grab her!
Don't let her touch that Simoun!
Don't tell me she's...
What?
If you're unsure of yourself,
you'll never find an answer.
Run, Floe.
Neviril!
Right. Bombs!
Run, everybody!
She's got bombs!
Aer!
What are you...
But why?
Nearly all the Simouns
here were destroyed.
We have to see
if the ones spared work...
Which can fly?
Only the Simouns on the left side.
Only Chor Tempest's
Simouns, you mean.
Are you all right, Aer?
That girl called out "Aer"...
At the very end...
What?
But why? Why my name...
Because it's not
a person's name to her.
The word "aer" in her own language...
...means "the highest love of all."
"Aer" means "the love of god"
in the Plumbum language.
Why?
Just what is it about this "love of god"?
How can it make
someone do a thing like that?
Sibylla Aurea,
please fly with me as your pair.
I just heard that Chor Tempest's
Simouns are the only ones intact.
You're completely sure
about this, aren't you?
We don't have time not to be.
Aer, what will you do?
I don't know. I just don't know.
I'm not sure anymore...
Aer, you came here
to fly a Simoun, didn't you?
I just don't want to go to the Spring.
But is that a good thing?
I don't even have
love of god or anything...
You needn't come up with an answer.
I'm unsure too.
About being a priestess.
About going into battle.
Whether those are
the right things to do.
You and I are completely
different in every respect.
But we're alike in just one way.
Stand up, Aer.
I am your pair.
One second is enough. Right the ship.
We're launching the Simouns.
Rubor and Caput were destroyed?
Chor Tempest will be going out.
It is played by my wounds...
the song of prayer.
Let it ring out over
the grieving universe.
Can we change tomorrow?
Don't be afraid.
I want to let you know
how my heart's overflowing.
"I want to get closer to you."
"I want to feel your pulse."
I was too defiant,
and I took the long way around.
The blue moon is swaying silently.
My true heart's desire is you.
I can't reach you.
My tears of pain trickle down.
Soar away into the sky, song of prayer.
Carrying my love that came too late.
What can I do to change tomorrow?
Just hold on to "now" the way it is...
To Be Continued
We will soon be performing...
...our last Ri Majon as members of
Chor Tempest at the great temple.
Next time on Simoun...
The Hearing
The Hearing.