Let's Explicitly Expose the "Simoun"
Cast's True Natures on This Program
The Guests for the Milestone
First Episode are These Two
Monthly!
ADR!
Bulletin!
Nice to meet you. My name
is Michi Niino, and I play Aer.
Hello! I'm Rieko Takahashi,
and I play Neviril.
All right, so anyway...
The ADR Bulletin has started.
Let's do a laid-back show, shall we?
The two of us...
...are going to be ourselves
during this time with you.
And I'm your MC.
Just call me Simoun.
No-Holds-Barred!?
Brutal, Live Talk Show.
Right.
This is a live session.
Now what are these?
Well, we're going to turn over
these cards one by one, you see.
Something written on the back then.
So whatever turns up,
let's give a laid-back answer.
So here's the first card...
May I pick the first one?
Okay, I'll start with this one.
Ta-da.
Ah, this is what I picked. Were you
uncomfortable doing explicit scenes?
Starting with me?
You turned it over.
I'll start this, huh? Well, I...
Um, I didn't really
have any explicit scenes.
I did have some
kissing scenes... We all did...
All the sibyllae kissed, right?
But in my case,
my scenes were all normal.
Oh, it's not that
my private life is totally normal...
No, that's not what I meant. Sorry.
They weren't especially...
Aer, your face is red
So now it's my turn?
Right. I'll take this one.
Have you ever fallen
in love with a woman?
Well, well!
Well, I went to
an all-girls' school, you see.
Oh, really?
And there was an older
student who was a little boyish...
There was a time when
my heart fluttered over that older girl.
This happened a long time ago...
All right, shall we move on?
Let's move on!
Let's see... Okay, this one.
Here we go.
I felt I'd get this one!
If you had to think of
a name for your pair?
Okay.
We fly the same Simoun, you see...
...and if we were to name it...
Our pair's name?
What do you think?
You know the Ri M_a_jon
Neviril did today to return...
The Diamond Ri M_a_jon?
Diamond?
Is something funny about that?
It's a diamond! That's
an outrageous name for a pair!
It makes you think, "What kind
of pattern are they going to draw?"
Well, personally,
I'd like to go with "diamond"...
You're really sure?
Who cares if you're sure.
Just hurry up and make a decision!
Let's move on to the next corner!
Why Oh Why!?
Simoun.
All right then...
Is this a quiz?
Since it's called "Why Oh Why?"
We'll be asked some questions...
...and they'll test how much
we've done our homework.
Let's do our best.
Well...
What does pair mean?
T-Team?
To ride together?
To... ride... together...
Teammate?
That's not it. Team...
It's something...
Pa... Pa...
Partner!
Correct... Try to get
some laughs, will you?
Where'd that come from?
You just heard a voice, didn't you?
I heard the voice of God just now.
It's your partner when you fly
a Simoun... That's your pair.
Now why don't you
talk about the CDs?
We'd like to tell you about Simoun's
opening and ending themes.
This is the opening...
...sung by Chiaki Ishikawa,
"Utsukushikereba soredeii."
("All You Have to Be Is Beautiful")
It's said it was
written with Neviril in mind.
It's a very beautiful song,
and it's selling to wide acclaim.
Right, and this is the ending theme...
...performed by Savage Genius.
It's called "Inori no uta."
("The Song of Prayer")
It's the kind of song
that touches your heart...
So I hope you give it a listen!
It's just about time to say goodbye...
Make sure you close out the show!
Good job, everyone!
I guess we were
laid-back to the very end.
It's almost time for
us to say goodbye...
Aer-chan, what did
you think of today's show?
I learned a lot today.
Things I'd never known till now...
Or rather things I should've but didn't.
It cleared up a lot of mysteries,
so it was a good experience.
What did you think, Neviril-san?
Let's see... I think I'll make
sure I study up from now on.
All right.
I hope you continue to watch Simoun.
Don't miss the next show!!
Fade out...
The way they're going,
I wonder if there'll be another show...