The countless flowers,
enveloped in light...
...gaze at tomorrow
with unwavering eyes.
Everyone wishes for me to be pure...
...but what can I bring
with me to the frayed skies?
What I've made my own
by breaking off flowers in bloom...
All such sinful things...
Why did I stop making
promises with the future?
Because even if I try
to run far from all the pain...
...a cold wind rustles
my hair... Don't you see?
Where can I ever find the answer?
I'm unsure too.
About being a priestess.
About going into battle.
Whether those are
the right things to do.
You and I are completely
different in every respect.
But we're alike in just one way.
Stand up, Aer.
I am your pair.
Everyone, hurry up
to the left flight deck!
Hurry!
All right!
Mamina, let's go.
Our Simoun is waiting for us.
Isn't that why we're here?
The Hearing
I'll make them pay for
taking my big sister hostage.
If our feelings go to pieces
again, I couldn't bear it.
Are you scared?
Not one bit.
I'm scared.
Let's hurry.
Neviril and I are alike
in one way... What is it?
Never mind. What matters is
that I'm Neviril's pair from now on.
One second is enough. Right the ship.
We're launching the Simouns.
Rubor and Caput were destroyed?
Chor Tempest will be going out.
Did you hear that? Keep the ship
level while Chor Tempest takes off!
We'll launch a simultaneous
counterattack. There's no time to aim.
Blast away!
This is...
Yes, the fuselage Amuria and I shared.
It looks fixed.
Let's go.
You're Sibylla Aurea's
auriga. Do your best.
Right.
Jeez, our attacks
aren't connecting at all!
They can't hit
anything from that position.
We're plunging in, Yun!
Look left!
Neviril...
We'll protect the Arcus Prima.
Diamond Ri Majon.
The Diamond Ri Majon...
The Diamond Ri Majon can
neutralize the enemy bombardment.
Right, it is one of the most difficult
defensive Ri Majons to execute.
The helical motors on this ship
are barely functioning anymore.
The only way is for
them to convey us...
Leave it to them.
I'm sure Chor Tempest can manage...
We'll hold the Diamond Ri Majon and
move out of the enemy's firing range!
Okay, gotcha!
The hearing will be held this
afternoon, as soon as we arrive.
We don't have much time to prepare.
I'd like to take this time...
...to once more go over what
happened with you, Sibylla Neviril.
You will see your father,
Lord Harukonf, at the hearing.
You and I are completely
different in every respect.
But we're alike in just one way.
Stand up, Aer.
I am your pair.
I wonder if Neviril's coming back.
But even if Neviril does come back...
...what difference would that make?
Listen, you...
Just when we finally
got back to full strength.
Just when I thought
we could all fly together again.
No one's blaming
you anymore, Mamina...
That's not what I meant...
Looks like Dominüra
ran off somewhere too...
Rimone, don't you know where?
Don't ask me.
Even if Neviril does come back...
...it's not as if we can
carry on as Chor Tempest.
We'll just disband
with all members present.
Oh, here you were.
We've been looking for you.
Chor Tempest sibyllae, it is almost
time for the ceremony to begin.
I'd appreciate it
if you started getting ready.
Nothing you did brought
about the desired results?
It's too early. I still believe that
Chor Tempest has vast potential.
For example?
Neviril has returned.
And two of the chor's
new recruits, Rimone and Aer...
...possess latent talents
unlike any sibylla before.
The sibylla in your report,
your favorite, Rimone, eh?
True, Harukonf-sama's prodding
added two more sibyllae...
...Sibylla Mamina and
Sibylla Yun, to Chor Tempest.
Yes.
But no matter how
convincing you are...
...everything will be
decided soon in that room.
Now that it's come to this, it would
be wise to switch to our next plan.
But...
...it was you who allowed the highland
agents to board the Arcus Prima.
Dominüra, this discussion is over.
Forgive me, Neviril.
But I only have your
best interests in mind.
And your own too, Father.
It is true Chor Tempest's record
is nothing short of dazzling.
But the sibyllae have
destroyed it with their own hands.
For Tempus Spatium's priestesses to
feud and go at each other's throats...
...asserting themselves by baring
their basest instincts, is unthinkable.
But what of our responsibility for
not recognizing the conference...
...a sham, allowing Plumbum
to carry out its destructive plot.
Chor Tempest saved our precious
Arcus Prima from the enemy's ruse.
Had it not been for
their excellence that day...
...I wouldn't be
standing here right now.
We...
No one granted permission
to speak, Sibylla Neviril.
I do.
Onasia...
Sibylla Neviril, that day at the Spring...
...I did indeed hear
Elly's wail of anguish.
I'm afraid...
Please say what you
have to say to everyone here.
All right.
We are all priestesses serving
Tempus Spatium, and as sibyllae...
...we've listened to the Simouns and
drawn Ri Majons across the skies.
And we have also killed scores of
soldiers from neighboring countries...
...attempting to invade
Simulacrum Kyuukoku.
Go on.
What we carried out could
almost be called slaughter.
We met a massive fleet of aircraft
from Shoukoku, and in the battle...
It wasn't a battle.
How dare a sybilla speak like that...
We have already lost three
of our beloved comrades.
As for Chor Caput, eleven of
their sibyllae have fallen in battle.
When the highland priestesses
gave their lives in the plot...
...to destroy the Arcus Prima,
even more lives were lost.
There was no deceit in
their devotion to their god.
As priestesses ourselves...
...what are we supposed to believe,
and how should we act?
We are waging war now.
Enough...
That's enough, Neviril.
We are gathered here today...
...because we must sadly bid farewell
to a number of our beloved friends.
We traveled together and fought side
by side with these comrades of ours.
Even for a time
of war, their departure...
This was our original job, wasn't it?
To offer flawless
Ri Majons to Tempus Spatium...
We'll return to our
normal sibylla duties.
But I'm not sure how I feel.
So you really wanted to mourn
the dead? That's pretty gloomy.
Aer, that's not what I meant to say...
This is the last Ri Majon we'll ever do
as Chor Tempest. Keep that in mind.
I wonder if we're really
qualified to mourn the dead.
Qualified or not, it's duty.
I just want to get
this over with. That's all.
Sibylla Paraietta,
please begin the ceremony...
...to commemorate those who gave
their precious lives for their country.
Yes, sir.
We'll offer the Ri Majon of the Fields.
I am not looking to blame
anyone for this war we're waging.
No matter how tragic and painful it
is now, I believe it was meant to be.
Whether or not that is
Tempus Spatium's will...
...it makes no difference to me now.
I no longer even care whether
it's God's will anymore.
However, I do have
one question for you all.
Despite all this, can I still
call myself a Simoun sibylla?
Sibylla Neviril...
As long as you yourself wish it,
you may still consider yourself...
...a Simoun sibylla.
All right.
Wait! You made a comment
we simply can't overlook.
We can't allow you to get away with
saying you don't care about God's will.
Please wait.
I have something to say to all of you.
You're from Chor Rubor...
My name is Vura.
I summoned her.
Guragief, how dare
you take such a liberty?
What is it that you
have to say? Sibylla Vura...
...speak now.
Onasia...
I will.
Chor Tempest is the chor all Simoun
sibyllae worship and take pride in...
...the finest chor of all.
On behalf of all Simoun sibyllae...
...I beg you to consider
preserving Chor Tempest.
Do you mean
Chor Tempest as sibyllae?
Or Chor Tempest as
a squadron of warriors?
You say you want us to preserve
Chor Tempest, but which one?
Twelve sibyllae...
...who become each other's pairs
and draw Ri Majons across the sky.
There is only one Chor Tempest.
Three o'clock!
The enemy.
Para-sama, look.
I know!
What is it?
I've never seen anything like it.
Is that a new type of cannon?
But I'm sure we can...
Those are no cannons. They're
headed straight for the great temple.
Let's go, Rimone.
We'll disengage from the Ri Majon
and shoot those things down!
Everybody's always ganging up
on us and making us suffer like this.
I suppose we...
This must be our fate...
One way or another,
we're bound to do Ri Majons.
Mamina! Look!
How can there be so many?
Only the Iron Ri Majon
can destroy a fleet that size.
We can't. It takes all six Simouns
to perform the Iron Ri Majon.
The Iron Ri Majon...
Neviril!
What a lovely breeze.
Vura?
Welcome back, Neviril!
I've come home, everybody.
I have good news. They won't
disband Chor Tempest after all!
Goody!
Isn't that great, Mamina?
Yes, it's wonderful!
Hey, what's the matter?
I'm so happy. This means we can fly
our Simouns across the skies again.
I'm so glad, Para-sama.
We'll be flying together again, right?
What in the world
happened down there?
Something must've
happened, right? Neviril, Vura!
Now that Chor Tempest
won't be disbanded...
...we must repair
the Arcus Prima at once.
I wanted you to move on to
the next phase of your life.
I can't lose face in the high council.
Chor Tempest can't go on as it has.
Until the repairs on
the Arcus Prima are completed...
...we'll board the Messis and be
charged with border reconnaissance.
What? We're boarding that thing?
I'm a bit...
Don't be unreasonable. You should
just be thankful Chor Tempest...
She's right.
That old boat should do just fine.
I don't mind at all!
It is played by my wounds...
the song of prayer.
Let it ring out over
the grieving universe.
Can we change tomorrow?
Don't be afraid.
I want to let you know
how my heart's overflowing.
"I want to get closer to you."
"I want to feel your pulse."
I was too defiant,
and I took the long way around.
The blue moon is swaying silently.
My true heart's desire is you.
I can't reach you.
My tears of pain trickle down.
Soar away into the sky, song of prayer.
Carrying my love that came too late.
What can I do to change tomorrow?
Just hold on to "now" the way it is...
To Be Continued
Chor Tempest...
...boards the antiquated ship Messis
and is on its way to the border.
Next time on Simoun...
Birds in a Cage
Birds in a Cage.