Emcee: Simoun
I wonder whose
"true natures" we'll expose today?
Emcee: Simoun
Today's guests,
please call out the title of this show.
Monthly.
ADR.
Bulletin!
Monthly! ADR Bulletin Special
Hello, everybody. I'm Ami
Koshimizu, and I play Paraietta.
Paraietta: Ami Koshimizu
Hello, everybody. I'm Ami
Koshimizu, and I play Paraietta.
Kaim: Michiko Hosokoshi
Hi, I'm Michiko
Hosokoshi, and I play Kaim.
Hey, that was kind of weird.
Why was it from the start?
Well, anyway,
this is part 2 of the series...
We'll be taking over this time around.
I heard part 1 with Aer and
Neviril was pretty relaxed.
The theme was "laid-back."
Then we'II...
I think we should do an efficient show.
Okay?
I don't think we're
up to it, but they know.
Efficient.
We'll give it a shot.
So anyway, hope you enjoy the show!
Okay, we're gonna
start with this corner...
No-Holds-Barred!?
Brutal, Live Talk Show.
Have you ever fallen
in love with another woman?
Well, I don't know if you'd
call the feeling falling in love.
When I see
a really gorgeous woman...
...I think, "Amazing..." or "How cool."
I think, "I wish I could be like that."
Or I find it somehow
healing to be near her.
I've felt that,
but whether that's "love"...
True, it's also how far you
go before calling it love, right?
Don't you think?
It's hard!
"I really like you. Just being
with you makes me feel great."
But would I want to kiss her?
That's another matter!
But if you could categorize love as
everything except for that kind... kind...
Oops...
Speak clearly now.
I'm a voice actress by profession!
Um... right.
Then if you leave out
certain stuff like kissing...
If you can call that love, you can't
rule out falling in love with women.
If you're a voice actress,
then speak like a professional!
This one!
Whoa, you faked me out.
Extreme! Cool.
Were you uncomfortable
doing extreme scenes?
The most extreme one was where
we went, "Vroom... pow, pow, pow!"
That's the most extreme!
Which episode was that?
Six?
Was it six or so?
We... It was a Paraietta-
and Kaim-centric episode...
...and the two of us were totally
pretending to fly in a Simoun.
We were playing, our two characters.
And our lines were like,
"Vroom, pow-pow-pow, blam, vroom!
Like grammar school kids going,
"Vroom! This is my plane!"
The two of us were
playing this kids' game...
And though she's not the type to do it,
Paraietta goes "pow-pow-pow!"
"There's an enemy there!"
"Okay, pow-pow-pow!"
So we played that scene,
and I agree it was pretty extreme.
Like, "We're gonna get trashed!"
But really, um...
To tell the truth,
that was the most embarrassing.
Sorry to interrupt as it's getting good,
but we're going to the next corner.
Why Oh Why!?
Simoun.
Yay!
Well, time for a quiz, huh?
Seems so.
Okay, let's start.
Simoun, please.
Let's quiz.
What's a "chor"?
When you go "ding, ding."
Yes, when you call.
We're a little off on that one.
It's like when you
address your butler...
"Sebastian!"
It's so trendy.
When you shoot a soccer ball...
Goal!
Hey!
Just give us
an answer already, will you?
You'd never go off track, Ami.
You weren't, Ami.
Really? Yeah, you were.
Quit it. We're supposed to be
united today. Today, it's two for one.
Well, a "chor" is...
To be specific, it refers to us...
The sibyllae as
a team is called a "chor."
Correct
You didn't know?
What is a "chor"?
A unit/team
You didn't know?
What is a "chor"?
A unit/team
Well, I knew there was a Chor Rubor...
What is a "chor"?
A unit/team
...but couldn't explain it.
What is a "chor"?
A unit/team
See? It's a unit or a team.
Like "Team Whatever."
"Team So-and-so."
I get it.
What was our team's name again?
Chor Tempest.
Oh, yeah! Close call.
How can you remember Chor Rubor's
name and not Chor Tempest's?
Time to tell everyone about
our CD. Advertise efficiently!
This here is Toshihiko Sahashi's
"The Dazzling Tango of Passion"!
As well as "The Majestic Symphony".
The music that's played in Simoun.
Simoun Original Soundtrack 1
The Simoun original soundtrack part 1.
This CD will be released on June 21.
We hope you enjoy it!
Please, please buy it!
Things were pretty
laid-back this time around too...
Okay, good work today.
How'd it go?
I have to say we were really efficient.
Such a brisk pace.
But I do think we did
a fun show... How about you?
I had a good time! I was like,
"Is it okay to enjoy myself this much?"
Was that okay?
It wasn't like a show.
It was more like the two of us having
a private conversation or something.
Still, I hope you all enjoyed it.
Since it's a "live talk show" after all...
About this particular DVD,
which is about to be released...
Since the feature itself is still
being broadcast to rave reviews...
...please keep watching as you wait
for the DVDs a-comin'... coming.
A-comin'? A-comin'?
Can Paraietta talk like that?
"They shall come out."
They shall come out,
and I believe they will be released.
That's it. Let's go with that.
So please, please support Simoun.
Please!
Anyway...
Simoun Bulletin...
No, let's end this right.
Monthly ADR Bulletin!
That's it!
Ready...
Monthly ADR Bulletin!
Don't miss the next show!!
Sloppy...
So lame...
Don't miss the next show!!