Junji and Asako's
Know-Your-Simoun Lecture
Jun-Jun and Asa-Asa's...
Junji and Asako's
Know-Your-Simoun Lecture
...Radio Wave Illusion!
We began with a title not discussed in
the meeting. It's the Simoun lecture.
Part one, right?
This is the director...
The director, Nishimura...
Junji-sensei.
And I'm Asako Nishida,
the character designer.
I also serve as animation supervisor.
And also light comic relief...
...but right now, I'm in
charge of Wauf love. And so...
The conductor of love who conveys
Wauf's allure to all our viewers.
This has nothing to do
with what's on screen!
Well, if you see
the Messis, you think of Wauf...
I came up with Wauf's name.
Oh? What does it mean?
Well, basically, all male names
are supposed to end with an F...
That was one of
the rules, as you know...
So "Wau"?
No, to be honest...
Since Wauf's a minor character,
I thought a short name would do.
You mean that was your reason?
Are you kidding?
I looked it up in a Latin dictionary,
wondering if it had some meaning...
Actually, in the case of the Messis...
...it means grain or something similar.
As for "Wauf," I just decided
on it by the way it sounded.
Like the sound you make
when you're kissing... Wauf!
Like, "What's with that?" Anyway, we'll
go back to the topic of Wauf later...
At this point...
...was this where
Neviril's love affair begins?
Yes. Needless to say,
around episodes seven and eight...
...Neviril actually begins to have
feelings to some degree forAer.
That was my intention for
this part. The thing is, though...
Seven and eight?
When she said pair...
"You are my pair." That was when...
Actually, she said, "I am your pair!"
Right.
That's right.
"I am your pair."
I tried to convey how she didn't
realize her feelings at the time.
And after that, it was a matter
of figuring out how to make Neviril...
...realize that she
was in love with Aer.
That was the story arc
I wanted to build.
Aerjust thought she
should follow Floe's words.
Just kissing her if there was
a Ri M_a_jon she'd like to invent.
Thinking like a child, right?
Since Aer has no complex
emotions like Neviril does...
But anyway, we shouldn't be
talking about stuff so far ahead.
Wait. She's now like, "What
good will it do to lose all hope?"
I assumed...
...she was implying that she'd already
seen her share of hopelessness.
Is that right?
Yes, um...
You once asked me, "Just what
did Aer go through before all this?"
Yeah.
Remember?
She's probably seen more than
anyone should in a lifetime.
Like in episode four...
...she's done things like
hacking a soldierto pieces.
She's been in an environment
more harsh than one should be in?
That's it.
Ah...
So she's only seen
the negative aspects of this world?
Negative aspects?
I don't know if you'd...
It's not about pluses or minuses...
It's simply that she knows that there
are harsh environments like that.
So it's not like she's known hardship
and wants to go to a better place...
It's more that she's
aware and can remain calm.
That's the nuance I was going for.
I really want to draw that Aer who's
so gung-ho about going into battle.
Very well.
That will come up next time.
Next time?
You mean in episode 27?
In that sense,
seeing Aer in a scene like this...
I mean Neviril...
And Paraietta's relationship...
You can see that it's
a little... How should I say it?
It seems more like they're playing
house. It's that nuance that I like.
You mean it still hasn't
evolved into a true romance?
Like two kids pretending.
You're pretty much
hitting it on the nose there.
And I felt that we should
keep it that way between them.
These scenes here...
Afterthe first approval...
...we were told, "Make Domin_u_ra
more drop-dead gorgeous!"
That was a direct request from
the director. You left me a little note.
And you complied?
Domin_u_ra's character... At what point
did you really start getting into...
...or should I say
focusing more on her?
Domin_u_ra? Well, what can I say...
In the end, it's really Domin_u_ra
who's most like an outsider.
Um... A-Aer, on the other hand...
...came from outside, began shaking
things up, and is a sort of heretic.
But Aer herself doesn't have
a problem with that at all.
But that's not
the case with Domin_u_ra.
She knows that she's an outsider...
...and you can see that it's causing
her distress. That's my take.
But she also knows she can only go
so far and is resigned to that fact.
That's the kind of person she is.
And that's the kind of mind-set
I had myself when I was a kid.
Oh, is that right?
I can relate to her kind of character.
You felt isolated, you mean?
Oh, I wouldn't say isolated.
So you had those drills
hanging from your head too?
Just like her!
The bamboo curls!
That's something
from my secret past.
I went through that for a while.
The background music in
this scene is pretty interesting.
Right, it really stands out like a sore
thumb on the CD! At least to me!
Because the other
songs are tango-esque, etc.
Then this mechanical-sounding
background music is suddenly heard.
I knew it would be
a challenge, but it fit like a glove.
Whoa... goosebumps!
So in your eyes,
Wauf was just a minor character?
Yes, that's right.
Oh, time out.
Sorry, Wauf.
We'll get back to you later!
This kiss here...
Yes?
Is shejust repeating
what Aer told her...
...or was she being mischievous?
No, she's truly acting on it in
all seriousness... The way a child will.
So she's just a really pure-minded
character. No motives at all.
In the beginning, Rimone was always
trying to shun Domin_u_ra, right?
But now she's attracted to her...
Did she sense her motherly instinct?
Or did she see her as a person trying
to achieve perfection in one thing...
...and that was what drew her?
Forgive me...
I really don't understand Rimone.
Hey, you're copping out!
Jun-Jun totally copped out!
R-Rimone's the one
I can relate to the least!
You've alienated every last Rimone
fan in Japan, all across the country.
You're finished.
Watching the show,
you may think that about her...
...but for me, Rimone is something
I have to handle with kid gloves.
Something about her keeps
me from answering promptly.
If you're too invested,
you'd be committing a crime.
So you're using restraint?
I'm just saying I don't
understand her as a character!
But doesn't that make
you want to know her all the more?
In that sense, the whole issue
is a pretty scary one for me.
I'd be scared to try to figure her out...
She's a "No offense, but I don't
think I'll touch you" kind of character.
So all your excess passion
is channeled into Domin_u_ra.
Into the bamboo curls.
I think that's
what happened, more or less.
But these two... Of course
when we first started out...
...we never intended for
them to go into this direction.
It's more like they headed
down that path on their own.
Pretty much...
Here, she's talking about
the fact that she's an immigrant.
You told me this over drinks last night.
What it means to be an immigrant...
Whether it means you're from
another country or another planet?
You mean that discussion we had.
The geography we're talking about...
In a historical sense, as well as...
I guess I should
say a physical sense...
You can think of it as
encompassing all of outer space.
I do believe that, but in
the 26-episode Simoun worldview...
...there's no need for viewers
to expand their perception that much.
And if it were, we'd be opening a can
of worms without resolving a thing.
And we still haven't
resolved anything to this day...
You said it!
I think that would happen.
But my imagined world has space
and immigrants from other planets.
That's the kind of worldview
I'm hoping to create.
Matsuda-san, use space engine
background music right here.
I see...
Right here in this scene is
precisely where we see Domin_u_ra...
The birth of "Drill-nura"!
Drill-nura is born! That's what I was
thinking when we did this scene.
In the first draft of the script, you
see her coming barefoot towards us.
And right after that,
she's stuffing herself with food.
Oh, so making her only wearthat slip
in those scenes was your doing?
More or less. So we had the script,
character design, and costumes...
...and it seemed she
kept sliding towards drilldom.
I get a strong sense of that
in this episode's second half.
When you see her stroking
Rimone's cheek in this scene...
...the segment director said,
"Try to make it look like it feels good."
"You know, like it's a crime!"
I was like, "Gotcha!"
That's what happened.
I wasn't consulted.
Are you serious?
I was totally gung-ho about it...
And I made it look as criminal
as possible. At least in my eyes.
Pretty criminal right here.
Everything's spiraling out of control
without the director's knowledge.
Itjust keeps snowballing.
Oh, wait...
As far as what happens when
you do the Emerald Ri M_a_jon...
At this point in the story,
does Domin_u_ra herself know?
No.
She may know
that it's one possibility...
...but basically, all she's sure of is
that she won't know unless she tries.
They're surrounded by enemies,
and it's a matter of life or death...
Just what is her motivation
for doing the Emerald Ri M_a_jon?
Does she think
they can change the tide?
No, she has a more...
It's a very personal reason.
She knows that this battle
means nothing to them anymore.
They'll get killed if she doesn't do
something now, so it's now or never?
Well, um, we'll continue
this discussion later. I think.
What?
Are you serious?
W-We're ending on this doll?
Roatreamon's doll will close it out?
Um, as far as
the Emerald Ri M_a_jon is concerned...
...we still have an immense
amount of explaining to do.
How should I say it?
The fact that they did
the Emerald Ri M_a_jon here...
...was a huge catalyst that moved
this story towards its conclusion.
And we really do need to talk
about the structure of this arc.
No, I mean
Domin_u_ra's emotional state!
That's what you're talking about!
About Domin_u_ra's emotional state...
The moment she drew herself up
to her full height in that scene...
She'd made up her mind totally to live
the rest of her life with Rimone...
So in my eyes, I think...
What happened
here gave her greatjoy...
And so at this time, even if they didn't
think at all of their comrades...
...I thought it was perfectly all right.
Old Lady Bamboo Curls snatched
Rimone and skipped town!
Do something about that please!
Featuring: Junji Nishimura
Asako Nishida