The countless flowers,
enveloped in light...
...gaze at tomorrow
with unwavering eyes.
Everyone wishes for me to be pure...
...but what can I bring
with me to the frayed skies?
What I've made my own
by breaking off flowers in bloom...
All such sinful things...
Why did I stop making
promises with the future?
Because even if I try
to run far from all the pain...
...a cold wind rustles
my hair... Don't you see?
Where can I ever find the answer?
With the death of Sibylla Mamina...
...and the ancient Simouns
now in the hands of Shoukoku...
...you could say they've
leveled the playing field.
No, considering their
battle expertise...
...they now pose a
considerable threat.
Just as we thought.
It was reckless to send in
Chor Tempest after all...
But Chor Tempest did cause damage
to the aerial base, didn't it?
The enemy will need
time to regroup...
...so I hardly think they'll
be attacking anytime soon.
That sibylla's death
bought us some time.
Am I wrong about that?
Remember that Tempus Spatium is
watching over everything you do.
Lament
Dominüra...
...and Rimone...
I bet they're dead too!
Floe...
They all...
They all died!
And it's going to keep happening!
All of us here!
We're all going to die.
I just know it!
You're too much.
What do you mean by that?
War is just a name
for killing each other.
If you can't accept that, then you
need to go to the Spring right away.
But why... did it
have to be Mamina?
I can't even shed tears over this.
The day Amuria died...
I think that maybe my own
heart died along with her.
I've caused others pain...
Rejected their advances...
Yet despite it all, here I am,
unable to shed a tear...
Living on with a heart
that's already dead.
Yes.
If only I'd died instead of Mamina.
The Emerald...
Have you been here all this time?
Have you been crying?
If only...
...I'd been stronger.
Mamina wouldn't have died!
If only I'd...
No.
I'm the one to blame,
because I was her pair.
You had nothing to do with it.
Don't say that I had
nothing to do with it!
Aer...
Why are you crying?
What happened to the Aer who
wasn't afraid of anything?
Amuria!
I said I want to become stronger.
You understand, right, Neviril?
We can do it.
I've got to live.
I... I've got to live.
To live.
Behind me lies the finest sibylla
in all of Simulacrum Kyuukoku...
...Sibylla Aurea Neviril.
I'm getting her out
of here no matter what.
And not one of you will lay
so much as a finger on her!
You're right.
We've got to live on.
Do you want something to drink?
Patch things up? That sounds like
we were actually friends before.
Till the end, one of us
will always be above...
...and the other below.
That's not true.
Anyway, just what were
you thinking that day?
That I wanted to be friends...
Don't joke.
It's because I really want
to be friends with you all.
Mamina!
So stop saying things like,
"We're friends," will you?
It's just a matter of
how you feel about me.
Okay.
I'll stop then.
I have summoned
Onasia from the Spring.
And the military council?
As you have ordered,
they know nothing.
They only have eyes for warfare.
It is truly deplorable.
Hatred has tarnished the land.
And yet they still cling to
this meaningless dispute...
...which can only lead to mutual
annihilation in battle. Such foolishness!
There is no time to lose.
We must find our way out of this
cursed land as soon as possible.
We must follow the path
of Tempus Spatium...
...and open the door
to a new world!
A new world?
Yes, and to that end...
Anubituf...
There is much that I must
ask you to accomplish.
First of all...
The phantom chor.
Chor Dextra must be resurrected!
Granted, they're somewhat inferior
to the Simouns in performance.
But other than that, there
are no major differences.
Sibylla Morinas.
Is Sibylla Neviril's Simoun...
No.
Dismantling the ancient
Simoun's your priority.
All else will have
to wait, I suppose?
Oh, not that I'm
blaming you or anything!
I'm sure you can't rebel
against your superiors.
Actually...
It was what I
wanted to do as well.
Sibylla Morinas...
Would you please
go to the Spring?
I can't do that right now.
The Simouns are cursed!
I don't care about the Simouns.
Sibylla...
"As long as I can fly a
Simoun, nothing else matters!"
"Who cares about my comrades?"
At least, that's what I used to think.
But it seems I was
wrong about that.
You've changed, Sibylla.
So have you.
Now that Mamina's gone...
...do you think they're going
to reshuffle our pairs again?
Yes, I suppose so.
But for all of us to pair up...
we're short one person.
What do you think, Para-sama?
Hey, Para-sama.
Don't ask me.
Because...
...I don't have any
answers for you.
Para-sama...
Mamina is dead. How do
I tell her I'm sorry?
All I could think about
was my own problems...
...and I wasn't performing as
a member of Chor Tempest should.
It's hopeless.
Since when? And how?
How did I come to this?
How?
Para-sama.
Alty?
It doesn't have to be for real.
What?
Just be Para-sama,
no matter what.
It doesn't matter if they're wrong,
just make bold decisions!
I know you're
suffering too, Paraietta!
But...
By simply being our
heroic Para-sama...
...you give us all
a little bit of hope.
You say "us all," but
you mean Kaim, right?
Why would you go so far for Kaim?
I just wanted to see
my sister smile again.
The reason why I wanted
to become a man...
Why I wanted to become stronger...
It was all because I wanted
to make my sister happy.
But I finally realized something.
That something's keeping
my sister from smiling...
...and it's because
I'm in her way.
And if that's the case, there's
only one thing I can do for her.
For my sister's sake...
...I'll separate myself from her.
Paraietta-sama!
It's Sibylla Floe!
Floe?
What's going on?
Floe!
Floe! What are you
doing with that suitcase?
I'm going!
What do you mean you're going?
I'm going to the Spring!
It's no use trying to stop me!
I have no intention
of going to war...
...and I have no
intention of dying!
Hold on! We should all
talk about this first.
Roatreamon.
What's that?
What, for heaven's sake?
Is it a patrol Simile?
Where would it be
going at this hour?
Mamina...
Sibylla Mamina's
remains have been...
...sent to her land where
she was born and raised.
But why? Why did you...
It was the high priestess's wish.
She felt that in order to
comfort Sibylla Mamina's soul...
...it would be best to return
her to her beloved homeland.
But you could've done that after her
funeral service here on the Arcus Prima!
You're absolutely right.
As a Simoun sibylla
who died with honor...
...it was our job to see that
she was given a proper burial.
Died... with honor?
Come in.
Vura!
Sibylla Vura. In place
of Sibylla Mamina...
...she will be flying
a Simoun with you all.
But wait!
It is imperative that we rearrange
your pairs as soon as possible.
As well as achieve even
more powerful Ri Majons.
Military Councilor!
We have just lost one
of our precious comrades!
Ri Majons require our souls to be clear.
We must be able to pray
with the purest of minds!
We are not ready...
You speak as if you have
no cares in the world!
What?
Do you wish Sibylla Mamina
to have died in vain?
You're...
It's just too cruel.
How could they not let
us even say goodbye?
The military councilor's
no different.
All he can think about is war. He's not
really thinking about Mamina at all!
It's because Mamina...
Because she wasn't from
a Simoun sibylla family.
It's just like Mamina said.
I'm just a pampered
rich girl after all!
And Mamina's feelings.
I wanted to understand them.
But...
But it turns out I
didn't understand a thing!
Do you want to understand?
Yun.
Mamina's feelings...
They're right here.
It resides here...
...Sibylla Mamina's soul.
And this soul... it has
accepted that her life is over.
What?
In her eyes, it was
a meaningful death.
Who...
You mustn't touch Onasia-sama.
Bring it to me.
Yes, madam.
"Accepted that her life is over?"
I hate when people
say things like that!
Floe...
That's just to make
us feel better!
How can anyone really know
what the dead are feeling?
Roatreamon...
I was always envious of
those braids of yours.
But these are...
You plait your hair because
your parents told you to.
But those things don't
mean a thing to a child.
To me, they were a
rich girl's hairstyle.
That day...
...I really wanted to
be friends with Mamina.
That's why I...
Just what do you
think you're doing?
That's why I...
She really wanted to
be friends with us all.
Mamina!
Mamina is a Simoun sibylla!
That's right!
And we Simoun sibylla didn't
come here to go to war!
Right!
Roatreamon!
Let's go!
For all of you to go, you
need one more person, right?
Vura!
All of my Rubor comrades
have gone to the Spring.
But I decided to
stay here anyway...
...for the same reason Mamina did!
Because I wanted to
stay a Simoun sibylla!
Vura... thank you!
Sibylla!
Please!
What on earth?
Who's allowing them
to take such liberties?
How dare they,
in a time of emergency?
We'll begin with one
that Mamina excelled at...
...the Wave Crest Ri Majon!
Roger!
Next, let's do the
Dandelion Ri Majon!
Just as we thought...
Yes.
Right! We're all...
Aer...
Sibyllae!
Who inscribe our
prayers across the skies.
Sibyllae.
We pray for the future that
will go on forever and ever...
And for the past that we've
already woven, we offer our prayers!
Sibyllae...
Yes...
That's who we are!
It is played by my wounds...
the song of prayer.
Let it ring out over
the grieving universe.
Can we change tomorrow?
Don't be afraid.
I want to let you know
how my heart's overflowing.
I want to get closer to you.
I want to feel your pulse.
I was too defiant,
and I took the long way around.
The blue moon is swaying silently.
My true heart's desire is you.
I can't reach you.
My tears of pain trickle down.
Soar away into the
sky, song of prayer.
Carrying my love that came too late.
What can I do to change tomorrow?
Just hold on to "now" the way it is...
To Be Continued
Bestowed upon us by Tempus Spatium...
...the other "if."
Next time on Simoun...
The Door to a New World
The Door to a New World.