Hello, starting today I'll serve as your
emcee. I am a French-born Simoun.
Emcee: Simoun
Hey, who
are you, anyway?
Emcee: Simoun
Today's guests, please call
out the title of this show.
Huh? What?
Monthly!
ADR!
Bulletin!
Monthly! ADR Bulletin Special
All right, I'm Mamiko Noto,
and I play Rimone.
Rimone: Mamiko Noto
All right, I'm Mamiko Noto,
and I play Rimone.
Hello, I'm Yukana,
and I play Domin_u_ra.
Domin_u_ra: Yukana
Hello, I'm Yukana,
and I play Domin_u_ra.
Right?
Monthly...
That's the third time you said that!
You're right. What should I do?
Anyway, the two of us are
in charge of this installment...
It'll be very calm and gentle,
a laid-back show...
Calm? I like that.
Laid-back? Calm and gentle.
It is.
Right.
So we're just going to be ourselves...
We'll present
the show in this fashion.
We hope you enjoy it!
Now then, let's start with this corner.
Hey, why are you
presenting the show, huh?
No-holds-barred!?
A Brutal...
Live Talk Show!
No-Holds-Barred!?
A Brutal, Live Talk Show
Live Talk Show!
No-Holds-Barred!?
A Brutal, Live Talk Show
Right.
Now that's really laid-back...
Super laid-back...
Extremely laid-back.
But they must've known
when they chose us...
You think so? I guess you're right.
Of the whole Simoun cast,
we're the most laid-back!
You think so too, Yukana-san?
Please tell us what you've
fallen in love with recently.
What we've fallen
in love with recently?
Please tell us what you've
fallen in love with recently.
Vegetable juice!
Please tell us what you've
fallen in love with recently.
Vegetable juice is your love?
I'm obsessed.
The sweet kind?
It's kale-based.
It's easier for me to drink if it's
kale-based. It's not very sweet.
So it's not very bitter,
and it tastes very green.
Right.
I'm so in love with it.
As for me, I was
drinking some just now... Cassis.
Oh, you mean in that little can?
People who aren't
used to it say it tastes sour...
But it's that sweet
and tangy taste that I like...
You don't really see it in stores...
I mean I've never seen it in stores.
Oh, right. Not that
many places carry it.
Hold on, aren't you two
digressing from the subject?
Next one?
All right, then this one!
Um...
If there was a Ri M_a_jon you'd like
to invent, what would you name it?
A name for a Ri M_a_jon?
If there was a Ri M_a_jon you'd like
to invent, what would you name it?
How about after a flower?
Oh, how lovely...
Sounds kinda good.
Pretty.
If you flourish it like this... When you
do that, everyone starts smiling.
Was that weird?
l-It's okay. It's okay. I like it.
Are you sure?
I'm sure.
It would be nice.
That's keeping with the image
of Ri M_a_jons, don't you think?
Flowers and such...
Hey, you!
Move this show along, will you?
Why Oh Why? Simoun!
Why Oh Why!? Simoun
Okay, now it's time for a quiz.
Simoun-sama,
please read out the questions.
Just what is "Tempus Spatium"?
Don't talk at the same time...
The wings...
The... uh...
Their religion.
That's right.
The deity they worship or whatever.
But how should we explain it?
Um, probably...
Our nation,
Simulacrum Kyuukoku's...
Uh, what?
Domin_u_ra...
Um, h-how should I put it?
Our one and only... absolute god.
Well, of course
she'd get that one right.
Correct!
What is Tempus Spatium?
The god worshipped by
the people of Simulacrum Kyuukoku.
Tempus Spatium's court protects
the "Spring," its religious center...
...which is served across
the nation by the great temple.
Oh, then that means that the Spring...
...Onasia's spring, the one Elly
entered, is the center of their religion.
In the middle.
Now then, time for...
Product Presentation.
Hey, why'd the camera move?
All right, here's what you've been
waiting for, Simoun DVD volume one!
August 25th, everybody!
That's the date
it's going to be released.
And here are the bonus features for
the limited edition. These two here.
Postcards by the character designer,
Nishida-san, will be included.
And this time around,
the pairing is of Neviril and Aer.
Simoun DVD volume 1
will be released on August 25th.
We hope you'll support Simoun...
Some closing words please.
You could've just spoken
in Japanese from the start...
All right... That's about it...
Right, we've come to the end...
That went by really fast, didn't it?
How was it, Mamiko Noto-san?
Well, it felt as though time
was passing very, very slowly...
But it was great getting the chance
to talk to you like this one-on-one...
...because although
we do chat during breaks...
It was the first time we did
a presentation and discussed Simoun.
Right, it was a valuable opportunity!
Well, I... Normally, when
I'm talking with Mamiko-chan...
I don't really say a lot, unlike today...
I have a feeling some people
will be like, "You talk even less?"
Words aren't...
Yes, it's not
a matter of words, you see.
Usually, I'll just look at her face...
...and maybe say
something once in a while.
So for the two of us,
I think we talked a lot today.
I really hope you all enjoyed our chat.
And that ends our
Monthly ADR Bulletin.
Bye-bye...
Don't miss the next episode!
Good night... Good night...