It's time for the Sibylla Aurea Battle.
Monthly! ADR Bulletin Special
Pair Versus Pair Competition!!
It's time for the Sibylla Aurea Battle.
Monthly! ADR Bulletin Special
Pair Versus Pair Competition!!
We're going...
...to determine which pair is worthy
of being called "Golden Priestesses"...
Mamina
RIKA MORINAGA
...to determine which pair is worthy
of being called "Golden Priestesses"...
...and you'll be
competing in teams of two.
After the last round, the pair,
or team, with the most points...
...will receive an extremely
valuable prize! Do your best, everyone!
Well then, let's have each member
introduce herself and their pair.
I'm Michi Niino, and I play Aer.
I play Neviril...
I play Neviril.
My name is Rieko Takahashi.
The pair's name is Lilies of the Valley.
I'm Ami Koshimizu,
and I play Paraietta.
I play Kaim. Michiko Hosokoshi.
What was that?
Sorry.
Our pair's name is...
...the Mangoes!
I'm Mamiko Noto, and I play Rimone.
Mikako Takahashi. I play Roatreamon.
Our pair's name is...
...Monotone!
Yay!
What's with that?
Black and white.
I'm Michiru Aizawa, and I play Floe.
Um... Alty, right?
I'm Megumi Toyoguchi.
Our pair's name is...
...Team Green!
Copycats! Copycats!
Rip-off! Rip-off!
Copycats? Yes, but please
root for us anyway.
All right, so here they are...
the contestants of this battle.
Who's the best couple?
Simoun Compatibility Test!
So let's start with
a simple word association game.
I'll give you
a keyword related to Simoun...
...and you each write down
whatever comes to mind...
...using those writing boards.
Points will be awarded if both
team members give the same answer.
All right, I'll give you the first
keyword now, and it is...
In your opinion, what's the first
step in becoming an adult?
All right, everybody!
Get your answers ready!
Simoun related?
Good luck!
We've been abandoned.
From the start.
Becoming an adult?
It depends if we keep
the story in mind...
Becoming an adult...
How are we doing?
Ding-ding-ding!
All right, now that time's up...
Let's hear how Ms. Niino and
Ms. Takahashi, the Lilies, answered.
Please show us!
Okay.
Pretty long! When you start your first
job, start making your own money...
But it's true.
Like a part-time job.
Very realistic.
That's so realistic. A part-time job...
She even wrote it down!
Then let's see your answer, Rieko.
Love
Ta-da... Totally different.
It's like you're really holding back.
But still, they're both mature answers.
I see.
The answers are
totally different, so no-go.
Okay, next up... Ami-chan
and Michiko-san, the Mangoes!
Why don't you show us at
the same time? Ready, set, go.
Shopping alone (running first errand)
Going shopping by yourself
Running your first errand too, right?
Amazing!
Unbelievable!
We're definitely a good match, huh?
Next up, Mamiko-san and
Meguko-chan, the Monotones.
Ready, set, go.
Go!
20 years old Alcohol
That's "you can turn
20 after you drink alcohol"?
You can drink alcohol
after you turn 20!
Okay, um, nothing doing!
No good, no good.
Wrong answer, wrong answer.
Okay, next.
It's Michiru-chan and Megu-nee!
Go, green team. Ready, set, go.
First Kiss (Smack!) Alcohol
Go.
We should pair up.
You can't!
I knew we'd agree on something...
And it had to be this!
I guess it's
the generation gap or something...
Yup, to be brutally honest.
After all, you can't...
You can't yet, right?
No, I can't drink yet.
Another no-go.
Then on to the next question.
Question number two!
What makes a woman beautiful?
What is beauty?
If you please.
Write it down, write it down.
Are you ready?
Okay! We're done!
Wait, which page
did I write my answer on?
You wrote a lot.
Ready? All right, then...
Let's start with the Lilies again.
Show us your answers.
Ready, set, go.
Never bending her will to the very end!
Her purity
Wrong!
No good...
Okay, next. The Mangoes...
Let's go! Ready, set, go.
To always be smiling...
Kindness...
Well, they're close.
Smiles equal kindness, right?
I don't think they're equal at all.
What do you say?
Wrong.
No good, no good.
Next, the Monotones!
Ready, set, go.
Appearance.
Content.
Oh, mine means "outside"!
So as long as it looks good
on the outside, it's all right.
They're opposite.
So we should write
the opposite thing from now on.
That's another "no-good" answer.
All right, Team Green next.
Okay, ready, set, go.
Neviril-sama Being in love
What kind of answer is that? You
okay?
I tried every which way
to come up with a teen's answer.
An answer that evokes youth!
What's up with that answer?
Neviril-sama?
Because she's beautiful.
"All you have to be is beautiful."
("Utsukushikereba soredeii.")
Good one!
The theme song.
Well, it is a typical Floe answer.
Anyway, I guess for this corner...
...l'll give the Mangoes
10,000 points or so.
10,000?
So anyway...
That's it for
the Simoun Compatibility Test!
The Super-Difficult Simoun Cult Quiz!
Okay, so the rules are very simple.
It's a quiz all about
what happens in the show.
I'll read show-related questions...
...and I'd like you to write your
answers on the writing boards.
So let's get started. Question one.
Before their first flight in episode
one...
...how many times did
Neviril and Amuria kiss?
Yeah, that is super difficult.
Before their first flight in episode
one...
...how many times did
Neviril and Amuria kiss?
Before their flight?
Five, four, three, two, one...
Chu-chu, chu-chu-chu!
What kind of a sound effect was that?
I thought I'd make it more quizlike.
Each team, show your answers.
First up, the Lilies. Ready, set, go!
Three times.
Which teams answered "three times"?
Hey, can we get extra points for this?
That side interests me more.
It's Paraietta!
Listen, this isn't
a manga-drawing class, okay?
Okay, Monotones, let's see.
Ta-da.
1.5 times!
Where does the 0.5 come from?
Wrong, wrong, wrong!
If they stopped at the last second...
We averaged it out.
Well, the correct answer is twice!
But we're closest! We're closest!
We're closer than anyone else!
You all said it was three times!
Since you two were so cute getting
all worked up, I'll give you points.
Enough! They told me I could
be biased and partial, all right?
Okay, next question.
In episode two, when Neviril
was wearing civilian clothes...
...what color was her bag?
A Neviril question.
Answer, answer!
Think, think.
Bag?
Wait, her hair's pink, so...
Let's go with that.
Five, four, three, two, one...
Kon-kon-kon-kon!
Did you hear that?
It was just a whisper.
Okay, let's start
with Team Lilies' answer!
Ready, set, go.
Purple.
How elegant!
Look at that smile!
She's brimming with confidence!
If she gets this one wrong,
it's going to be funny!
Neviril's answer is purple.
Okay, the Mangoes next. Ready, set...
Go! An orangish-brownish color.
An orangish-brownish color?
Which is it?
Well, it's kind of subtle.
More of which?
Mottled!
You mean marbled?
In keeping with the Simoun theme...
Please accept our answer!
Then next...
H-How cute...
To the next answer. Ready, set...
Go-go-go!
A pink flower pattern.
Her hair's pink, you know.
Since her hair's pink,
she decides to color coordinate.
When she has to ponder
becoming a man or woman?
"Since I've got pink hair,
let's go with a flower pattern!"
"It won't do without it."
It's very typical.
On to the next team,
Team Green. Ready, set...
Go. Black.
Black?
I seem to remember it was
a darkish color, like purple.
Like brown.
No, not brown!
I'll tell you the correct answer.
The correct answer is brown!
Hey, hold on! Hey, MC!
"Orangish-brownish" isn't brown!
I think it could look orange too.
Okay!
Yay!
Kaim! Kaim!
So I'm counting that
as a correct answer.
That's it for
the Super-Difficult Cult Quiz!
Simoun Anything and
Everything Case Files.
Okay, in this corner,
I'll ask you to answer questions...
...about inside stories,
things that happened during ADR.
So it's a kiss-and-tell contest.
I'll pick a question out of this box...
Written by you before...
So I'll start drawing, and I'd like
to discuss these stories with you all.
I'm agreeing with myself.
The keyword... Okay, here it is.
Surprised to be in a place where
women gave their all playing men!
Right!
Meguko-chan.
Right from episode one, everyone
did a valiant job playing old men...
...throwing themselves into it,
and I was very surprised.
When they did the first session,
you could hear laughter in the booth...
The staff was cracking up.
Because usually, having a girl's voice
coming out of an old guy's mouth...
It never happened in anime till now.
It shouldn't ever happen.
Government Official
Voiced by Megumi Toyoguchi
Your daughter is
an outstanding pilot, as expected.
If we signed up for old guys,
we'd say, "This one!"
Like the somewhat chubby one.
I wish they'd credit us
for the old guys we played.
They're not old guys! Like "soldier"...
Let's move on.
Okay, um...
Basically, I have very few lines.
And no ad libs.
That's me.
You see, in the beginning...
The thing is... basically,
Rimone doesn't have a lot of dialogue.
I had quite a few ad libbed lines.
But one by one, they'd say,
"Not needed, not needed, not needed."
So she hardly had dialogue.
Only a line or two when she did.
So I thought, "I wish I could
talk as much as everyone else."
That was my secret dilemma.
Not that it was accidental...
They pretty much delete everything.
So in the nondialogue
parts of the script...
Like when they write "turns around"...
They'd normally write "ad lib"...
But as far as this show, they're like,
"We don't need this. Cross that out."
But when you think you don't
have any lines, they add something!
Like to turn around violently.
Like, "Hah!"
It's hard to know
where to draw the line.
And sometimes they throw
land mines like that...
Set traps for you in your path.
Okay, that's it!
Sibylla Aurea Battle
Pair Versus Pair Competition!
Here are the results!
All right, which team will
claim the "Golden Priestess" title?
I've taken the liberty of deciding,
and it's a biased and partial decision.
All right, well, what did
you think of the games?
Did you have fun? Was it hard?
I was really motivated!
I drew some pictures too.
It was pretty hard.
But I have a feeling we're gonna win.
Did you score?
The green in your clothes
is even more dazzling now.
You didn't get any points.
Anyway, let me
announce the winning team!
The winners are the Mangoes!
Winners
The Mangoes
Yay!
Yes, you put up a good fight...
As expected.
...and you performed well.
Now then, the Mangoes will be
presented with this Simoun candy!
Please accept it.
Kaim...
Para-sama...
Please shower your
kisses on this candy.
Calm down, Kaim!
Right, congratulations!
Okay, so the Mangoes
ended up winning today...
And I'm glad we all got
to have a good time today!
Please keep watching Simoun!
Please keep watching!
So the Sibylla Aurea Battle...
The Simoun... No...
The Sibylla Aurea Battle
Pair Versus Pair Competition...
That's all, folks! Everyone, bye-bye!
Bye-bye!