The countless flowers,
enveloped in light...
...gaze at tomorrow
with unwavering eyes.
Everyone wishes for me to be pure...
...but what can I bring
with me to the frayed skies?
What I've made my own
by breaking off flowers in bloom...
All such sinful things...
Why did I stop making
promises with the future?
Because even if I try
to run far from all the pain...
...a cold wind rustles
my hair... Don't you see?
Where can I ever find the answer?
You said it once yourself.
That I should dismantle a Simoun.
What's there is nothing but a helix.
The only thing we're
capable of understanding is...
You can see something!
What... What can you see?
One, and Then Another
What's that for?
Oh, I'm going to use
these to build a cradle.
A cradle?
Where I grew up, we used to set
out cradles like this every spring.
For those who passed too soon
to at least know a peaceful sleep.
That one's too thick.
How's Dominüra?
I don't know what made
Dominüra break down, but...
...Rimone,
you should stay by her side.
Why?
Of us all, you're the one
closest to Dominüra.
Aer!
Neviril... So nothing happened?
That's right. Nothing happened.
The enemy's aerial base has
vanished. Though I don't know why.
And nothing else happened?
No.
What?
Come on.
I want you to tell me.
What did Dominüra see?
I never should have touched
something so sacred after all.
I never should have touched it.
As you wish,
I'll never let you touch me again.
So warm...
You should get some rest today.
But with Dominüra in that state...
No...
What's going on?
We've spotted
the enemy at 11 o'clock.
It seems they're not attacking, but...
How's Dominüra?
She still seems quite indisposed...
Excuse me!
Let's go, Paraietta.
Let's go, Neviril.
Wait. Neviril is exhausted. She's in
no condition to go back up there.
But...
Dominüra is currently unable to pray,
so for now you'll obey my orders.
Orders, she said?
It sounds like the army.
Fine.
It's a scouting mission.
There's no need for Neviril to go.
Kaim?
Right.
To think Aer would
just back down like that.
It was surprising.
Before, she'd take her up even
if she had to drag her by the arm.
I don't want to see Aer acting like that.
The best thing about Aer is
she's almost aggressively positive.
To see her being tactful...
It's not like her at all.
Are you jealous?
N-No! That's not how I feel about Aer!
Hey, Rimone... Where's Aer?
I just saw her leaving the ship...
Leaving, huh?
I wonder why she did?
Who knows?
It's not what you think. I was just
thinking of showering or something.
Nobody's asking, you know.
Really now.
Sorry.
What are you apologizing for?
You can't even think of a reason to,
but you're just doing it anyway?
I do have a reason.
The reason you're in so much
pain, Neviril... I know it's my fault.
I don't know why that is, but it's my
fault... That much I know at least, so...
Don't flatter yourself!
Floe...
That was so uncool.
Please forgive me, Sibylla Aurea,
for speaking to you so rudely.
They're so alike.
Amuria... was just like that girl.
She was never really looking at me.
That's right...
I finally realized it because of Aer.
In their eyes, I'm...
...no more than a tool to help
them reach greater heights.
Neviril...
I think I might have made a mistake.
With you...
Don't say it.
I'm not the person you think I am.
If I'm not mistaken about
what you're about to say...
I'm sure...
that it would make me waver.
You're exhausted right now.
You're not yourself. So please...
I'm sorry.
What have I done?
I'm sorry, Paraietta...
I'm sorry!
Neviril...
Again...
I'll go too.
No. You should...
But...
Neviril...
I'll go for heaven's sake!
The air's not good here anyway.
The air?
All right, Alty?
I guess, if that's what Floe wants.
And the other will be flown
by Mamina and Roatreamon.
Roger.
I don't know about this...
Aer?
Yun and Kaim haven't
even come back yet...
And if there's no attack,
for us to mobilize...
Are you implying I've
made the wrong decision?
I never said that.
I can't always be by your side.
Even so, I can at least protect you.
Neviril...
It's so quiet...
You're not going to hang
around the Simouns today?
Well, no.
Wanna play hide-and-seek?
Treated like a child...
Well, Aer?
Sure! Sounds good.
All right, Morinas, count to 100.
No cheating, got that?
I know.
Here goes.
One, two, three, four...
Rimone! Go hide!
...five, six, seven, eight,
nine, ten, eleven, twelve...
This way!
...as blue as a tear.
As white as a lily...
In the pitch-black darkness...
...the light of a red flame...
That song...
It's from Aer's music box...
The doorway to a new frontier.
For those who seek a land
of peace... The immigrants' song.
Tempus Spatium embraced us, those
whom had no place to call home.
Chor Dextra was created
to perform the Emerald Ri Majon...
Its soldiers were recruited for their
willingness to lay down their lives.
But none of that mattered to me.
In return for my death,
Kyuukoku actually needed me.
And I wanted to feel needed.
That was what I'd always... always...
That's why...
You're still needed. Because I...
I want to do the Emerald Ri Majon.
I want to do it with you, Dominüra.
But why?
Because you're my pair.
Sibylla Paraietta, the rain
is coming down harder.
This can't be good for
your health. Please go inside.
What's the matter?
Do you need to see Dominüra?
No.
Why am I so indecisive? I've got
to do something, or I'll lose Neviril...
Another attack.
It doesn't make sense, you know.
Shouldn't we wait for Dominüra
to get back to normal?
Can't you do anything without
Dominüra instructing you?
This is no time for petty nitpicking.
Petty, you say?
Seriously, at this rate...
Aer!
Pair up with me.
You and I will patrol. From now on...
No.
I'm going.
Neviril!
Morinas, come with me.
Me?
Neviril, you can't go. You're still...
Please.
Let me go, Paraietta.
I'm so...
...powerless.
What about our game
of hide-and-seek?
She's going to die.
Dominüra...
People who are about to die
have that look in their eyes.
Rimone...
Dominüra.
Dominüra, I want you
to tell me what you think.
What's your read on this situation?
Dominüra!
Don't ask me.
Could the judgment of
someone who's been asleep...
...be less questionable
than your own?
Dominüra.
Another helping please.
The Emerald Ri Majon...
By dismantling a Simoun...
...I think that I've seen what
lies beyond its completion.
You only think you did, right?
You can't be sure
unless you really do it.
There's no other way, is there?
The only thing you've ever
been asked to do was to fly high...
To inscribe Ri Majons across
the vast sky. That's precisely why...
To be denied this would be the same
as having your own existence denied.
You and I are very much alike.
I chose you.
And you chose me.
If it's that link between us that
makes a Ri Majon what it is...
I'm going to do it for you.
The Emerald Ri Majon.
It is played by my wounds...
the song of prayer.
Let it ring out over
the grieving universe.
Can we change tomorrow?
Don't be afraid.
I want to let you know
how my heart's overflowing.
"I want to get closer to you."
"I want to feel your pulse."
I was too defiant,
and I took the long way around.
The blue moon is swaying silently.
My true heart's desire is you.
I can't reach you.
My tears of pain trickle down.
Soar away into the sky, song of prayer.
Carrying my love that came too late.
What can I do to change tomorrow?
Just hold on to "now" the way it is...
To Be Continued
The Messis has finally...
...become the target of
Shoukoku's mid-sized air fleet.
Next time on Simoun...
The Emerald Ri Majon
The Emerald Ri Majon.