The countless flowers,
enveloped in light...
...gaze at tomorrow
with unwavering eyes.
Everyone wishes for me to be pure...
...but what can I bring
with me to the frayed skies?
What I've made my own
by breaking off flowers in bloom...
All such sinful things...
Why did I stop making
promises with the future?
Because even if I try
to run far from all the pain...
...a cold wind rustles
my hair... Don't you see?
Where can I ever find the answer?
It would be too
dangerous to sit back...
...and do nothing about
that mobile air base.
We are hereby sending the Chor
Tempest on a reconnaissance mission.
The Messis shall serve
as the relay point...
And if we discover the base?
That will be left to
your discretion, but...
As for me...
I do believe you have the capacity
to blow it up at this point.
Why do you think they
took you off the mission?
I have a pretty good idea.
You do, huh?
What about you?
There's something that I
can't quite put my finger on.
And what would that be?
I can't tell you.
Because I promised not to.
I've got to go now.
As do I.
Sibylla
As if Sibylla Aer would
ever do as she's told.
Are you really
going to let this go?
Honestly, this makes me wonder
what the sibyllae are thinking.
You're absolutely right.
What I would give for that
kind of single-minded passion...
What is the meaning
of that Simoun?
Captain!
Who's that?
I believe it's Sibylla
Aer and Sibylla Yun.
I see.
Sibylla Aer and Sibylla Yun.
Vura!
After Chor Rubor was
disbanded, these two sibyllae...
...were assigned to the
Messis as your replacements...
...and have been on
reconnaissance duty ever since.
Good job.
This is all that we have
to offer at this point.
We heard about Dominüra and Rimone.
But where are Aer and Yun?
Those two will be
sitting out this mission.
There'll be plenty of
time to discuss that later.
Sibyllae, won't you
please come inside.
We should go over the
details of our mission, and...
First of all, I'd like
you to get some rest.
It's a little early,
but I'm going on ahead.
I'll meet you in the
dining room in half an hour.
Right. I'll be along soon.
Oh, it's you, Roatre!
What's going on?
Well, you were
taking so long, Mamina!
Was I?
Let's go!
Oh, Mamina.
What? What's wrong?
Your braids are
starting to come undone!
What?
I'll fix them for you.
We still have time anyway!
Those Simouns we
saw at the Ruins...
...do you think they've made it
back to the highlands' base station?
Probably.
But there's nothing to worry about.
You're paired up with Morinas,
and she's an excellent auriga.
Yes, she is.
And even if something
should go wrong somehow...
...I'll be there to protect you!
Right.
Even so...
This is just a reconnaissance
mission after all.
It would be better if we could avoid
going into battle at all, wouldn't it?
Yes, it would.
That would be the
best of all, right?
Right!
Thanks to the data these two
have gathered on patrol...
...we've narrowed down the Shoukoku
air base's approximate location...
...to this region right here.
In those defenseless Similes?
Sibylla Aurea, we two will
hold the rearguard position...
...and relay all
communications from the Messis.
The rest...
I know.
The rest is up to us.
There's no getting around the fact
that the gap between the Similes...
...and the Simouns in terms
of mobility is far too great.
Putting together a mixed unit like
this... It's just not feasible.
Just leave it to us!
There you go making rash
promises again, Floe.
What do you mean "again"?
Would you knock it off?
Both of you!
But Alty's the one who...
Let's try to get along, people!
Come on, we're comrades. We all
ate from the same pot, remember?
Don't say it, Mamina!
Oh, um, don't mind me...
Please continue, Captain.
Very well.
First, we'll have the
members of Chor Tempest...
That Mamina's changed, hasn't she?
Yes.
By the way, what did you
not want her to say, Roatre?
The mice.
Who knew Vura was flying
reconnaissance in a Simile?
I had no idea.
Right, and to make sure their
efforts don't go to waste...
...the rest of us need to be
in top form during this mission.
Sibylla Aurea, this is where
we're supposed to deploy.
You're right.
Then we're going to proceed
according to plan. Understood?
Roger!
How can the center deploy
Chor Tempest in this state?
It's just as Sibylla
Dominüra said to me once.
The center understands nothing!
It will be a while before
Chor Tempest returns.
I'd like you both to get
some rest while you can.
It's part of our duty
to rest... correct?
That's correct, Sibylla.
Make sure you don't miss any
signs of Chor Tempest's return.
I want you to reiterate
that to the patrol unit!
Yes, sir!
Mamina...
They forbade you from attending
Anglas's funeral, didn't they?
That is rather harsh of our
country, don't you think?
Oh, no, Sibylla Aurea.
The more tenuous a state
they find themselves in...
...the more people try to cling to
the comfort of their conventions.
You're right.
Mamina, I can see that
you've changed after all.
Do you think so?
Gimme a break!
"I'm detaching the cables for
the time being." So she says!
How annoying is that?
So they must be having a private
conversation one adult to another.
I say leave them alone.
3 o'clock! There's a huge shadow
in that break in the clouds.
There.
Found it!
We're going to keep the
communication cables intact...
...and approach from above.
What?
But we've found the base.
Those Simouns we encountered
at the Ruins could be here.
We should find out for sure.
Right.
Let's just confirm that
before we head home, Floe.
Okay.
Don't let down your guard!
There's a chance that the enemy
could be patrolling this area too.
Right.
Nothing here.
If we go much farther, we'll be
leaving the patrol area, Para-sama.
Don't you think we
should be heading back...
...to our rendezvous
point with the regina?
Para-sama?
Let's patrol this
area a little longer.
Roger!
There it is! The Messis!
To the rear of our ship.
A single Simoun!
Approaching at a rapid pace.
It's a Chor Tempest Simoun!
Who are they?
It's Aer and Yun!
Vura!
Who would've thought we'd
find Vura on board the Messis?
Yes, it's quite surprising.
Understood.
Actually, I was worried
about that myself.
Sibylla Aer and Sibylla
Yun, please go on ahead.
Right.
Please, be careful.
Thanks!
Captain!
I thought they might show up.
So?
Yes. Let's head that way ourselves.
Channel all power from the
helical motors to the engines!
We're heading for the
patrol zone at top speed!
Yes, sir!
Hey, Para-sama!
Para-sama!
We're heading toward the
rendezvous point with the regina.
Right!
Roger!
No, they've spotted us!
Retreat at top speed!
Para-sama, behind us!
Para-sama!
Come on, let's get going!
Roger!
Right!
We're going to keep going!
Shark Ri Majon!
Roger! Shark Ri Majon!
Can't shake them off!
Those guys are way too fast!
She just...
Neviril just told us
to make a run for it!
But...
Hurry!
We should do as she says!
Otherwise, both our
Simouns will be shot down.
We've got to hurry back
and let the others know.
They're coming after us!
Hang in there. We'll come
back for you as soon as we can!
Sibylla Aurea!
Neviril!
Sibylla Aurea...
Please have no fear.
No matter what it takes, I'll...
If you can understand what I'm
saying, then listen to me now!
I'm nothing but
an unknown sibylla...
...doomed to die in
such a place as this.
What do I care
about my own life?
But...
Behind me lies the finest sibylla
in all of Simulacrum Kyuukoku...
...Sibylla Aurea Neviril!
I'm getting her out
of here no matter what.
And not one of you will lay
so much as a finger on her!
No.
Both the sibylla behind you...
...and you yourself are
the finest of all sibyllae.
You two are sibyllae
from Simulacrum Kyuukoku.
There's no one closer
to God than you.
In our nation,
the Plumbum highlands...
...you are respected
above all others.
It is not our choice to
engage in battle with you.
And it is not our will to
capture an injured sibylla.
You...
We are priestesses of
the Plumbum Highlands.
We're not the same as the Shoukoku
soldiers on board this ship.
The battle we have just
been waging is already over.
There is no longer any
reason for us to fight.
Please, you must believe us.
If we were planning
to capture you...
...then there would be no need
for us to go to all these lengths.
Mamina...
Sibylla Aurea?
What those priestesses
are telling us...
I am sure it is the truth.
Please, you must hurry!
Right.
Come, together now.
There's no time to lose!
Right.
So that's what's
going to happen.
If you four let us get
away from this base...
...you'll have nowhere to go.
No. If they capture you,
you are certain to be killed!
You four recognized
me as a true sibylla!
And if you let me escape, you'll
be put to death as traitors!
Farewell, Sibylla Aurea.
Are you out of your mind?
If you're planning to go to your
death at the hands of those soldiers...
...then let me!
This is how it should be.
It's what I want.
Let me say it in your language...
Aer...
Aer!
We've sighted a huge
shadow straight ahead.
Captain, we believe it's
Shoukoku's aerial base!
And it appears to be on fire!
All hands, take your
positions for battle level one!
No, it's not true.
All hands, brace
yourself for impact!
Come on, we're going
to the priestesses' aid!
Mamina!
Let's hurry back
to the Messis!
Right.
No!
Step back, Roatreamon!
You're in our way!
Hurry!
Mamina!
Roatreamon!
Aer!
Come on, let's go, Roatreamon!
We've got to hurry too, Aer.
Aer!
We've got to get away from
here! We've got to run!
We can't afford to just stand
here forever, don't you see?
Sibylla!
It is played by my wounds...
the song of prayer.
Let it ring out over
the grieving universe.
Can we change tomorrow?
Don't be afraid.
I want to let you know
how my heart's overflowing.
I want to get closer to you.
I want to feel your pulse.
I was too defiant,
and I took the long way around.
The blue moon is swaying silently.
My true heart's desire is you.
I can't reach you.
My tears of pain trickle down.
Soar away into the
sky, song of prayer.
Carrying my love that came too late.
What can I do to change tomorrow?
Just hold on to "now" the way it is...
To Be Continued
She was a proud sibylla...
...not to mention just a young
girl from Simulacrum Kyuukoku.
And now Sibylla Mamina is dead.
Next time on Simoun...
Lament
Lament.