The countless flowers,
enveloped in light...
...gaze at tomorrow
with unwavering eyes.
Everyone wishes for me to be pure...
...but what can I bring
with me to the frayed skies?
What I've made my own
by breaking off flowers in bloom...
All such sinful things...
Why did I stop making
promises with the future?
Because even if I try
to run far from all the pain...
...a cold wind rustles
my hair... Don't you see?
Where can I ever find the answer?
Neviril, more... More powerful, Neviril.
Neviril, don't look! You can't
kill them if you see their eyes!
Neviril!
Amuria!
Wounds and Pain
Hey, Alty. Chase those birds. Please?
We're on duty right now, you know.
So what? We won't
run into the enemy here!
You'll just miss out
if you're so wound up.
Well, I guess you're
right about that, but...
They've been flying by us awhile.
I wonder where they're headed.
They can't fly forever. They'll rest
their wings when they're tired.
They've got to eat
when they get hungry, right?
What are they doing? We're on duty.
Things seem pretty
mellow these days.
I guess so.
We finally returned to duty too.
We seem to have lost our edge.
And Aer never
volunteers to fly anymore...
Para-sama...
How's Sibylla Aurea
doing these days?
The same, huh?
Are you concerned?
Not really.
But it's like we've been left hanging.
It seems like the others are
starting to accept her being gone.
This means we can never go back
to the old Chor Tempest, doesn't it?
Para-sama...
I'm keeping
an eye on you, Para-sama.
Just kidding.
Rimone,
we're heading for the pool now.
I'm not.
No.
You're still young, so your endurance...
I'm hungry!
Rimone! Hey, hold on!
Um, why don't we all take lunch first?
Is something the matter,
Sibylla Paraietta?
This is Sibylla Aurea's...
I'm still repairing it.
We had to rebuild
some things from scratch...
...so I had a hard time
getting all the components.
Your wounds haven't healed yet.
You haven't flown in a while.
Neviril! Hey, Neviril!
You've been cooped up long enough.
Get back on duty already!
Chor Tempest just gets lame missions
because you won't come back!
I can't take much more!
This is no place for us to be flying!
Are you listening, Neviril?
Neviril!
You stubborn mule!
Really, what a childish thing...
I guess I'm in no position to talk.
I'm sorry. There was
no need for you to do that.
No, I really didn't mind.
Really, what are
we going to do with Aer?
She's troubling you, right?
Shall I make her stop?
Of course, I'm sure
it's not going to be pretty...
Neviril... Don't you think
it's time you made things clear?
Made what clear?
Either way, we can't go on like this.
Won't you come back to the chor?
If you decide to go to the Spring,
then this time I'll accompany you.
I'm sorry.
I'm still unsure myself.
About going to the Spring...
and about flying Simouns.
I can't decide yet.
But...
I'm fully aware that it's wrong.
But I feel that no matter which choice
I make, it would be a betrayal...
Betrayal?
That's the feeling I get.
You mean Amuria.
Neviril... I've spent my life by your
side ever since we were children.
I've always walked
the same path as you.
That's why I can say this.
Your place is in a Simoun.
Even if that means
you'll have to betray Amuria...
Don't talk to me as if you know!
It's not as simple as that.
Leave me.
I see...
She's overwhelmed, huh?
And you've been so worried
about her, Para-sama...
But I don't see why she doesn't
try to understand how you feel.
I don't like the way Neviril's acting.
Don't talk like you know.
I do know.
In other words,
she's just being childish, right?
She's not.
Then what's up with her?
Sure, losing Amuria
was a big blow to her...
...but she's not
the only one who misses her.
Keeping herself holed up is really
causing trouble for the rest of us.
Kaim.
I'm sorry. I was out of line.
Para-sama.
What happened to your hands?
Oh, I was cleaning something...
You can't just leave them like that.
I know! Could you wait a little?
S-Sure.
I see... My nails are starting to shine.
Aren't they? You've got such beautiful
fingers, so take care of them...
...or Tempus Spatium will scold you.
You enjoy this.
I'm getting to take care of you, aren't I?
And touch you.
Just kidding.
I think she's just lonely.
We probably all are.
All of us on this ship...
Lonely, probably... That's what I think.
I'm sorry.
Hey, Para-sama.
Are you lonely too, Para-sama?
Do I look that bad to you?
That's not what I meant.
I'm asking because I'm lonely too.
Para-sama...
It's hot in here, isn't it?
Then why don't
we go where it's cooler?
No change in the princess yet?
Unfortunately, no.
It reminds me of the past.
Like a certain someone, no?
It's not uncommon for a sibylla
to question her flight duties.
I was the one who offered
you a helping hand then, right?
I haven't forgotten.
Vroom!
Pow-pow-pow-pow!
Vroom! Blam!
I see some more coming at us!
Blam! Pow-pow-pow-pow!
I'm not scared of that lame attack!
Let's see you hit us if you can!
Vroom! Pow-pow-pow-pow!
Hey! Para-sama!
Enemy to your right!
Strafe them with
the machine gun! Hurry!
All right!
Pow-pow-pow!
Wow, Para-sama! 100 of 100!
Pow-pow-pow! Pow-pow-pow-pow!
Another group of enemies
beyond the clouds! Ray Ri Majon!
Kaim?
Hey, Para-sama...
Let's do a Ri Majon.
Strange... We always do that, but...
Uh-oh! We've got to turn it off!
Kaim!
Big Sister...
Big Sister Kaim...
I was always by her side.
I'd decided to stay by her side forever.
And before I knew it, being near
her had become a natural thing.
How arrogant of me...
Thinking I was the only
one she could ever lean on...
I thought that it was obvious...
In that moment,
I wasn't the only one who felt pain.
Is that the reason why?
Para-sama?
Let's not do this.
Why?
Because you're still a child, Kaim.
What? I'm not a child!
You are.
I'm not!
We're all children.
That's why we try to heal our wounds
but end up creating new wounds.
I'm going now.
Good night, Kaim.
Why?
Jeez, why can't you
see how I feel, Para-sama?
Neviril!
Neviril! Just listen to me
for a second, will you?
Neviril!
I swear...
Now that it's come to this, I'll drag
you out if it's the last thing I do.
Paraietta.
Aer, I'd like to talk.
It doesn't look like we're
about to do any talking.
Didn't you know?
The maju pool can
be used for this too.
So how did I end up
having to face you like this?
Let's go!
The reason Neviril refuses to decide
isn't just because of Amuria.
I see now.
It was also out of
respect for my feelings.
Neviril, I'm sorry.
I didn't know anything.
But just let me say this.
I don't feel as though
you've betrayed me!
And I appreciate how
considerate you're being.
That's why...
That's why I'll put my hopes on
one who can surpass Amuria!
I've got you!
What?
Over here!
You're open!
What?
Is that good enough?
Aer! Go and pair up with Neviril!
You don't have to tell me that.
Hey, Floe...
What is it?
So what happens next?
What?
The birds who rest their wings...
You said they couldn't fly forever.
They'll fly again of course.
They will?
That's right. Because birds
were born to fly in the sky.
To fly in the sky...
If she's resting her wings, it's all right.
But a bird who can't fly
because she's been wounded...
...has no hope of survival.
It is played by my wounds...
the song of prayer.
Let it ring out over
the grieving universe.
Can we change tomorrow?
Don't be afraid.
I want to let you know
how my heart's overflowing.
"I want to get closer to you."
"I want to feel your pulse."
I was too defiant,
and I took the long way around.
The blue moon is swaying silently.
My true heart's desire is you.
I can't reach you.
My tears of pain trickle down.
Soar away into the sky, song of prayer.
Carrying my love that came too late.
What can I do to change tomorrow?
Just hold on to "now" the way it is...
To Be Continued
In order to sign a peace treaty...
...delegations from the highlands and
the Arcus Prima are about to meet.
Next time on Simoun...
Over International Waters
Over International Waters.