The countless flowers,
enveloped in light...
...gaze at tomorrow
with unwavering eyes.
Everyone wishes for me to be pure...
...but what can I bring
with me to the frayed skies?
What I've made my own
by breaking off flowers in bloom...
All such sinful things...
Why did I stop making
promises with the future?
Because even if I try
to run far from all the pain...
...a cold wind rustles
my hair... Don't you see?
Where can I ever find the answer?
I know they say,
"there's no place like home"...
...but you're all so comfortable.
It looks like some
still have a way to go.
Oh, the young lady with
the charming new hairstyle.
Boo!
What's the matter, Roatreamon?
Well, this bed seems
to be a little lopsided.
It's not just your imagination, milady?
It's old.
You can put up with that much.
But it really bothers me.
It creaks if I move
just a little, and that bothers me.
Hold this.
Do you think you can...
Here goes...
Hurry up...
How's that?
You fixed it.
Thank you, Mamina.
Don't thank me
for something like this.
What's with them?
Who knows?
Something to do with that haircut?
We're descending.
Have we reached our destination?
We've stopped.
United Front
Man, what a piece of junk.
Where's the bridge?
This is the priestesses' ship?
I imagined something better.
Like a secret garden?
Hey, look.
Those are sibyllae?
This is the first time I've seen one.
Hey, you! Quit socializing.
Let's go.
What's going on here?
This ship has Simoun
sibyllae on board...
We know. That's why we
went out of our way to join you.
Out of your way?
Perfect timing.
Can you take me to the bridge?
I won't allow
such disrespect! We are...
If you please... Come this way.
Yun.
Just a minute.
I will show them the way.
This way.
Neviril.
Wait here, guys.
Gotcha.
Just as you'd expect from Neviril.
Welcome to the Messis. First of all,
please make yourselves at home.
Thank you, Captain.
But is this really going to work?
The youngsters on board this ship
just don't look like they're up to battle...
If battles could be won on the basis
of looks alone, I would abide by that.
But the Simoun sibyllae
are the mainstay of our nation.
That is an undeniable fact.
All sides are watching as we
launch this historical campaign.
There will be no room for failure.
First and foremost, I believe it is
important that we trust each other.
Yes, you're probably right.
Then we've agreed
to go through with this?
Of course.
We're counting on you too.
Very well.
Explain, Dominüra.
We're about to form
a united front with these soldiers.
We're counting on you, Sibylla...
It's Neviril.
Sibylla Neviril.
A united front?
Yes, it seems we'll be joining
forces with those men somehow.
Us?
With those people?
Sibylla, you're so sweet!
We're being dragged
down further and further.
What'll become of us?
Well, a cramped ship getting
more cramped is a problem.
Some people seem
to be enjoying themselves.
Oh, for real?
You're from around here.
Yes, I enlisted as
soon as this war began.
Good for you. You're an ally of justice.
Then as a reward,
I'll show you around this ship.
What's wrong?
Uh, you see...
I shouldn't be touching a sibylla...
It won't make any difference.
We haven't gone to the Spring yet,
but that's the only difference.
Don't worry... I'm going
to become a woman anyway.
T-That's not what I meant...
Under normal circumstances,
a lowly enlisted man like me...
...wouldn't dare speak to a priestess...
I told you not
to make things so complicated!
Let's go!
The last few weeks,
enemy attacks have increased...
...leaving us no choice but
to fall back from our defense lines.
To keep the enemy from gaining more
ground, we'll launch an operation...
...to reclaim this town here,
Urvel, their apparent target.
It'll go down like this.
First, we'll transport our troops
by using the Simoun planes.
Transport? Us?
Yes, we'll outfit the Simouns with
special transport armor to do it.
The Simouns will transport soldiers?
If there were another way, we'd do it.
Can you try to understand?
The soldiers aboard will be deployed
to secret posts around the city.
After which the main battalion
will push forward on my signal.
We'll launch a pincer attack
and destroy the enemy.
What else do you wish us to do?
Leave the rest to us. Once you've
transported us, your job is done.
The operation will start the night
of the new moon, tomorrow at 2300.
Make sure you're all
in top form for this task.
Right.
What?
How could they do such
a thing to the Simouns?
I'm not doing this to our divine
aircraft because I want to either.
No way! Don't you feel
bad for the Simouns?
And that thing...
To tell you the truth, it's so lame!
I'm telling you...
The other day,
we were flying over the ocean.
And we saw this huge fish, and I
thought, "That looks pretty tasty."
You can tell she couldn't
care less about the rest of us.
The way she's just about
throwing herself at him...
Well, we might not be that different.
When your back's to the wall, there's
no time to think of others' feelings.
In an ideal world, we'd all
learn to understand each other...
...just like those two.
Is it good?
Yes, quite delicious.
Delicious?
Well, I'm glad to hear it.
I can see I've been mistaken
about sibyllae all along.
Mistaken?
Yes, I thought sibyllae were holier,
those whom must never be violated...
I thought you didn't talk much.
Are you disillusioned?
No, totally the opposite!
Because I'm talking to you like this.
Yeah, I'm glad too.
Floe.
What is it?
I hear you're friendly with a soldier.
Yes, his name is Mastiff.
Keep your standing in mind.
Standing?
We are priestesses
serving Tempus Spatium.
Indiscretions should be avoided.
That kind of talk's
so behind the times.
I can't help it. I like him.
Floe, I said you
shouldn't say things like that...
We'll all go to
the Spring sooner or later.
Then sibylla or soldier won't matter.
Listen, Floe...
Jeez, I'll just quit being a sibylla then!
Then it won't be a problem, right?
Floe!
What a headache...
Sorry to keep you waiting!
Still, is it all right?
Yes, it's fine. Did I keep you waiting?
No.
Really, Mastiff! You're so sweet!
Don't you want to get close?
It's not that...
Then...
Sibylla Floe, you and
the others serve Tempus Spatium...
...and are closest to God.
I guess. Where did that come from?
We too harbor
deep religious convictions.
But rather than out of love
and respect for Tempus Spatium...
...it's because we couldn't
go on if we didn't believe.
What do you think of
this war we're fighting?
I don't like it. But we've
got to fight or we'll be killed.
How do you feel about killing people?
Then why did you enlist?
I can't really explain it,
but everyone else enlisted...
Tomorrow's operation is a campaign
to reclaim the city where I was born.
Mornings are very beautiful in Urvel.
Especially the view from the top of
the tower in the center of the city...
It's beyond compare.
That's why I...
It'll be all right, Mastiff.
Because I'll protect you.
Begin the operation!
Let's go, men!
By the grace of Tempus Spatium!
By the grace!
We'll fly as close to the ground as
possible. Stay out of enemy sight.
We are banning Ri Majons till further
notice to avoid damaging facilities.
After transport, disengage
containers and retreat northwest.
Understood?
Yes, sir!
Simoun sibyllae,
we pray for your safe return.
I have to say they've become ugly.
I can't wait to get rid of these things.
It's hard not to drop them.
Yeah... I just hope Mastiff
doesn't run into any danger.
Roatreamon,
that hairstyle of yours is so lovely.
Thank you, Morinas.
We'll see more of these.
Rimone, this is a pivotal operation,
a springboard for future missions.
You'll understand soon enough.
So this is a front-line mission...
We're almost at
the drop-off point, Paraietta.
Right.
So we're done already?
That was a pretty quick operation.
I'll undock the containers.
So you didn't like those things either.
I guess. It's asking too much to even
pretend to like such awkward...
What's this...
Flares. Have they spotted us?
No, from the number, we should
assume it was a trap from the start.
Not good. If so, then those
old guys will get ambushed!
We'll go support them.
Understood, Aer?
They set us up.
Everyone, retreat!
Yes, sir!
Hey, they may be ugly,
but they can be useful.
We'll keep up support.
Okay.
See that? We've got
holy priestesses on our side!
Step it up, guys!
Right!
That's right, Rimone... Keep going...
Just keep going!
Just keep going?
What are you doing? Fire, Floe!
Mastiff... Where's Mastiff?
Floe!
Please, Alty, try to find him!
We don't have time.
Please!
What's wrong, Kaim? Fire!
Kaim!
But, Para-sama...
I can see...
I can see people down there!
Pull it together. Don't dare bring any
more dishonor to the priestesses!
Neviril, at this rate, they'll...
A Ri Majon. Strike with a Ri Majon.
I know. But a Ri Majon
would unleash too much force.
Will you stand by and
let those men die, Neviril?
The Ri Majon ban is lifted.
Floe, the Iron Ri Majon!
We can't! If we do,
it'll put Mastiff in danger!
His city will be...
If we don't, he'll die anyway!
Floe!
All right.
This is a Ri Majon's power?
Amazing... It's like ten tanks at once.
We can make it...
We can make it now!
Target is city plaza,
the enemy command center!
Iron Ri Majon!
Stop!
I want...
I want to protect Mastiff.
To protect Mastiff!
They did it!
They blew up
the enemy command center!
Could they really be
Tempus Spatium sibyllae...
Simouns...
Could that be Floe?
All right! The priestesses
have cleared the way for us!
Let's show what we're made of!
Right!
This battle... No...
They can't be divine aircraft...
They're...
The Simouns are...
The Simouns are demons!
Mastiff, what are you doing?
You can't let children like that
take part in a war anymore!
This war is ours to fight!
It is played by my wounds...
the song of prayer.
Let it ring out over
the grieving universe.
Can we change tomorrow?
Don't be afraid.
I want to let you know
how my heart's overflowing.
"I want to get closer to you."
"I want to feel your pulse."
I was too defiant,
and I took the long way around.
The blue moon is swaying silently.
My true heart's desire is you.
I can't reach you.
My tears of pain trickle down.
Soar away into the sky, song of prayer.
Carrying my love that came too late.
What can I do to change tomorrow?
Just hold on to "now" the way it is...
To Be Continued
Kaim and Alty have taken off on
a reconnaissance mission as a pair.
Next time on Simoun...
Sisters
Sisters.