The countless flowers,
enveloped in light...
...gaze at tomorrow
with unwavering eyes.
Everyone wishes for me to be pure...
...but what can I bring
with me to the frayed skies?
What I've made my own
by breaking off flowers in bloom...
All such sinful things...
Why did I stop making
promises with the future?
Because even if I try
to run far from all the pain...
...a cold wind rustles
my hair... Don't you see?
Where can I ever find the answer?
Dominüra?
You said you'd
do it for me, right?
The Emerald Ri Majon.
The Simouns are the
vehicles of the gods.
They can't fall.
But that's...
...the Emerald Ri Majon!
The Ruins
Hey, check that out
for me, will you?
Adjust the oil pressure for
the communication-wire ejectors!
I need somebody to
pull on this for me!
So we're going to be
working here again.
Yes.
First off, I want you all
to thoroughly pinpoint...
...the areas that sustained damage.
Right! We're already on it!
How is the old place?
Sibylla...
You look well. Glad to see it.
Yes.
Likewise.
We just got back, and things
are already hectic, I see.
Yes, we were told to put a
rush on the Simoun repairs.
Hmm.
Um.
Huh?
Excuse me.
I need you to take
a look at the lift.
Fine.
Sibylla.
Please excuse me.
All right.
Now that Shoukoku and the
highlands have formed an alliance...
...it's only a matter of
time before they attack.
Meaning we'll have to ask the sibyllae
again to carry out such a cruel task.
It's not a request.
It's an order, Guragief.
All of this happened
because of me.
All because of
my own selfishness!
To think that I could ever forget
Amuria and the Emerald Ri Majon...
How could you have
been so naïve, Neviril?
There are so many things that
must never be forgotten, Neviril!
Dominüra and Rimone...
They vanished, didn't they?
The Emerald Ri Majon...
...failed, I suppose.
Or maybe what really happened
was that they copped out!
If that were true, it would at
least offer some consolation.
No. What matters is not
the cause but the result.
For once again, we have lost
precious comrades of ours.
We've come home to the
Arcus Prima, haven't we?
How can you be so
cavalier about this, Floe?
Then are you saying that you're
not glad to be back, Alty?
Of course I'm glad!
Sure I'm glad, but still...
Come on, we're going to
be roommates, you know.
Let's try to get along.
I guess you're right.
Welcome back, everyone...
...to the Arcus Prima!
I know that you have all gone through
many changes during this time...
...and we are most...
The center was destroyed in the attack.
As for the 12 Simouns belonging
to Chor Rubor and Chor Caput...
...we had no choice but to abandon
any hopes of restoring them.
At this time...
...the only chor remaining
on the Arcus Prima...
...is your own, Chor Tempest.
High Priestess.
What has become of the members
of Chor Rubor and Chor Caput?
Nearly all of the sibyllae
have gone to the Spring.
You mean you gave them the axe.
Watch your mouth, Aer!
Come on, you know it's true!
If there are no Simouns
to fly, they don't need us.
Silence!
Now then, there's somebody here
who would like to meet with you all.
Father!
Welcome home, Neviril.
I have returned, Father.
That goes for all of you
Chor Tempest sibyllae.
We are happy that you
made it back safely.
Father.
Oh, that's right.
Yes, I know.
Sibylla Rimone and Sibylla
Dominüra are no longer with us.
That's right.
We are now headed toward the Ruins.
The Ruins?
Why the Ruins?
We all know it's
no simple matter to...
You are correct, Sibylla Yun.
The Ruins happen to be the holiest
place in all of Simulacrum Kyuukoku.
Not to mention a forbidden area.
However, it is imperative that...
...we reach the Ruins before the
forces of Shoukoku and the highlands.
By any chance...
Yes, what is your
question, Sibylla Floe?
By any chance, are you forcing us?
The only ones in all of
Simulacrum Kyuukoku...
...who have the ability
to execute this strategy...
This is not a request.
You are all expected to participate
in this battle without exception.
I guess this means we don't have the
right to go to the Spring anymore.
Yes.
Most likely...
...we have nowhere to escape to.
The only thing we
can do is move on.
I never thought I'd get the opportunity
to speak with you like this again.
No.
Neviril is no longer
the daughter I knew...
...who would do anything I'd ask of her.
And so there is nothing
more I can do for you.
Oh, no. I am grateful that you took
me under your wing, Vice Chancellor.
What?
No...
It's just that you seem
to be a changed person.
Yes.
We owe you our lives.
If it hadn't been for the Arcus Prima,
the Messis would have surely fallen.
You have done well.
Thank goodness we were in time.
But still, Captain...
Yes?
You entrusted me with 12 sibyllae,
and I failed to return them all to you.
Please forgive me.
Captain Wauf.
Yes?
A detailed report can wait.
In your opinion...
...are Sibylla Dominüra
and Sibylla Rimone...
I believe that they are both alive.
Then what exactly happened to them?
That I don't know. However...
Perhaps we will find the answer
to that question at the Ruins.
Neviril!
Aer, quickly!
Right!
Neviril.
What is it?
Oh... nothing.
Para-sama! Hurry!
I know this is hardest on you.
No.
I'm not the one who
has to suffer the most.
Look.
As planned...
...with communication cables
intact, Chor Tempest...
...will descend as low as possible...
...and protect the Ruins from attack
by the Shoukoku-highland forces.
So these are the Ruins.
Yes.
This is my first time here as well.
This is Tempus Spatium's holy land.
I don't think the enemy
is here yet, do you?
Don't let your guard down!
Oh, don't be so bossy!
Two o'clock!
What?
What's that?
Could those be Simouns?
But I've never seen
anything like them before!
Nor have I!
What should we do, Para-sama?
Para-sama!
Go after them!
Yes!
We'll take the one on the left!
Leave it to me!
Are they planning to attack?
The Shark Ri Majon?
No way!
The enemy?
Hurry, go after them, Para-sama!
We can't let them get away!
Who are they? Who's
operating those Simouns?
Who's flying those Simouns
to pray to the skies?
You're right.
How can they
possibly fly like that?
Enemies... Is that the enemy?
I won't let them get away!
They're firing at us!
I'm not afraid!
B-But, how could those
Simouns be enemies of ours?
Let's worry about that later, Floe!
Aer?
Aer, what do you
think you're doing?
Hurry!
Aer!
Leave the pursuit to the others.
Let's see what's inside those Ruins.
What?
What on earth are
you talking about?
My music box...
...it's playing now.
It's closed, but
it's still playing!
What?
They managed to get away.
What should we do now, Para-sama?
Head back to the Ruins.
Hey, it stopped.
Come on, let's go, Aer.
H-Hey...
Hold on a minute!
How come you're acting
like this all of a sudden?
But this is...
What's the matter, Neviril?
They think they're gonna get away!
Not if I have my way!
Huh? What the...
The Spring.
I hit it.
Just one down after all that?
Onasia!
Onasia...
I am glad that you're here...
...Sibylla Neviril...
...Sibylla Aer...
But why...
...why are you here, Onasia?
Sibylla Neviril...
...I happen to be everywhere.
And yet nowhere.
Can't catch up...
Who in the world
is flying that thing?
Good question.
And besides, there's something
not right about this place.
Let's go back!
Yes!
Onasia, how can...
...this place be exactly
the same as the Spring?
Tempus watches over
the flow of time.
While Spatium shows us
mankind's rightful place.
And when these two become a pair...
...they bestow boundless
blessings and fear to the people.
Yun?
Huh?
A Simoun?
Yun!
Yun, what's wrong?
This place... What exactly
is going on in this place?
Yun!
Here in the Ruins...
...time and space...
...are released from all curses.
Hold on a second, Yun.
Just what was going on back there?
They're all...
...waiting for me.
Neviril.
I know what's going on.
This isn't just some place
that looks like the Spring.
What?
What do you mean, Aer?
This place is...
...the Spring itself.
It's just like Grandpa said!
Anglas!
Aer!
It is played by my wounds...
the song of prayer.
Let it ring out over
the grieving universe.
Can we change tomorrow?
Don't be afraid.
I want to let you know
how my heart's overflowing.
I want to get closer to you.
I want to feel your pulse.
I was too defiant,
and I took the long way around.
The blue moon is swaying silently.
My true heart's desire is you.
I can't reach you.
My tears of pain trickle down.
Soar away into the
sky, song of prayer.
Carrying my love that came too late.
What can I do to change tomorrow?
Just hold on to "now" the way it is...
To Be Continued
Aer and Mamina have been barred
from attending Anglas's funeral.
Next time on Simoun...
The Funeral
The Funeral.