Junji and Asako's
Know-Your-Simoun Lecture Part 3
Fake-Anubituf and...
Pseudo-Guragief's...
Ready? One, two, three...
"I Never Thought You'd
Hide Anything from Me!"
This is a new program!
Episode one.
Yes, it's episode one.
This is fake-Anubituf, played by...
...the director of Simoun, Nishimura.
And I'm pseudo-Guragief, played
by the character designer...
...and animation supervisor....
...slash Anubituf's lover, Anubituf's
messenger of love, Asako Nishida.
Here's an old geezer. Right
off the bat, it's an old geezer.
You're in love with that geezertoo?
Oh, yes, I am!
In my mind, this old geezer...
...lives a secluded life in a
mountain shack, dressed smartly...
...and was once an
illustrious sibylla...
...someone who'd achieved
the ultimate Ri M_a_jons.
The kind of person who'd
confront the military councilor...
...and snap a 100-yen coin at him
with his fingers, breaking him in two!
That's how clear a picture I had of him!
Amazing.
It was like I'd accessed
Shoukoku's secret files.
And yet I couldn't draw his face.
His face?
And that's why I have a powerful
grudge against fake-Anubituf.
But during the
pre-production meeting...
...I remember telling you we
wouldn't be showing his face.
But his face was showing
in the storyboards...
...so I thought, "Hey, I get to show
the geezer's face just this once!"...
...and I re-edited my drawings.
But when the show aired, they'd
completely rubbed out his face!
I never thought you'd do
anything like that to me!
So now you're blaming me.
That's what it felt like to me.
Anyway, about these two...
Yes.
They have a casual little fling.
Well, during the course of this
scene, I completely forgot...
...that they were both girls.
That never even crossed my mind.
I started seeing them as just
having the purest feelings...
...of love for each other.
That's how I wanted to proceed.
Aer would be the young boy...
Yes, that's right.
But the thing is, after this scene, Aer
starts acting more like a young girl.
It's like Neviril has to go
through the process of taming her.
So were you thinking it
should be like My Fair Lady?
With Neviril as Professor
Higgins thinking...
...I'm gonna transform
you into my kind of woman?
No, actually...
In the end, Neviril's feelings
for Aer never really changed.
On the surface, yes, it
appears that they've changed.
But not the way Neviril
felt about her deep down.
Did you choose this scene?
Yes, I chose it.
It's over.
In the character design sheet...
Oh, here's the next scene.
Anyway, go on, tell us.
In the character-design sheet...
...there was a description of
how her hair was being braided.
And that really intrigued me.
And I thought that in order to
create that kind of hairstyle...
...we'd have to show it all, the
shape and everything, on screen.
I wanted to make that
a very convincing scene.
In my eyes, that scene...
...reminded me of someone
getting ready to become a bride...
...and someone helping her prepare.
That's the feeling I
got from that scene.
Of course, Roatreamon had no
inkling that Mamina was going to die.
But Mamina was going to fly as
Neviril's pair for the first time.
So she was getting her
ready for her big moment.
Like braiding her hair
for a bridal ceremony...
That's what I was thinking
when I drew those scenes.
Hey, here it comes.
It's the Wauf festival!
Can you tell me why Wauf...
...is piloting such a rickety ship
and being forced to wander the borders?
Well, it goes without saying that
he's the one whom in the next series...
The next series?
According to the outline
for the next series...
He was once the leader of a yakuza
gang. That's his backstory, you see.
Are you serious? Is it okay
for you to be mentioning that?
I think they're going
to bleep it out, but...
Jun-Jun, you're so irresponsible!
Well, with that kind of story...
Hey, just now I started seeing a
ton of rough sketches in my mind!
We're going to see Wauf as a youngster.
Seriously? I've got those sketches too!
You already drew them?
Oh, yes, I did!
Like "Wauf at 14" and "Wauf at 16."
So you've got everything.
They're all right at my fingertips.
I could turn in a
character-design sheet right now.
You're amazing!
So anyway, why have they
banished Wauf to the borders?
Well, you see, he's just extremely
competent and very intelligent.
He was far too capable.
That's the reason, you see.
And since he decided he wasn't
interested in being promoted...
...the center ended up
deciding what they'd do...
...was send him off to the borders...
...and not allow him to participate
in their political games.
If I were one of the
higher-ups in the center...
...I'd take a guy like this
and send him to the front lines.
So he's got a lot of status?
Yes.
I imagined him as being a
graduate of the military academy...
...and climbing higher and higher
in rank as an elite officer.
But then he grows weary of
the corruption at the top.
Here's his best line.
Yes, I'm sure there
was a time like that.
But wait, were we really like that once?
Is that like your own personal feeling?
Well, no, if you don't mind my
giving you a straight answer...
Just before the final episode,
the older men start talking...
...about the same thing.
In this scene, he mentions
it in a much more casual way.
But the thing is what they're
saying is actually a running theme...
...throughout this story
that holds it together.
That's my take on it.
"Long ago, we were all young girls."
So that's an underlying theme.
That's what we just decided!
It's like an afterthought, but...
Are you serious?
That's it? I was giving it
some serious thought now...
Here, we kept the
scene going by using...
...nothing but the sound
of the sibyllae breathing.
We recorded everyone's
breathing, actually.
We made sure that you
couldn't tell who was whom.
You did?
Wait, so if we raise the
volume, can we hear it?
And the part where he's
walking down the hall...
If you look at the whole
scene, you can hear...
...each one of the sibyllae deep
in sleep and their breathing.
Well, how lewd!
Oh, yeah, it's quite scandalous.
Now this scene...
It was the very first scene I
wrote for this particular episode.
Really?
It was the first one that came to mind.
Here, Morinas...
I think it was in this
scene that Morinas...
...realized for the first time
that he was seeing her as a girl.
And that she wanted him
to see her as a girl.
But here Wap_o_rif is so
spineless! I was so mad.
If he'd been standing in front of me,
I would have punched him out!
That's how annoyed I was!
We got this far, and it
still wasn't enough for you?
Giving her a little kiss
and then leaving? Come on!
You're absolutely right.
There's no point at all.
And I really like this confession scene.
I think Morinas was gambling on this.
If he saw her as a girl,
she'd choose to become a woman.
And if he just wanted to be friends
after all, then she'd become a man...
...because she wanted to work
on the Simouns by his side.
But Wap_o_rif...
They're getting smaller, aren't they?
Well, I'm certainly
glad she meant his boobs.
If she'd been pointing down there,
it would've been terrible!
So terrible that I'd never get
over it! You know what I mean?
Well, never mind that.
In this scene, Wap_o_rif...
Because he confessed his
love to her, he's forced to...
I can't keep up with you anymore.
Come on! Come on, Jun-Jun!
He has to eliminate one possibility.
Losing a physical trait like that because
of love. I found that very refreshing.
Well, I'm sure you were quite shocked
as soon as you read the script.
Yes, I was!
I was rushing around since I had to
give him smaller breasts all of a sudden.
Here we go.
You said initially that
this wasn't about love...
...but I can't get that feeling out
of my head that it is about love.
Because in the commentary
for the previous volume...
...you said that Yun couldn't
experience falling in love.
But I think in this scene...
...she experiences it for
the first and only time.
I'm happy that you think that.
Did you decide thatjust now too?
This show's story keeps
changing afterthe fact!
Yun, you see. Yun...
This is how she decided
to resolve everything.
But this decision of hers...
I just couldn't shake off
my feelings of pity for her.
Now that you've come out and
said she was probably in love...
...that makes me happy.
Looks like they're planning something.
Here it comes. Here it comes.
Wink!
That was a little touch that
the episode director added.
It wasn't in the script.
When the storyboards came in, Kato
asked if it was all right to do that.
And I said, "Please, feel free!"
And this scene here...
I heard about this yesterday...
That the chors were under the direct
supervision of the military council.
But...
Anubituf had some connection
to the high priestess.
And that's what he was trying
to tell Guragief. Is that right?
He was trying to tell him about that.
Or rather, he was
just about to tell him.
He couldn't make up his mind?
Yes, in the end...
Oh, Anubituf, you baby!
Well, that's what I find
so charming about him.
In retrospect, when you give
Anubituf a second look...
...you can see that he's never
really grown up completely.
I mean, in the first place...
...remember you said that he
didn't want to get Guragief...
...involved in all the politics?
Well, tell me this. Do men...
...really try to protect
their close friends that way?
Yes, I'd have to say that's true.
Really?
Yes.
It's almost like a man shielding his
wife from the corrupt aspects of his job!
No, no, that's exactly it.
That's exactly it?
Yes, it is.
So these two...
Is that because they were in love
back when they were paired up?
Yes. Remember that idea I had
that you totally shot down?
They went to the Spring, and before they
knew it, they'd both turned into men!
They both believed that the
other would become a woman, but...
And you sent me an e-mail saying that
it wouldn't happen in a million years!
In my mind...
...I've got enough ideas for
about three different OVAs...
...focusing on these two
and their days as a pair.
With a whole backstory about
how they came to be lovers!
But you never even came
close to that possibility.
Oh, wait, I'm in the middle
of researching their past.
Really? I'll be waiting for your report.
Didn't you say there was
something about his flight suit?
Flight suit?
Oh, well, I thought the scarf
he's wearing was awesome.
You did? Really?
I couldn't get over how
perfect the shape was.
I mean, that was deliberate, wasn't it?
Because when you look at the
other characters' costumes...
...there's nothing similar.
Right.
But even though that's just
a scarf around his neck...
...I thought, "Wow, that
scarf is shaped so perfectly."
In other words, I got the
impression that you'd...
...deliberately drawn it so
that it wasn't quite realistic.
What do you say about that?
Yes, in anime shows featuring Hiroshi
Miyauchi, like Kaiketsu Zubat...
...or in V3, they all
wore those white scarves.
I thought that if the captain's going into
battle, then he's got to have that scarf!
And that gesture there
was another touch by Kato.
Stealing away the hearts
of young girls everywhere.
Does anyone realize what that's causing?
The e-mails I've been getting...
Oozing with love.
I really don't know what to do.
I think those little gestures...
There's so much attention to detail.
Yes, they really worked, didn't they?
This is the scene...
...where I put my career as an
animator on the line. I gave it my all!
And I stole it away from
Matsuda, the producer.
At first, they were just going to do it.
That's right.
Hey, don't say it like that!
Just a little kiss.
Right.
Well, I thought I was doing
a little peck. That's all.
What did you think?
I thought it worked.
The way you showed him bracing
himself and then relaxing was perfect!
I couldn't believe you'd gone that far!
I carried out simulation
after simulation.
You simulated that scene?
Well, actually I walked up and
down the hall in the studio.
I played Anubituf...
...thinking, "If I stand on my tiptoes
here, I'll fall back in this manner...
...so this is where I've got to
fall away." That's what I did.
Amazing.
Of course you had someone
play Guragief, right?
Nope.
Virtual, virtual! Virtual Guragief!
A virtual Guragief!
That's right.
That's the measure of an animator!
Oh, I see.
The way Guragief braced himself
and then the way he relaxed...
I thought the timing was so
perfect it was almost funny.
Funny?
Sorry. I mean it was awesome.
About this girl...
Remember we were talking about
how she's connected to Amuria?
Well, it's not as though this girl
has any direct connection with Amuria.
But the story line, in
terms of structure...
The same kind of relationship
Neviril and Amuria...
...had in episode one is happening here.
That's what I hope some people will
be picking up as an underlying theme.
That's why I used the same
voice actress who played Amuria.
So you deliberately created all these
scenes where people are pairing up.
Yes, that's right.
At long last!
Floef!
That's right. I was
told to talk about Floef.
Why don't you talk about him now?
Well, the thing about Floef is
that with the other characters...
...I was able to design the way
they had matured in a natural way.
But in Floef's case, I didn't draw
him as the evolved version of Floe.
What I wanted to do was evoke my
own impression of the eternal youth.
And contrast him with Aer,
who's the eternal maiden.
That's the design I came up with.
And that's what I showed you, and I
asked you to use that design for Floef.
And you did approve the design.
That's right.
But the amazing thing is that...
...although in that respect there's no
direct link between Floe and Floef...
...as viewers, it seemed like
a perfectly natural transition.
So this is how Floe evolved!
This is how she ended up looking!
The fact that you pulled
that off is extraordinary.
You say that you evoked
something entirely different...
...but my impression is that
there's a definite emotional link.
My take on Floef is that after
everyone was done with the Simouns...
...I feel strongly that he was
the only one who came home to me.
It's like I married off
all the other girls...
...but Floef is the only one who...
...stayed by my side and
still needs me to mother him.
How about you, as the director?
I'm the dad who sent
him off, waving goodbye.
That's pretty sad!
So you're like Harukonf!
No emotional scenes!
Featuring: Junji Nishimura
Asako Nishida