The countless flowers,
enveloped in light...
...gaze at tomorrow
with unwavering eyes.
Everyone wishes for me to be pure...
...but what can I bring
with me to the frayed skies?
What I've made my own
by breaking off flowers in bloom...
All such sinful things...
Why did I stop making
promises with the future?
Because even if I try
to run far from all the pain...
...a cold wind rustles
my hair... Don't you see?
Where can I ever find the answer?
Yun!
Pair
But that's Yun.
Yun!
No way...
Where's Onasia?
What's become of Onasia, Yun?
And why are you...
I think I know why.
You decided this is where
you want to be, right, Yun?
Roatreamon, what do you mean?
Yun has made her choice.
She's chosen her own path.
I am here now.
That's right. Yun's right there.
Let's go.
Maybe...
...I should've come here before
with all my friends from Rubor.
Let's go in together.
Yes!
Paraietta, you've been
through a lot, haven't you?
I think we all have.
Morinas, you don't have
any regrets, do you?
Well, I did want to pray to
the skies in an ancient Simoun.
I mean I wanted to operate one!
I always wanted to sit in the captain's
chair on the Arcus Prima, just once!
Come on!
Knock it off, both of you!
But...
I...
I feel...
...as if I don't know
anything about any of you.
Right.
We don't really know
anything about each other.
But we must all fall if
we ever want to understand.
We must fall.
Uttering screams along the way...
Even as we're racked by fear...
With our hearts in our mouths...
We must hold on to ourselves and
keep falling and falling endlessly.
And as you continue to fall...
You reach out and cling to something...
...because you're so afraid,
and you try to hang on somehow.
But we have to let go
eventually, don't we?
Somewhere at the bottom of that
abyss, I promise you I'll be waiting.
Big Sister...
The priestesses of Chor Tempest...
Actually, I suppose we shouldn't
be calling them that anymore.
But yes, they should be returning soon.
I'm looking forward to finding out...
...what decision each of the
priestesses of Chor Tempest has made.
Yes, I'm looking forward to that too.
And what about those two?
I think they're going to be
our last responsibility here.
Yes.
At the Spring...
Yun was supporting us, wasn't she?
Yes.
It almost felt like being in a cradle.
All of our emotions,
all at the same time!
Listen, we're...
I am here now.
What's the matter, Aer?
Aer?
Tell me!
What?
Tell me why my heart hurts so much!
You know the answer, don't you?
Yes.
Why?
Why is it that my heart
is hurting so much?
Because you're in love.
This is love?
Yes. That's what love is, Aer.
I love you!
And I love you.
Amuria... She was a
strong person, wasn't she?
Yes, she was.
She was a strong person.
Secretly meeting with
a highland priestess...
...and before Tempus Spatium too?
That can't be the
action of a sane person.
I believe...
...this will be my last task for
the Chor Tempest Simoun sibyllae.
I hope that Tempus
Spatium will be forgiving.
I can't forget what Sibylla
Neviril said during the hearing.
I am not looking to blame
anyone for this war we're waging.
No matter how tragic and
painful our lives may be now...
...I believe that it was
all meant to happen this way.
Whether or not that is the
will of Tempus Spatium...
...it makes no difference to me now.
I no longer even care whether
it's God's will anymore...
However, I do have one
question for you all.
Despite all this...
...can I still call
myself a Simoun sibylla?
Guragief...
I have a feeling you never
stopped being a sibylla, even now.
Yes?
Oh, Paraietta!
I'm back.
We're all waiting on
the observation deck.
Okay.
Paraietta!
I'm back, Neviril.
I think I'll go on ahead!
You guys can join us later.
Would you do that, Aer?
See you!
I'll see you later too, Paraietta.
Right.
Will you dance with me?
Yes.
The soldiers are watching.
I don't mind.
Does it bother you, Neviril?
No, not really.
There are still two priestesses
who have not yet entered the Spring.
Yes, Sibylla Neviril and Sibylla Aer.
When do they plan to
make their pilgrimage?
Welcome back, everyone!
How was the city?
Everyone seemed really happy.
Yes, so many smiling faces!
Were you bored, Aer?
Well, I did some maju by
myself and then had some tea.
You guys haven't really
changed much. Uh...
I chose to become a woman.
I chose to become a woman too.
And I...
Male?
Right!
I chose to become male also.
I see...
They'll go as soon as
they feel ready to do so.
We cannot wait.
This is the most crucial
condition in our peace treaty.
Yes, but it's not as if a time limit has
been set for that condition to be met.
Foreign
We cannot wait.
The reason I didn't choose Aer...
...wasn't because I didn't
want to betray you once again.
It was simply an excuse to
protect myself from getting hurt.
I just wanted to be a good girl.
Can you imagine?
Wanting to be a good
girl all the time...
How childish is that?
I was sure that both Amuria and
Aer had chosen me as their pair...
...just as a tool...
...to complete the Emerald Ri Majon.
But I was wrong.
I was the one who was drawn
to their single-mindedness!
I came to realize that they're
both far more pure in spirit than I.
Neither of them are
afraid of getting hurt.
Yes, exactly, Paraietta.
I've made up my mind to be true
to what I'm feeling right now.
Once you stop trying to subject
others to your own feelings...
...you start to feel as if you can
plant your feet on a bigger stage.
I'm not going to wait and be
consumed by the waiting anymore.
And I'm going to stop blaming
everything on the one I love.
Because I want to learn what
it's like to be truly loved.
Paraietta! Did you...
Yes.
I chose to stay female.
We will arrange for them to be
escorted to the Spring by nightfall.
Our soldiers will accompany them.
I chose to become a woman.
Right.
Me too. I chose to become a woman too.
I see!
Welcome home.
I'm back.
What do you want?
Neviril!
Let go of me!
Aer!
Neviril!
Sibylla Aurea, please wait here for now.
Let go of me, you morons!
Aer...
Let go!
No! They can't make Neviril
and Aer go to the Spring.
Right!
Those two are our...
That's right. They're carrying
our present on their shoulders!
Paraietta, is this really part of the
peace treaty that Simulacrum agreed to?
Yeah, can they really do this?
Neviril and Aer...
...will only go to that
Spring over my dead body!
The eternal present...
Aer...
I love you.
I want to see you, Neviril!
I want to touch you, Neviril!
Aer...
Neviril...
Foreign
Don't do it, Alty!
Now what should we do?
Captain!
That title is no longer
appropriate for me.
But...
We have asked permission
to give our sibyllae...
...a final farewell before
they go to the Spring.
That's the most the Arcus Prima's
captain could manage to do for them.
Foreign
How uncharacteristically
barbaric of you!
I suppose.
Aer...
Right!
Let's go.
Thank you!
Please hurry!
Aer! Neviril!
Paraietta!
Floe, Alty.
Don't cry, Floe.
But...
I said don't cry!
Morinas.
We're counting on you!
Roatreamon...
I suppose this is
goodbye, Sibylla Aurea.
Farewell, both of you.
I know you two can do it!
Vura, Kaim.
Paraietta.
Farewell, Aer...
Neviril...
Farewell.
I promise you, someday,
we'll meet again...
Take care of yourselves.
Farewell, eternal priestesses.
It is played by my wounds...
the song of prayer.
Let it ring out over
the grieving universe.
Can we change tomorrow?
Don't be afraid.
I want to let you know
how my heart's overflowing.
I want to get closer to you.
I want to feel your pulse.
I was too defiant,
and I took the long way around.
The blue moon is swaying silently.
My true heart's desire is you.
I can't reach you.
My tears of pain trickle down.
Soar away into the sky, song of prayer.
Carrying my love that came too late.
What can I do to change tomorrow?
Just hold on to "now" the way it is...
To Be Continued
This is...
...the tale of the
sibyllae's "tomorrow."
Next time, on the final
episode of Simoun...
Their Portraits
Their Portraits.