The countless flowers,
enveloped in light...
...gaze at tomorrow
with unwavering eyes.
Everyone wishes for me to be pure...
...but what can I bring
with me to the frayed skies?
What I've made my own
by breaking off flowers in bloom...
All such sinful things...
Why did I stop making
promises with the future?
Because even if I try
to run far from all the pain...
...a cold wind rustles
my hair... Don't you see?
Where can I ever find the answer?
Bell Ri Majon!
Let's go, Kaim!
Right, Para-sama.
Rimone! You're going off course!
They failed.
We failed again?
I won't let them get away!
You did it!
Those two have been weird since
that day. Did something happen...
That was so Rimone's fault.
And after they let her in
for being some genius.
Floe...
This isn't fair to Aer.
White Loneliness
Chor Tempest may be back on
active duty, but in that condition...
That's Chor Tempest's current state.
Can you give us your perspective
as Chor Dextra's sole survivor?
Granted, we're not in
a position to be optimistic.
It's quite clear that this isn't the same
unit known as the "elite" chor.
At their current strength,
the afternoon shift is their best.
It seems they can't
return to night shift soon.
The team needs urgent rebuilding.
That's why I summoned you.
Can you do it, Sibylla Dominüra?
That's why I came after all.
Let's get moving!
We're checking the helical motors!
Don't forget to reload the ammo!
Look here, Rimone,
what are you doing?
Stop dragging Aer down.
If you're not motivated,
why don't you quit?
I'm here because
they told me to come.
Listen, you!
That's...
You must be the new arrival.
Your name's... Dominüra?
So you're Rimone.
Sibylla Rimone...
During your trainee days, your
talents were asserted to the fullest.
Since training school,
you've rewritten record books...
...as the youngest achiever in written
and practical exams, the top sagitta.
Afterwards, recognizing your skills,
the powers that be assigned you...
...the youngest sibylla, to Chor Tempest
as an exception among exceptions.
Combat experience... zero.
You mobilized without
permission the other day...
How...
Because I was interested.
You don't need me to tell
you that your dossier is ideal.
At least until Chor Tempest fell apart.
You're feeling hesitant, aren't you?
After all, who ever thought
you'd turn into a sibylla like this?
What are you saying?
I'm the one who can save you.
Trust me, dear.
Just do as I tell you.
Then you can
return to your past glory.
Back to the peak
where prodigies belong.
It seems Dominüra plans to rebuild
Chor Tempest with Rimone at its core.
Well, chor matters are your domain.
I have no clue about them.
No clue?
Just think.
What are those highly
emotional sibyllae thinking?
It's far beyond the grasp of us adults.
We can't even begin to understand
how the youngest sibylla feels...
How presumptuous would that be?
Guragief, let me say one thing.
What?
What we're dealing with now is a war.
Even children can sense that.
Who is it?
I didn't expect you to show up here.
Um, if I said I wanted to dissolve
our pair, what would you think, Aer?
I wouldn't mind.
If that's what you really want,
Rimone, I'm fine with it.
It's not as though I...
Is that all?
If only these hands on
the flight stick could be removed...
It can't be helped...
It can't be helped.
Rimone, you can
go over there till I'm done.
Hurry! Go over there!
I've never made any
choices on my own till now.
I've always done
whatever others told me to do.
And the next thing I knew, I was here.
So I'd like you to decide for me, Aer.
Does that mean you'd kill
someone if you were told to?
I don't know...
I won't tell you
what to do. Not anything.
I'm here because
I chose not to make choices.
If you're scared of fighting,
you should quit being a sibylla.
If you want to stay here,
you have to keep flying a Simoun.
If you really have no reason to be
here, quitting's the only choice.
Why?
Rimone, you're wonderfully talented.
I'm sure you can become
an amazing Simoun sibylla.
Rimone, match your partner!
Because there isn't anyone
who can keep up with you.
You're still a child!
Don't butt in just because
you have a little talent!
I'm just...
Why have you stopped
flying Simouns, Sibylla Aurea?
Are you afraid?
That's not it.
It's just that right now, I...
Sibylla Aurea...
what are we all here for?
You...
You should know the answer.
Please tell me...
As I am now, I can't possibly help you.
Rimone!
After all that...
After all that,
nothing's changed for me at all.
Scout their strength?
It seems there's word of
significant military action in the north.
In the north?
The Plumbum highlands?
Or rather, it's a chance to see
Dominüra and Rimone's compatibility.
They're sending those
two along with Floe and Alty.
Have those two paired up?
They say it was Dominüra's decision.
I wonder what kind of person she is?
Wait, Rimone.
This is where you're sitting.
I'm the auriga?
Right. This is where you belong.
But...
I know.
I'm doing this for your own good.
Despite that?
That's precisely why.
Since that incident...
...you've been subconsciously holding
back your abilities. Release them.
Didn't I tell you? No one
knows more about you than me.
Trust me.
If you do, everything will turn out fine.
She made Rimone the auriga.
I guess she's giving it some thought.
Well? Are you starting to get the feel?
Arriving at target destination shortly.
Maintain contact as we start scouting.
Roger.
So let's hear it, Rimone.
Are you up to the job of auriga?
Or are you being a pushover again?
There's to be
no talking during the operation.
Also, never ask Rimone
questions like that.
Yes, ma'am.
It's snowing.
No wonder it's so chilly.
Right wing, no sign of aircraft.
Likewise, no sign of aircraft ahead.
Enemy at three o'clock!
There's a lot!
Let's go too, Rimone.
Rimone!
Stop it, Rimone! A sudden
Silver Ri Majon is too risky!
No, we can.
It's not possible! Just do as I say!
We can do it.
It's simple.
Your trainee days still haunt you?
Not good. All this snow...
This snowstorm!
They're late... They should've
been back a long time ago.
Oh! Who knew there were so many?
What do we do?
We can barely fly straight in this
snowstorm, let alone try a Ri Majon.
It's hard enough for us...
but those two just paired up.
Rimone, we're retreating. There's
no point if we can't do a Ri Majon.
Our mission is scouting.
We'll regroup and come back later!
Rimone, answer me!
Rimone!
Aer.
Why did you come?
You were so late we came
to pick you up. Situation?
We're about to retreat.
Rimone!
What should we do, Rimone?
I...
Rimone! Do as I say!
Make up your own mind.
Or are you being a pushover again?
Rimone!
Silver Ri Majon.
Aer, together?
Roger! Go for it!
It's suicidal! In these conditions...
And it needs several Simouns!
Silver Ri Majon!
It won't work! Disengage!
That's right...
What I wanted to achieve...
...was a Ri Majon more
perfect than anyone else's.
Did we do it?
Did we destroy those enemy tanks?
She's a genius after all.
I was right about her all along.
It is played by my wounds...
the song of prayer.
Let it ring out over
the grieving universe.
Can we change tomorrow?
Don't be afraid.
I want to let you know
how my heart's overflowing.
"I want to get closer to you."
"I want to feel your pulse."
I was too defiant,
and I took the long way around.
The blue moon is swaying silently.
My true heart's desire is you.
I can't reach you.
My tears of pain trickle down.
Soar away into the sky, song of prayer.
Carrying my love that came too late.
What can I do to change tomorrow?
Just hold on to "now" the way it is...
To Be Continued
I'm Kaim, Sibylla Paraietta's...
Para-sama's pair.
Next time on Simoun...
Wounds and Pain
Wounds and Pain.