The countless flowers,
enveloped in light...
...gaze at tomorrow
with unwavering eyes.
Everyone wishes for me to be pure...
...but what can I bring
with me to the frayed skies?
What I've made my own
by breaking off flowers in bloom...
All such sinful things...
Why did I stop making
promises with the future?
Because even if I try
to run far from all the pain...
...a cold wind rustles
my hair... Don't you see?
Where can I ever find the answer?
Just one.
You just said,
"This will be easy," didn't you?
That fool...
The Simile Simoun
is a Simoun prototype...
It hasn't received
the grace of Tempus Spatium.
It can't draw a Ri Majon wake.
The Blue Spring
Such beautiful lines.
Watch closely. M? U isn't just practice.
Because it'll be your souls and
bodies that control the Simouns' flight.
Sibylla Elly, why are
you dressed like that?
This is the last time I'll ever
see anything as beautiful as this.
That's the emerald pattern...
Impossible!
What's she thinking?
She's crazy!
Does this look like a real Simoun?
Where did you find her?
She enlisted.
Enlisted? That's hard to believe.
Who'd volunteer at a time like this,
knowing they'd have to go into battle?
That's...
Are you in Tempest too?
Nobody else joined the battle.
I was alone...
What were you thinking?
But I was alone...
Simulating the Emerald
Ri Majon of all things.
How would that make
Neviril feel if she saw it?
Was I doing a Ri Majon?
Who's Neviril?
When Simoun sibyllae take to the
skies, it's called praying to the skies.
Make sure you never
use the word battle again.
So who's Neviril?
Neviril is the regina of Chor Tempest.
Sibylla Aurea, the Golden Priestess!
I want to pair up with her!
No way...
Why not?
She's the top Simoun rider, right?
Simoun rider...
Yeah, till now.
But it might not be true anymore.
Because you're amazing!
I think I really like you.
Hey, why don't you pair up with me?
Listen, where's this Neviril?
It brings back memories.
When we were trainees...
...nothing made me happier
than waiting on you.
That hasn't changed one bit.
Dressed like that...
you're leaving the ship too?
Yes. Since it's been a long
time since my 17th birthday...
I've decided to go to the Spring.
And I have one last favor to ask...
What is it?
I'm afraid...
...of going to the Spring.
If you don't mind...
Of course, Elly.
I will accompany you.
Neviril! Anyone seen Neviril?
Have you seen Neviril?
Stop calling her that. Please...
...um, Aer.
This is Chor Tempest's
maintenance hangar.
Where's Neviril?
You here, Neviril?
This is the cafeteria.
And this is the ballroom.
Where's Neviril?
Wow!
This is the forward deck.
Neviril, what's the meaning of this?
Elly said she's going to the Spring.
She's unpaired at the moment,
so I'm accompanying her.
You're lying.
Then why are you taking luggage?
I haven't made up my mind yet.
So there's a chance that
I might enter the Spring as well.
If so...
But you can't...
You can't do that!
Because if you enter the Spring...
...that means you'll have Tempus
Spatium choose your gender, right?
It's none of your business.
Who are you?
Aer. Chor Tempest Simoun sibylla.
I'd like to pair up with you.
Those who are neither male
nor female can fly Simouns.
Now's our only chance.
Yet if you go to the Spring,
you can't be my pair.
She couldn't to begin with.
My 17th birthday
passed over a year ago.
You're an exceptional Simoun sibylla...
...and in this state of emergency,
the nation can't afford to lose you.
So Onasia has agreed not
to summon you to the Spring...
Please, Paraietta.
Let me go.
Please.
We are all born as females.
But to create a society,
half the population must be male.
Tempus Spatium has decreed
the world should be so.
Once we've turned 17, we're allowed
to choose our permanent gender.
But in the case of Simoun sibyllae,
this can be delayed.
Our nation, Kyuukoku, has gotten
invaded by countless countries.
Our only hope of battling
them are Simouns...
...and you sibyllae,
who can talk with the Simouns.
If you wish, you may delay
your pilgrimage to the Spring.
If, on the other hand, you yearn for
the Spring, we cannot stop you.
Especially Chor Tempest...
Since the war began, you and Chor
Caput have suffered great losses.
Those who've turned 17 are free
to choose the same path as Neviril.
There's no way I would.
Man or woman, I haven't
decided yet. I don't even want to.
As long as I'm in battle with a Simoun,
I won't have to go to the Spring.
That's why I came here.
Are you guys different?
No question.
Once you're of age, you have to go.
It means you're going
to become an adult.
But right now, the nation
needs our powers, so...
Oh? Is that right?
Then you've all already decided
to become a man or woman?
Have you, Big Sister?
Listen, you...
It's fine, Elly.
One last time...
Won't you pair up with me?
I want you to see me fly as
an auriga to the great temple below.
Then I'll have them
get a Simoun ready!
Well? How's my driving?
Not "driving,"
"speaking with the Simoun."
Oh, sorry. I'm just so psyched.
Because this is the first time
I've touched a real Simoun.
First time?
I've always wanted to ride one.
Really?
You know what I mean, don't you?
Everything has changed.
Because you're not "praying to
the skies" for Tempus Spatium...
...but for war?
Yes.
There's no difference.
You don't understand.
What kind...
What kind of place the battlefield is.
I do. Because I trained
on the front lines in the south.
Before the war, sibyllae would go to
the Spring when they turned 17, right?
Yes.
But now, the great temple's laws
say we don't have to go to the Spring.
As long as we're winning this war...
Thank you, Aer.
How rude. She's an auriga, right?
Yes.
So she made you fly as her sagitta?
The finest auriga in the nation?
Out of all of us here, is Paraietta
the only one who's turned 17?
Big Sister, you'll be
17 next month, right?
Either way, we all will be soon.
Aren't you going after Neviril?
You're going to become a man for her...
You made
that decision long ago, right?
I still feel that there are things
I need to accomplish here.
Elly, have you decided?
Which gender you'll
choose at the Spring.
Um, no.
I see.
I've always been female, so I think
it'd be more natural to stay one.
I might also want to become a male.
After all, there aren't a lot of job
opportunities unless you're a man.
I know you must be weary,
Simoun sibylla, but...
I don't mind.
Simoun sibylla...
Such a beautiful sight...
O priestess, please guide
our nation to the righteous path.
Please protect us.
Are you Neviril?
Yes.
If I'm with you,
I think I'll have fun flying.
O sibyllae...
We are overjoyed to know that
your time for prayer is now over.
We thank you for having
protected us all thus far...
What should I do?
I'm supposed to think
"male" or "female" in my head...
...but what happens if I think of both?
You'll be fine.
There's nothing to worry about, Elly.
Onasia...
Great Priestess Onasia...
Forgive me for not journeying here
though my 17th birthday is long past.
Sibylla Elly, enter the Spring.
And offer a prayer...
No...
What should I do? I can't decide!
The holy sounds of Tempus Spatium
have just been bestowed upon you.
I was told that starting
today, my name is Eliph.
Yes.
Congratulations.
They say your voice
changes overtime...
...and your chest gets smaller, but...
Nothing's really changed, has it?
Right.
Nothing has changed, Eliph.
Well, Sibylla Roatreamon.
You're staying too, my lady?
I grew up being told
I should become a sibylla...
...so if I went home now,
they'd yell at me.
We all have one, don't we? A reason...
The thing is...
I can't fly this alone, right?
You didn't go to the Spring?
I did go. But I decided not to enter.
Higher.
Than our ship?
Please.
It is played by my wounds...
the song of prayer.
Let it ring out over
the grieving universe.
Can we change tomorrow?
Don't be afraid.
I want to let you know
how my heart's overflowing.
"I want to get closer to you."
"I want to feel your pulse."
I was too defiant,
and I took the long way around.
The blue moon is swaying silently.
My true heart's desire is you.
I can't reach you.
My tears of pain trickle down.
Soar away into the sky, song of prayer.
Carrying my love that came too late.
What can I do to change tomorrow?
Just hold on to "now" the way it is...
To Be Continued
Shoukoku's massive long-range cannons are
headed this way.
Next time on Simoun...
The Distant War
The Distant War.