The countless flowers,
enveloped in light...
...gaze at tomorrow
with unwavering eyes.
Everyone wishes for me to be pure...
...but what can I bring
with me to the frayed skies?
What I've made my own
by breaking off flowers in bloom...
All such sinful things...
Why did I stop making
promises with the future?
Because even if I try
to run far from all the pain...
...a cold wind rustles
my hair... Don't you see?
Where can I ever find the answer?
The technology
in my country, Shoukoku...
...is the most
cutting edge in Daikuuriku.
Even so, we still can't build a plane
that can fly above the clouds...
...and if lightning struck the gas tank,
it would instantly explode into flames.
We're aware of
this danger but must go forth.
Beyond the waves' crests...
Kyuukoku.
This sublime and peaceful
country carries a certain secret.
To gain this secret, my country
has mounted countless invasions.
But we have always been thwarted.
Kyuukoku's secret.
The demonic Simoun.
No other vessel in Daikuuriku
is capable of flying so freely...
Fallen Wings
...throughout the skies.
It's a routine patrol flight.
The governors are observing today,
so they're making a show of it.
Neviril-sama...
Call her "Sibylla Aurea."
She glitters like gold...
Was your father well, Neviril?
Amuria, you're tormenting me.
There are hundreds
of Ri Majon patterns...
...and depending on the mix,
they take infinite shapes.
We've forgotten what many
of those patterns signify...
...but the Simoun sibyllae are
always prepared to rediscover them.
Your daughter is
an outstanding pilot, as expected.
It seems she's become a
full-fledged pilot, which relieves me.
Indeed, she's become the premier
Simoun sibylla called "Sibylla Aurea."
Her prayers may
indeed be exceptional...
...but if she's used in war,
we're only tarnishing an old tradition.
High Priestess...
How can we use prayers meant
only for the gods for war?
By deploying Simouns to the border,
we display Tempus Spatium's power...
...and can repulse these nefarious
invaders in a peaceful manner.
Is that not
in accordance with God's will?
My father made a point of ordering
Chor Tempest to mobilize...
...since he wanted to look
good for the spectators.
It's because Chor Tempest
is the best chor.
Amuria, it's not becoming of
a sibylla to use the word "best."
You're wrong.
We're only offering up our prayers.
By achieving a perfect Ri Majon,
we give comfort to Tempus Spatium.
It is our duty to become powerful.
More and more powerful.
Powerful? For what purpose?
Neviril!
Do you hear what I'm hearing?
This is...
This is Neviril of Chor Tempest.
Are you all right?
They fell... Which Simoun fell?
All of them.
Chor Caput has fallen.
We are the only survivors.
Send a messenger
to Guragief-sama right away.
Sibylla Aurea, please be careful.
That's impossible.
A Simoun was shot down...
Calm down, Neviril.
We knew this day
would come someday.
Ever since the day they decided
to send us into battle with Simouns.
No, Amuria.
Simouns are divine aircraft.
No matter what country
develops a flying machine...
...they cannot match the craft of gods.
That's why enemies flee
at the sight of a Simoun...
They flee when they see us...
My lady...
Did I say something?
Are we going to die?
But I'm with you,
Para-sama, I don't mind dying.
I still have things to do. I can't die.
You mean Neviril?
Did I allow such familiar
addressing, Kaim?
Oh, we need your permission.
I wonder if they're good? Shoukoku's
flying machines float like clouds, right?
There must be some mistake.
There's no question.
Simouns can't fall.
We just fly them,
and the enemy runs off.
Sublime harmony...
Neviril, let's try the Emerald Ri Majon.
That again. We don't have the ancient
Ri Majon patterns fully analyzed yet.
Simoun sibyllae of legend succeeded
with an Emerald Ri Majon...
...and served as priestesses
close to Tempus Spatium.
If we succeed,
we can end up that way too.
You're so impatient. Now isn't
the time to think of such things.
I want to become more powerful.
That's the border. I'm taking us down.
The Simouns are divine aircraft.
True, the technology is on
a whole different level than ours.
But if we can discover their secret,
our country will make great advances.
The Falcon Ri Majon.
If they dare to enter our country,
then they'll never leave.
They're just flying after all.
They're not like Simouns.
A Simoun inscribes patterns upon
the sky using the light from its wake.
That is a Ri Majon.
We haven't yet discovered
why it's so powerful.
Once we find out this secret,
our nation's technology will advance.
But Kyuukoku has long kept
the secrets of the Simouns from us.
We've been taught that Simouns
send those who pursue them to hell.
But now I see.
The Simouns are mere machines.
There's no hell in sight.
How can there be so many?
The Simouns aren't divine aircraft.
They're just machines.
So they can fall.
It's possible to shoot them down.
Someday we'll solve
the Ri Majon mystery.
The era of Kyuukoku's monopoly
on Simoun technology will end.
There are a lot, but they're slowpokes!
Shoot them all down!
Shark Ri Majon!
Six-unit Iron Ri Majon...
Got it!
They'll erase the glyph!
What's with them?
If they fail to draw a glyph,
they can't achieve a Ri Majon.
The Emerald Ri Majon, Neviril.
A miracle is sure to happen.
No, Amuria.
There's no telling what will happen...
I want to become stronger.
I want to become stronger, Neviril.
I can't go on like this!
So many things getting in our way.
They're taking our wings away.
That's right... We've got to fight.
Amuria!
I said I want to become stronger.
You understand, right, Neviril?
We can do it.
Let's go. To where we can be free.
Neviril, more... More powerful, Neviril.
Yes.
She was so beautiful...
Neviril, don't look! You can't
kill them if you see their eyes!
Neviril!
The Emerald Ri Majon failed.
What's going on?
Neviril!
Tempus Spatium is full of fury.
The Simouns are machines.
Not divine aircraft at all.
My country will surely
discover this demonic secret...
But could it be...
...they really were...
Huh?
Sibylla Aurea is exhausted.
I'll relay your message.
Paraietta-sama.
Um, we're...
...leaving the ship?
Yes.
We intend to go to
the Spring to meet with Onasia.
If you go, you can't be a sibylla.
You'll never be able to touch
a Simoun again. You're sure?
Yes.
I intend to become a male.
To become just as gallant as you.
It's unseemly to speak of
such intentions to others. Go on.
Do you plan to stare at
her door forever, senpai?
I am unable
to assuage a sibylla's grief.
All I can do is grieve just as much.
Are you a trainee?
This is the sanctuary
of the sibyllae. Leave.
Are the priestesses
in better humor now?
Should the moon be covered
by clouds, the stars fade too.
That's where they stand.
They have lost a precious pair.
They're not to blame.
Chor Tempest has lost three sibyllae.
Not counting those going to the Spring.
Meaning it is no longer our elite chor?
Dux.
What is it?
Sibylla Floe. Sibylla Rimone.
Actually, this child...
Sibylla? But...
She's young, but we're having her join
Chor Tempest as a special case.
This is most irregular. Promoting
such a young trainee to sibylla.
But if we don't, we'll no longer
be able to protect the Simouns.
So is that doll your only replacement?
No, there's one more before launch.
Another oddball?
No, a normal one, Captain.
Who's that?
Wow! This is a Simoun, huh?
I've never seen the real thing before.
Sibylla Aer?
I expected you to arrive sooner.
Shoukoku's planes are advancing
along the border once again.
I'm sending Chor Tempest.
Isn't that futile?
I'm sure Neviril won't like it.
I agree.
I don't see Neviril and Paraietta here.
They won't want to fly.
I'm so scared...
We have nothing but
the Simouns to fight with.
But is it God's will that
we do something like this?
I'm going up.
I'm on my way.
Please wait, Sibylla Aer!
She's probably not a priestess.
That's a Simile training craft!
That can't achieve a Ri Majon...
The rest of you can go on praying.
I've come here to go into battle.
It is played by my wounds...
the song of prayer.
Let it ring out over
the grieving universe.
Can we change tomorrow?
Don't be afraid.
I want to let you know
how my heart's overflowing.
"I want to get closer to you."
"I want to feel your pulse."
I was too defiant,
and I took the long way around.
The blue moon is swaying silently.
My true heart's desire is you.
I can't reach you.
My tears of pain trickle down.
Soar away into the sky, song of prayer.
Carrying my love that came too late.
What can I do to change tomorrow?
Just hold on to "now" the way it is...
To Be Continued
Simouns can't
possibly fall, and yet they have.
The Blue Spring
Next time on Simoun...
The Blue Spring.