The countless flowers,
enveloped in light...
...gaze at tomorrow
with unwavering eyes.
Everyone wishes for me to be pure...
...but what can I bring
with me to the frayed skies?
What I've made my own
by breaking off flowers in bloom...
All such sinful things...
Why did I stop making
promises with the future?
Because even if I try
to run far from all the pain...
...a cold wind rustles
my hair... Don't you see?
Where can I ever find the answer?
Hold on!
Big Sister...
I'm Para-sama's pair! You can't
just tell me to team up with Alty now.
This is all for the sake of restoring
Chor Tempest to its former prestige.
Neviril, look!
What's happening?
Why aren't their prayers
being heard by the Simoun gem?
Kaim!
Big Sister!
Don't call me that!
I said stop calling me that!
Reason
Their prayers?
Yes, the divine vehicles are
activated by Simoun sibylla prayers.
The two priestesses are joined in
spirit as they honor Tempus Spatium.
To reject the one you're paired with
is the same as rejecting the Simoun.
I really find that hard to believe.
We've never heard such a thing.
I'm only speculating.
Even so, thanks to your efforts...
...we were able to discover
a secret aspect of the Simouns.
Well done...
...or would that be
inappropriate to say?
What this means...
...is that my sister and I won't be
able to fly as a pair anymore, right?
Do you think you
can understand why not?
Yes.
No enemies in sight, huh?
Oh, boy!
I'm so bored to death it feels
like I'm gonna get moldy all over!
Pow!
In other words,
you'd rather we were at war?
I never said that.
It's just that there's nothing to do.
Such sinful thoughts should be
banished from your mind right away.
Oh, I'm so bored! I'm so bored!
She doesn't look it, but Roatreamon
can be scary when she gets mad.
Don't look at me.
What are you thinking about?
Something that's not on your mind.
I see.
The Emerald Ri Majon?
Right, the ultimate Ri Majon
that can be achieved by a Simoun.
They say it can inscribe
the final miracle on earth.
Final?
Simulating the Emerald
Ri Majon of all things.
How would that make
Neviril feel if she saw it?
Was I doing a Ri Majon?
I get it now.
So that's what that was all about.
Aer?
Aer.
Hey, tell me...
What happens?
Unfortunately,
I've never seen it before myself.
Waporif, didn't Neviril and Amuria...
So Neviril and Amuria did it.
The Emerald Ri Majon...
Well...
I get it! They didn't succeed.
That's right.
So that's it. Not with Amuria...
Oh my! You're so thorough!
The god
Tempus Spatium is a neat freak.
If the water's murky,
Tempus Spatium won't come near.
That's what Mother said.
According to her, misfortune seeps in
through dirty kitchens and bathtubs.
You're amazing. You know so
many things I've never heard of.
Maybe it best suits me.
Cleaning house
like this, cooking meals...
Maybe I was only
dreaming for a moment.
It's so stuck on I can barely
scrape it off! If we had citrus...
Citrus?
The acid rubs stains away.
As I said, you're amazing!
It's delicious!
Neviril!
Do it with me! The Emerald Ri Majon!
Aer! You...
I know.
It was a bust with Amuria, right?
I know I'll work out. Come on,
Neviril, let's do the Emerald...
Stop it!
Wait.
I'll get something to wipe that up.
Neviril, you okay?
Shut up, Aer.
Why?
We just don't talk about that...
Because it reminds
you of Amuria's death?
Neviril!
That was just going too far.
I feel so sorry for Neviril.
I never knew Amuria personally.
But to speak ill of
the dead is an unforgivable sin.
Come on. I was only...
Come with me.
Aer...
Why'd you bring me here?
Jeez.
Listen, do you love Neviril or not?
I love her.
Not like that...
Then how?
Wishing to chat just a second more
or hold her tight and feel her warmth...
The kind of love where you
desire her more than anything.
I desire Neviril.
If I'm with Neviril,
I know I can fly higher than anyone.
Aer.
Well?
Well what?
How'd it feel?
Since we're not about
to go into battle, it felt weird!
When you stop feeling that way,
it'll mean you're really in love!
Neviril was in love with Amuria.
Do you get what I'm saying?
What does that have to do
with the Emerald Ri Majon?
It's better in all kinds
of ways when you're in love!
Neviril!
Neviril...
Neviril.
Don't worry. It'll happen with us.
We can do it.
The Emerald Ri Majon!
Amuria...
Because it reminds
you of Amuria's death?
Neviril! What's wrong, Neviril?
Neviril!
I'll open the window.
It's horribly dusty in here, but Aer...
You'd rather not be in the same
room with everybody, right?
Yes. Thank you.
All right... you get some rest now.
The Emerald Ri Majon...
It must be incredible.
I'd like to try it too.
With Dominüra?
I don't really mind who I do it with...
Do you love Dominüra, Rimone?
I don't know.
If you do, then you'll want to kiss even
when you're not in a Simoun, I hear.
I hear it's better in all
ways when you're in love.
All kinds?
Right, all kinds.
What did the Powers That Be say?
That so long as the enemy's idle,
we'll take a wait-and-see approach.
After discovering that aerial base,
they're saying to let it go?
It seems an unexpected crisis
occurred aboard the Arcus Prima...
...and everything's in chaos.
As I thought...
...the here and now is so distracting
that they're missing the big picture.
If this goes on, Kyuukoku will...
Sibylla Dominüra...
If I may, you seem
to be in some kind of rush.
Far be it from me to presume
such things of a sibylla...
Yes, I would say that's accurate.
Rimone.
What's the matter?
Is there some problem?
What is it?
What did you think?
Did you feel like you were in love?
Run along now.
Amuria is... dead.
Neviril?
Neviril!
I was looking for you.
But why?
Whoops-a-daisy.
Now wait a minute...
You're not feeling well?
Look at me, will you?
You could choke in this room.
It's full of old junk.
There's no air circulation.
All that's left...
...is useless memories, nothing more.
Let's go outside.
We've got to go.
Let's open the door together, Neviril.
Neviril...
What are you doing?
T-That hurts, you know!
Neviril's exhausted. Get out of here.
Huh? But...
I said get out of here!
Neviril, I don't think Aer
means you any harm. But...
I want...
...to get some sleep now.
Do you mind?
N-No.
Where's Aer?
Who knows?
What she said was
shocking, don't you think?
It's not just Neviril.
All this time, the rest
of us were avoiding it too.
Saying those words out loud...
Because if we did, it felt as though
we'd never be able to move on.
Amuria was so strong.
Always looking skyward...
She never seemed unsure of herself.
Yes, war was something
I never thought I could handle...
...but if she was there,
I thought we couldn't lose.
That's how she made me feel.
That's why I was afraid to admit it.
No, I still don't want
to admit it, even now.
But...
What's this?
Uh, guess I'm busted.
What is it?
What's up with that?
That's awful!
What kind of animal is that?
So funny...
Excuse me!
I worked really hard sewing it!
Sure, I made him a little uglier, but...
Looks like he's already met his doom.
No, he hasn't. He's so sweet!
I guess you could
say he took after his creator.
Hey, you.
I never wanted to hurt Neviril.
It's just that I felt if we were together,
we could accomplish anything.
How can you be so sure of yourself?
Have you never
experienced utter despair?
If I had, what good would it do?
Entrusting Neviril to you
may have been a mistake.
We can't afford to wait
for orders from above.
Now that the enemy's idle,
we must investigate that aerial base.
Neviril, Aer, I leave this to you.
Wait, these two are...
Those two are, at the moment,
Chor Tempest's top pair.
What is the issue?
But...
Dominüra, I'm not in a place
where I can team up with Aer.
You said so
yesterday, right? The Simouns...
That's precisely why.
People's emotions aren't toys!
If you're speculating...
Neviril...
I... want to fly with you.
Maybe you don't want to...
...but I...
Neviril...
I want you to put
Kyuukoku above all else.
We are Simoun sibyllae after all.
Worried?
I knew it was futile.
It's not futile.
You and I will be able to fly.
You and I...
Their prayers were heard, it seems.
So emotional stuff had
nothing to do with it, right?
That's not possible. The only
explanation would be that Neviril...
Neviril...
But why?
I knew it. You're seeking me after all.
You can fly if you're with me.
You can do it if you're with me.
Am I really seeking Aer?
Surely not...
Because I... Because I...
Because I'm afraid of Aer.
It is played by my wounds...
the song of prayer.
Let it ring out over
the grieving universe.
Can we change tomorrow?
Don't be afraid.
I want to let you know
how my heart's overflowing.
"I want to get closer to you."
"I want to feel your pulse."
I was too defiant,
and I took the long way around.
The blue moon is swaying silently.
My true heart's desire is you.
I can't reach you.
My tears of pain trickle down.
Soar away into the sky, song of prayer.
Carrying my love that came too late.
What can I do to change tomorrow?
Just hold on to "now" the way it is...
To Be Continued
Are you telling me to dismantle
a Simoun, Sibylla Dominüra?
Next time on Simoun...
Sacrosanct
Sacrosanct.