The countless flowers,
enveloped in light...
...gaze at tomorrow
with unwavering eyes.
Everyone wishes for me to be pure...
...but what can I bring
with me to the frayed skies?
What I've made my own
by breaking off flowers in bloom...
All such sinful things...
Why did I stop making
promises with the future?
Because even if I try
to run far from all the pain...
...a cold wind rustles
my hair... Don't you see?
Where can I ever find the answer?
I wanted you to move on to
the next phase of your life.
I can't lose face in the high council.
Chor Tempest can't go on as it has.
Until the repairs on the Arcus Prima
are completed, Chor Tempest...
...will board the Messis and be
charged with border reconnaissance.
What? We're boarding that thing?
I'm a bit...
Don't be unreasonable. You should
just be thankful Chor Tempest...
She's right.
That old boat should do just fine.
I don't mind at all!
Birds in a Cage
Hey, are we really
gonna live here, all together?
Floe, you'd better save your
complaining till you've secured a spot.
The beds on the window side
are first come, first served.
No way!
Best regards, Floe.
Best regards, Aer.
Big Sister, do you think we'll
be living here for a long time?
Just like we can't
change what's happened...
...there's no telling
what's in the future.
Right...
You may be right about that, Kaim.
Yun, where's Mamina?
I have no idea.
I see...
We believe the damage
was caused in transit.
The communication-wire
ejectors have come a bit loose.
Can you manage
without replacing parts?
Yes, somehow...
There'll be a severe shortage of
replacement parts. Keep that in mind.
Right.
Looks like you're having
a hard time, Waporif.
Not compared to
you sibyllae. You're all so noble.
Everything must seem new to you...
I'm sure you're taken aback.
Noble you say? We can't afford
to worry about being noble right now.
Anyway, I...
As long as you can
fly a Simoun, correct?
Absolutely.
Then that's how I'd like
the reconnaissance tasks divided.
Very well.
But if I may, Sibylla Dominüra...
What is it?
Chor Tempest is the finest chor and
the pride of Simulacrum Kyuukoku.
Though my crew and I are
greatly honored by your presence...
...why were you assigned
to an old front-line vessel...
Captain, the inconvenience
is written all over your face.
N-No, not at all.
No matter. You're quite right.
And someone from a different chain
of command is invading your bridge.
Very well, Sibylla Dominüra.
I will refrain from
asking you anything more.
Sibylla, please stop... Sibylla!
It's beneath you...
Don't worry, I've worked in
kitchens since I was a child.
I really enjoy doing this, you know.
This area along the Shoukoku border
is most vulnerable to invasion.
This may be a scheduled recon
flight, but don't drop your guard.
Scheduled recon flight, huh?
What's wrong?
When Simoun sibyllae take to the sky...
...she is "praying to the skies."
Controlling a Simoun is
"speaking with a Simoun."
Right, we took off to speak with
our Simouns and pray to the skies.
Isn't that right, Para-sama?
We're to be back at base at noon.
Till then, don't forget to be vigilant.
It's a mouse! A mouse, a mouse!
Where? Where?
No way.
You mean there are mice on board?
Aren't you scared, Aer?
Well, I grew up on a farm,
so there were lots of mice around.
Hey, the same goes
for you. Right, Mamina?
Two o'clock.
So far away.
It's the third time.
They can really get
on your nerves, huh?
Para-sama, let's head back now.
Right, they're too far away to pursue.
It'd be wiser to return
and make our report.
I can't stand living in a room like that.
Why does Dominüra get
her own room? It's definitely fishy.
It was thanks to Dominüra's pleading
that we were able to board this ship.
You really shouldn't say such things.
But...
I'm sick of hearing your
whining and complaining.
Hey, Aer...
Is it true that mice bite people?
If they're hungry.
So they do bite!
Grr!
Welcome back. So?
We spotted far off what we
believed to be enemy planes.
When they noticed us,
they fled immediately.
I see...
I don't like it...
They were so far
we lost them in an instant.
You should report to me.
Oh, the acting captain is here.
I've explained my position.
Would you like to hear it again, Kaim?
Chor Tempest's regina is Neviril.
Dominüra is the mediator
between our chor and Wauf...
...the patrol ship Messis's captain.
A Chor Tempest comrade.
Paraietta,
make your report to Dominüra.
All right.
Everybody! Lunch is ready!
I heard Mamina made it!
You seem sad, Guragief.
Yes...
To tell you the truth,
I'm feeling very sad.
However, Anubituf, I was sure
that you'd be feeling the same way...
I suppose I am...
Chor Tempest,
those glorious Simoun sibyllae.
But we're the ones
who took away that glory.
No matter what it takes, I'll save them.
And I shall do everything in my
power to summon them back here.
However...
Is it really in their best interests to be
called back to the Arcus Prima?
Even I can't answer that...
Thanks for the meal!
Go ahead!
Looks delicious!
Smells great.
I'm impressed.
Me too.
It's making me all warm inside!
It's delicious.
It tastes great.
There's still plenty,
so you can have seconds.
Okay!
Mamina, aren't you eating too?
Yes, I will.
U-Um...
What is it?
What happened the other day... I...
Let's pretend the whole thing never
happened. Is that clear, Mamina?
Yes...
Hey, hey,
what are you talking about?
Oh, you're so mean.
You could at least tell us, Mamina.
Neviril!
Don't ask me.
Can I sit here?
What?
Listen, Mamina...
I'd like to talk to you
after lunch if you don't mind...
All right.
The new sibylla made this?
Yeah, it's pretty good.
Mamina?
You're pretty late for someone
who called me here, Roatreamon.
I'm sorry. I got lost...
On a puny boat like this?
Oh, never mind.
What did you want to discuss?
So what is it?
If you don't say anything...
I...
Come now, Mamina.
It's not that I didn't
have any feelings for you.
How can I patch things up?
Patch things up? That sounds
like we were actually friends before.
Till the end, one of us will always
be above and the other below.
That's not true.
Anyway, just what were
you thinking that day?
That I wanted to be friends...
Don't joke.
And I feel the same way even now.
This conversation is over.
I was always envious
of those braids of yours.
But these are...
You plait your hair because
your parents told you to.
But those things don't mean
a thing to a child. To me...
...they were a rich girl's hairstyle.
That's not true...
Chor Tempest is the chor all Simoun
sibyllae worship and take pride in...
...the finest chor of all.
On behalf of all Simoun sibyllae...
...I beg you to consider
preserving Chor Tempest.
Do you mean
Chor Tempest as sibyllae?
Or Chor Tempest as
a squadron of warriors?
You say you want us to preserve
Chor Tempest, but which one?
Twelve sibyllae...
...who become each other's pairs
and draw Ri Majons across the sky.
There is only one Chor Tempest.
You were there that day
as well, weren't you?
Yes, I heard everything that
went on during that hearing.
Thanks to Vura and Onasia, Chor
Tempest was saved from disbanding.
It was also due to your
brilliant speech, Neviril.
I am not looking to blame
anyone for this war we're waging.
No matter how tragic and painful it
is now, I believe it was meant to be.
Whether or not that is
Tempus Spatium's will...
...it makes no difference to me now.
I no longer even care whether
it's God's will anymore.
However, I do have
one question for you all.
Despite all this, can I still
call myself a Simoun sibylla?
So you overheard that.
Neviril, I'd like you to select
the next sibyllae to go on patrol.
All right, next will be two pairs,
you and Rimone, Alty and Floe.
Very well.
Dominüra.
The truth is you're the one
who saved Chor Tempest.
You negotiated with the council
to keep us, provided we be sent...
...to the front lines
on this ship, didn't you?
Thank you.
Chor Tempest is the greatest
chor in Simulacrum Kyuukoku.
There is no doubt about that.
Still, how can you do such things?
Wow...
That's pretty neat.
It's a keepsake from my grandpa.
Paraietta, are you here?
What's going on, Neviril?
Something's been bothering me.
I'd like you to tell me the enemy's
behavior in this morning's patrol again.
Fine... But what for?
If I recall, you sighted distant traces
of the enemy several times...
...and they immediately fled.
We encountered them
three times to be precise.
What are you getting at, Neviril?
I wonder if you four
really saw them first.
Then they spotted us first and
revealed themselves on purpose?
Most likely. Paraietta, we must hurry.
I'll notify the captain.
The rest of you,
hurry to the flight deck.
Forgive me, Neviril.
It never occurred to me.
Your scouting flight
path has been tracked.
Dominüra and the others are being
ambushed. We're at the border.
We're at the front lines
of the enemy's assault.
Mamina and
Roatreamon aren't here yet.
All right.
I'm the auriga.
Kaim, please pair with me.
Right!
Yun, you're my sagitta.
Right.
Get a move on, Morinas.
Waporif.
I'll send Mamina and Roatreamon
as soon as they arrive.
What will you do,
Sibylla Roatreamon, Sibylla Mamina?
The others have already left.
Mamina, let's hurry.
No! I'm not going to pair
with you! Didn't I tell you before?
Over my dead body.
It's never going to happen.
W-What are you doing?
W-What... What do you
think you're doing, Roatre?
You called me that
when we were little too.
Sibylla Roatreamon...
Everyone's in danger...
They could all die...
This is no time for us
to be hesitating, Mamina!
Let's go, Roatre.
Yes, Mamina.
Emergency positions!
Yes, sir!
You're still sniveling?
We're on our way to meet the others.
That's not it... That's not it.
It's just that I've always,
always worn braids...
There they are!
Now's our chance!
We can take on that many.
The Iron Ri Majon!
That meat...
It was delicious.
It was the mice.
It is played by my wounds...
the song of prayer.
Let it ring out over
the grieving universe.
Can we change tomorrow?
Don't be afraid.
I want to let you know
how my heart's overflowing.
"I want to get closer to you."
"I want to feel your pulse."
I was too defiant,
and I took the long way around.
The blue moon is swaying silently.
My true heart's desire is you.
I can't reach you.
My tears of pain trickle down.
Soar away into the sky, song of prayer.
Carrying my love that came too late.
What can I do to change tomorrow?
Just hold on to "now" the way it is...
To Be Continued
It's our job as sibyllae
to take the soldiers near that town.
Next time on Simoun...
United Front
United Front.