The countless flowers,
enveloped in light...
...gaze at tomorrow
with unwavering eyes.
Everyone wishes for me to be pure...
...but what can I bring
with me to the frayed skies?
What I've made my own
by breaking off flowers in bloom...
All such sinful things...
Why did I stop making
promises with the future?
Because even if I try
to run far from all the pain...
...a cold wind rustles
my hair... Don't you see?
Where can I ever find the answer?
I am Wauf, the captain of the Messis.
The highland aerial base, found on
a Chor Tempest scouting flight...
...has since vanished without a trace.
Four of Chor Tempest's Simouns
have already left the ship.
The sharp surge in enemy attacks
the last 12 hours is worrisome.
The Messis has been left with
only two Simouns on board.
I'm getting a bad feeling...
Captain!
Everyone's in position.
The kitchen staff
can be relieved for now.
Yes, sir!
The Emerald Ri Majon
I'm going to do it for you.
The Emerald Ri Majon.
He sure does have
a screwed-up face.
You think he takes after his owner?
Roatreamon?
Or maybe the one who made him.
How can you laugh?
We're in trouble!
A-Aircraft sighted!
Um... Um...
Nine o'clock! A fleet of planes!
Non-Simoun!
Nine o'clock!
A fleet of planes! Non-Simoun!
We should assume
they've spotted us.
Six o'clock! A fleet of planes!
Take us down lower!
Any lower and we'll hit trees.
It doesn't matter! Mow them down!
Find a hiding place for this ship!
There's a hill at one o'clock.
Turn us around at full speed!
Prepare to land!
We can fight with two Simouns,
but it's over if the Messis falls!
Baby birds who've lost their mother
are doomed to starve to death.
Don't say things like that.
You'll frighten the child.
I'm not...
Rimone's not scared at all, see?
Come on. Let's go too.
Sibylla Dominüra...
The Simouns are the vehicles
of the gods... They can't fall.
What should we do, Dominüra?
Pursue the enemy?
No.
The priority now is
to protect the Messis.
We'll flank and keep
its launch position undetected.
Good idea. We'll attack by land,
using it as a smokescreen.
Roger.
You know what, Aer?
Rimone?
I kind of brought Roatreamon's
stuffed animal with me.
Drop anchor!
Now dropping anchor!
Captain, I believe we're
going to get away with this.
Looks like it.
So we pulled the wool
over their eyes after all, eh?
It seems they're gone. Aer...
Not yet.
They made it look like they'd gone,
but they were keeping an eye out.
Should we head back now?
Hey...
I have no idea how to survive here.
Having honed our war skills
isn't anything to brag about.
War skills, did you say?
That's right. It's my war skills...
Techniques for survival...
I've got to learn more about them.
It's quiet here, isn't it?
Dominüra?
You said you'd do it for me, right?
The Emerald Ri Majon...
I never intended to put
such a burden on you.
It's just that unless I know
I'm doing it for someone...
...the way I am right now,
I have no chance of moving forward.
I don't understand...
I do understand
how you feel, Dominüra.
But I don't understand
why I understand.
Because you're my pair... That's why.
We should've realized it sooner.
So you're saying
the others were lured away?
Yes.
They've splintered Chor Tempest...
...forcing it
to disperse its combat power.
It's going to be all right, Rimone.
They still haven't
pinpointed our exact location.
Sibylla Dominüra...
I'm sure you're
as aware of this as I am.
The sun will rise soon.
Once the enemy attacks again,
there'll be no escaping detection.
In that case, what kind
of choices do we have?
One would be to wait for
the four Simouns' return...
...and sit tight until we can launch
a counterattack against the enemy.
The other would be...
...to make our escape from
this airspace as soon as possible.
Then what will become
of Neviril and the others?
Well...
This is your opinion, is it not?
As things stand, the survival rate for
the Simouns that have yet to return...
...is extremely low.
How can you utter
such groundless rubbish?
Chor Tempest is Kyuukoku's
finest chor! We can't fall!
You're absolutely right.
They're all coming back for sure.
So try to calm down.
Paraietta!
I'll search for the Simouns.
What about the Messis?
The captain's view about Shoukoku's
new aircraft attacking again...
...isn't guaranteed!
Your behavior is quite violent.
Rimone.
I want you to come with me.
You and I...
Rimone is my pair.
Dominüra!
And I am Rimone's pair.
Why are you doing this?
What's going on with you? All of you!
How can you stay so calm?
When your own
comrades are in peril?
I could never bring myself
to abandon my comrades!
You don't mean comrades.
You mean Neviril, don't you?
Since when is Neviril your underling?
My underling?
Sibylla Aurea is
Chor Tempest's highest sibylla.
Thinking someone
like you can protect her...
...is gross arrogance.
Fine.
I'll go with you.
Rimone, you and I will go with them.
But give me a little time
before we leave. I won't be long.
Besides, in the state
you're in right now...
...you can't activate the Simoun
with Aer, can you, Paraietta?
Sibylla Dominüra!
I see someone else got here first.
Without something to believe in...
...none of us can even
plant our feet on the earth.
In my case, that was Kyuukoku,
as well as Tempus Spatium.
What are you...
The Simouns taught me something...
Something I never wanted to know.
Please tell me...
What was it that you...
What on earth did you...
Forget about that day, Waporif.
But...
That's the last warning
I'll be giving you.
As we thought.
What is it?
Planes sighted at eight o'clock!
They got here sooner than I thought.
We probably don't have time to run.
The Messis will remain moored
here and attempt a counterattack!
Let's go, Aer.
You all right?
I want you, Aer.
Because unless you come
with me, I can't save Neviril.
Sibylla Dominüra...
Please be safe.
You too.
Rimone?
I forgot to give it back!
Do you see that?
They're flying so high!
They're practically Simouns!
Dominüra! Rimone!
Aer, let's go! The Falcon Ri Majon!
Aer! The Falcon
Ri Majon one more time.
Right! As many times as it takes!
Rimone, which Ri Majon can we do
that has the most destructive power?
The Wave Crest Ri Majon!
Rimone! One more time!
Wave Crest Ri Majon!
But why?
How?
They've made huge technological
advances in such a short time.
They haven't reached the Simouns'
level yet, but such great numbers...
The Fish Silhouette Ri Majon!
It's no good! We can't do
Ri Majons with all this interference!
The Messis!
The Emerald Ri Majon...
Has the time come for us to do it?
But I don't know...
Afraid?
No, not me. But...
You're afraid, aren't you, Dominüra?
Who ever thought you'd
understand me to that degree?
What I saw that day...
It was a terrifying sight.
It destroyed every last shred of my
pride and shattered all I believed in.
But that's not what I'm afraid of.
Beyond that terrible sight,
I caught a glimpse of something.
That's what I'm afraid of.
What was it?
I can't describe it in words.
But if I had to give it a name...
I'd call it hope.
For the Messis...
They're fighting so
that we might be saved.
They're fighting for us!
Captain!
Don't let the sibyllae's
prayers be in vain!
We'll draw the enemy's attention
so the priestesses can escape!
Yes, sir!
What the?
Madness! Are they trying to die?
Are they doing it for us?
Yes, I'm sure they are.
Prepare the cannons!
Dominüra...
Yes.
I want to!
No matter what may lie ahead?
The Emerald Ri Majon.
I guess we lost sight of them, huh?
I suppose.
What is this? This feeling?
It feels so familiar
yet so relentlessly cold.
Neviril!
Over there... Look.
That's...
The Emerald Ri Majon!
What's going on?
Stop it, Dominüra! Rimone!
You've got to stop!
That's the Emerald...
But why?
Hold up, who's doing
the Emerald Ri Majon?
I never thought
we'd ever see it again...
We're heading right back!
You're sure? That's...
No! They'll be killed!
Stop it... please...
Stop it!
Rimone...
Dominüra?
I'm not afraid.
Right, I'm not afraid either.
We're together.
Together...
Forever and ever.
Yes, forever and ever.
Nothing's changed.
Wait. Where did
Dominüra and Rimone go?
They're gone.
They don't give up.
Neviril...
Captain! It's the Simouns!
Thank goodness! They're all safe!
Sibylla Dominüra...
What's this?
What's going on?
Hey!
C-Captain!
Directly overhead...
I-It's the Arcus Prima!
That was a close shave,
but it seems we're in time.
Sorry to have kept
you waiting, my sibyllae.
Everybody...
I am Wauf, the captain of the Messis.
In the end, we survived.
Thanks to the Arcus Prima and the
return of Chor Tempest's Simouns.
But as for the Simoun flown by Sibylla
Dominüra and Sibylla Rimone...
We never found
even the slightest trace.
It is played by my wounds...
the song of prayer.
Let it ring out over
the grieving universe.
Can we change tomorrow?
Don't be afraid.
I want to let you know
how my heart's overflowing.
"I want to get closer to you."
"I want to feel your pulse."
I was too defiant,
and I took the long way around.
The blue moon is swaying silently.
My true heart's desire is you.
I can't reach you.
My tears of pain trickle down.
Soar away into the sky, song of prayer.
Carrying my love that came too late.
What can I do to change tomorrow?
Just hold on to "now" the way it is...
To Be Continued
Headed for the forbidden land, Chor
Tempest makes a startling discovery.
Next time on Simoun...
The Ruins
The Ruins.