The countless flowers,
enveloped in light...
...gaze at tomorrow
with unwavering eyes.
Everyone wishes for me to be pure...
...but what can I bring
with me to the frayed skies?
What I've made my own
by breaking off flowers in bloom...
All such sinful things...
Why did I stop making
promises with the future?
Because even if I try
to run far from all the pain...
...a cold wind rustles
my hair... Don't you see?
Where can I ever find the answer?
The Nearby War
That wraps up
the patrol flight schedule.
Have you authorized
mobilization of Chor Tempest?
We're still flying?
You said we couldn't gauge
Simoun chemistry otherwise, Morinas.
I've had enough!
You're amazing, Aer.
So can we...
We haven't done a Ri Majon yet.
Let's try the Ray Ri Majon.
Look at Aer go!
Morinas.
It's too complicated! I'm confused!
Morinas, focus.
All right.
Just wait... Wait.
Chor Tempest is currently grounded
until its newest members arrive...
...Sibylla Aer.
If we don't practice,
it'll be tough when trouble comes.
Then use Similes.
After you've received permission.
Aer! Morinas!
Why'd you pray without permission?
It was a battle drill, not a prayer.
Why are you scolding us?
You're not even
the regina of Chor Tempest.
The regina of our chor,
Neviril, is indisposed.
In the meantime, I'm stepping in.
Oh? Don't tell me
that you and Sibylla Aurea...
...have that kind of special relationship.
Aer! You forgot something!
The kiss of gratitude. After exiting
the Simoun, Tempus Spatium...
I couldn't care less about that.
Do you hate doing it with me?
Waporif, I'm sorry. We might've
gotten you in trouble too.
It's our job to launch
Simouns when sibyllae request it.
How cold.
She's a child. You needn't tease her.
Tease? Why would I?
But you know what? Flying with
that girl was simply wonderful.
Aer.
That was amazing, Aer.
Which Ri Majon
were you trying before?
Aer, don't do anything like that again.
Why not? Are you all okay
with the way things are?
When will they put Chor Tempest
on duty to relieve the other chors?
At this rate...
If that happens, we can go back
to being normal Simoun sibyllae.
Offering prayers and waiting
for our time to go to the Spring.
The day I choose to become male.
I can hardly wait, Big Sister.
I'm planning to choose
the male gender myself, Alty.
You all think so?
That it's fine to not
go into battle anymore?
It's Chor Rubor.
Making a safe return
again today, I hope.
You tried to do
the Ray Ri Majon, right?
You are a genius after all.
You can't even do
a simple thing like that...
I wonder if this really
is Chor Tempest?
Is that how you feel too, Neviril?
That it doesn't matter as long
as you don't go into battle anymore?
How could anyone want to go to war?
Aer, we are merely...
...fulfilling our duties as priestesses
protecting Tempus Spatium.
Then you fulfill that duty too!
Let me make myself clear.
Aer, you and I will never be a pair.
I'm Vura of Chor Rubor.
We'll be roommates starting today.
Is that right? I'm Aer of Chor Tempest.
You're an auriga, right?
I am too.
Say, has that Neviril always been...
Since Chor Tempest is off active duty,
my chor's been split into two units...
...doing patrol flights night and day.
We don't have the luxury
of lazing around like you people.
Let me sleep.
I bet I can fly in a way
that would satisfy even you.
Perhaps.
Then come with me.
Everyone's in
the cafeteria at this hour.
But...
It's all right. I grabbed dinner for us.
That's not it...
What a pain in the butt...
Um...
Here, your half.
Also...
Let's go.
Which Ri Majon first?
Which do you like?
I don't know...
You must like one.
The Silver Ri Majon... I guess.
Yeah? That's a good one.
But if we're going to,
let's do it when we find the enemy.
You're going into battle?
If we do, they won't be able
to ground our chor anymore.
Isn't that right?
You think so?
Aer...
Is that...
It's a Simoun.
The new recruits in Chor Caput
are out on patrol tonight, right?
Why's it there?
Maybe they were attacked.
Then they've got info on the enemy.
Let's make sure the area's secure first.
Just one unit.
I'm in luck. This will be my last...
It has to be Aer!
And with Rimone this time!
Rimone? But that's my pair...
She rejected me too.
It's not really
a matter of being rejected...
Another unauthorized flight?
I wish my chor had free time.
This means the end of
Chor Tempest. We're going to be busy.
Should we notify the dux?
If we don't get them,
we're all accountable.
Why don't we leave them alone?
If they want to fly,
we should let them fly.
They'll be back by morning.
We can't move
the Arcus Prima right now.
Just what kind of
priestess is this Aer girl?
All that is certain...
...is that she has a reason.
A reason for being here.
It's a fake...
Rimone!
Aer!
Damn you...
That's right.
We're both Simoun sibyllae.
So it's true when they say that young
girls fly the Simouns in Kyuukoku.
The disease is eating
away at our bodies.
We are in need of new technology.
The secret of Simouns,
hidden by Kyuukoku.
If we can acquire that...
...we can bid farewell to
technology that pollutes the skies.
I did it... I've taken a Simoun...
I'm not going to retire from the military!
Glory to Shoukoku!
It's useless!
You soldiers from Shoukoku aren't
protected by Tempus Spatium!
Only priestesses who haven't gone
to the Spring can operate Simouns!
Only us, people who haven't
decided on a gender yet!
Tell me how to fly it!
Tell me!
Aer, what do we do?
We retake the Simoun.
Don't talk so loud!
He can't understand our words anyway.
Shoukoku wants the Simouns.
Since only Simouns fly freely through
the skies. But we can't hand it over.
Aer...
All of my friends
have gone to the Spring.
I'm the only one
in my village who hasn't.
Why don't you want to go, Aer?
Because I'm not sure. Whether I want
to become a man or stay a woman.
If you go, they say Onasia
chooses if you haven't decided.
Having someone else choose
is worse! No, I don't want that!
I can't afford to make
mistakes in a place like this.
I'll become the best
Simoun sibylla of all.
After all, as long as I fly a Simoun,
I won't have to go to the Spring.
Tell me, young ladies...
How does it feel?
Not to be a man or woman?
You don't understand, do you?
I was turned male via medicine
and surgery right when I was born.
That's the way things
are done in Shoukoku.
That's why I have no idea.
Being born in a female body...
...and then being able to choose
whether to become a man or woman.
How does that feel?
Do you think that man is ill?
Go! Fly!
Come on, fly! What's wrong, demon?
Why won't you fly?
Sorry, young ladies.
I can't hand this over
to you. It's mine now.
If I can just take this back,
my country will usher in a new era.
The skies will clear...
No matter what, I'm going to...
Like I said, you can't fly a Simoun.
His comrades might come for him.
In Shoukoku aircraft...
I won't let him have it.
He'll never take the Simoun.
Help me get him down.
We need to get back right away.
He's all stiff.
Let go! Let go! Let go, will you?
Don't. It'll break.
I'm sure someone
will come looking for us...
Then we can...
No.
We don't know when the enemy will
come. We have to take off right away.
And we can't ever report that we
nearly got captured by the enemy.
If only these hands on
the flight stick could be removed...
It can't be helped...
It can't be helped.
Rimone, you can
go over there till I'm done.
Hurry! Go over there!
Ow...
Rimone!
Rimone! Help me carry him, Rimone!
Are you awake, Rimone?
Rimone!
I guess I made trouble for you again.
As an apology,
we'll clean it ourselves.
You don't have to do that, Sibylla Aer.
It's fine. We want to.
Rimone, if you please.
Taking on the task of
cleaning the Simoun themselves?
They're starting to recognize
that they're priestesses.
You think so?
I'm sorry.
For getting you so dirty.
It is played by my wounds...
the song of prayer.
Let it ring out over
the grieving universe.
Can we change tomorrow?
Don't be afraid.
I want to let you know
how my heart's overflowing.
"I want to get closer to you."
"I want to feel your pulse."
I was too defiant,
and I took the long way around.
The blue moon is swaying silently.
My true heart's desire is you.
I can't reach you.
My tears of pain trickle down.
Soar away into the sky, song of prayer.
Carrying my love that came too late.
What can I do to change tomorrow?
Just hold on to "now" the way it is...
To Be Continued
Will Dominüra be up
to the task of guiding Rimone?
Next time on Simoun...
White Loneliness
White Loneliness.