The countless flowers,
enveloped in light...
...gaze at tomorrow
with unwavering eyes.
Everyone wishes for me to be pure...
...but what can I bring
with me to the frayed skies?
What I've made my own
by breaking off flowers in bloom...
All such sinful things...
Why did I stop making
promises with the future?
Because even if I try
to run far from all the pain...
...a cold wind rustles
my hair... Don't you see?
Where can I ever find the answer?
I could've sworn it was
somewhere around here...
Right, Neviril?
Around this area, our nation...
...shares a border not only with
Shoukoku but also with the highlands.
Perhaps the spot where Shoukoku's
aerial base was found the other day...
...was within the highland border.
How would you interpret that in the
clearest and most pessimistic terms?
I'd have to say the highlands and
Shoukoku have formed an alliance...
What is the center doing?
Nothing.
For the next few days, the Messis...
...will dry-dock and undergo
maintenance for our return trip.
I know that times are grim...
...but I hope you sibyllae
will enjoy the time off.
There's been far
too much tragedy lately.
Yes... And most likely,
more lies ahead.
Sacrosanct
Oh, someone was here.
Sibylla Morinas...
I'll leave right away.
Don't worry about it. I'm going
to be a man myself after all.
Still, that really blew me away.
Who knew the Simoun gem
gauged people's emotions?
It shows you that we understand
nothing about the Simouns even now.
It does look that way.
You said so yourself, remember?
That first day we met...
Oh, sorry.
I just remembered, you see...
S-Something
tells me this isn't good...
Well, you said this before.
That years ago, you and Floe...
Actually, Floe and I used to be in love.
I-In love?
To tell the truth, I didn't think
you made a very good couple...
Oh, are you mad?
If I tell you something now, will you
keep it between the two of us?
It's true I did harbor what could
be called affection for Sibylla Floe.
However...
Since she was
a sacred sibylla, I just couldn't...
Take it to the next level.
That's right.
No matter how
aggressively she pursued?
That's right. The thing is...
Listen, Waporif.
You and I were lovers.
If anyone asks, that's how
you'll answer. Understand?
Don't worry. I won't tell anybody.
But a story this funny...
I wonder if I can hold out?
Sibylla Morinas!
Anyway... I don't know
about the "sacred" part.
Can we really be that big of a deal?
You feel that way because you have
yet to truly understand who you are.
I wonder if that's all there is to it?
Is that thing really gonna work?
Be patient. Be patient.
I've seen it in a book.
Well, even so...
Here's one!
Mamina, that's awesome!
Hey, Para-sama, it's amazing!
Come over here and see!
Sure.
I guess Kaim's back
to calling her "Para-sama."
What a lovely sound...
The laughter of young girls.
Captain, were we
really like that once?
Well, I have a feeling that
we must have been once...
But wait, were we really?
You called for me, Sibylla Dominüra?
First, let us pray.
I need something done in secret,
and I can ask no one but you.
The Simouns must
never be violated...
...as they are the holy
vessels of gods, correct?
Yes.
And this divine vessel has fallen.
Why?
You should already know
the answer to that question.
If you can't bring
yourself to say it, allow me.
Because the Simouns
are machines, nothing more.
The Simoun gems,
which gauge our souls...
The helical motors...
Granted, some mysteries remain.
Nevertheless, the truth
is just as you described.
The Simouns' undeniable superiority
over other nations has now been lost.
In the not-so-distant future,
the military dynamic between...
...Simulacrum Kyuukoku and our
neighboring countries will be reversed.
Dismantle a Simoun.
You're the one who said
they were nothing but machines.
With all due respect,
Sibylla Dominüra...
...that is something
we've all been long aware of.
But people have looked
upon these "mere machines"...
...as something divine and
sacrosanct, with love and respect.
And why do you think that is?
Because all we have are the Simouns.
All we have are the Simouns.
And to desecrate a Simoun
is something I simply cannot do.
You know it as well as I do.
If we can unlock all
of the Simouns' secrets...
...our country,
Kyuukoku, will be saved.
Something's not right.
After all this searching,
how come we haven't found it yet?
Why?
They could've moved the base
because we found them.
Let's head back.
Hold on. If I'm right,
we've got to check...
Turn back!
So you're not even
going to ask my opinion.
It's just the two of us.
We can't bring it to a vote.
You don't think we could ever
have the same opinion, Neviril?
I'd never before seen
a cockpit mangled so badly...
...until that day.
I could imagine the sheer shock
and pressure sustained in that blast.
And then... when I had taken apart
the twisted wreck of the cockpit...
...I didn't find Sibylla Amuria inside.
But judging how
the cockpit had been mangled...
...it's not plausible that
she'd been thrown out.
In that case,
where did Sibylla Amuria go?
Have you made up your mind?
I thought I had refused.
We're running out of time.
Our neighboring countries are allying.
That aerial base is one good example.
Without us knowing a thing...
"Us"? Who do you
mean by "us," Sibylla Dominüra?
Just who are you?
What did Dominüra want?
Oh, she said
Rimone's Simoun is malfunctioning.
You're not...
...a very good liar now, are you?
I guess you're right.
Yun...
If Neviril...
Rather, if anything happens,
I want to take off at once.
When the time comes,
I want you to be my pair.
The sum of one person's soul
is equal to everyone else's.
Should you overestimate its value,
the decisions will be flawed.
Of course, if our comrades
find themselves in danger...
...it's a given that
I would take off at once.
The Simouns are activated
by its two helical motors.
Well, to be precise, you could
say they're being manipulated.
And beyond that fact,
we know nothing about the Simouns.
Waporif, don't tell me that...
You said it once yourself.
That I should dismantle a Simoun.
After flying a Simoun...
sensing that Simoun...
...I did learn something.
That they are divine vehicles.
That they're sacred...
Just like the sibyllae themselves,
the Simouns are sacrosanct.
However...
I might be about to desecrate
that which is sacred.
They didn't get back tonight.
It's just a reconnaissance mission.
You don't have to worry.
Aer...
Do you think she's still
planning to do an Emerald Ri Majon?
They say things work out
if you're in love. If you love your pair...
...it makes your
Ri Majons turn out right.
H-Hold on. That's what I told Aer.
Is that right, Floe? Have you
really ever experienced true love?
True love?
Hey, don't insult me!
I'm always in true love...
Would you be quiet?
I'm sure you think
I'm out of my element here.
But I promise it's a fine cup of tea.
What did you want to talk about?
Sibylla Dominüra,
you must forgive me.
I've looked into your background a bit.
The only remaining survivor
of the fabled Chor Dextra.
Chor Dextra...
Today, its very existence has
been erased from the records...
...formed for the sole purpose of
completing the Emerald Ri Majon.
A phantom chor.
The Emerald Ri Majon failed...
...and the rest of
the sibyllae lost their lives.
And now you're a sibylla under
the military council's direct command.
An appointment that even those
high priestesses had no say in.
Yes, that's right.
You invited me to tea to discuss that?
No, to inform you that the plans
you're about to execute...
...are being watched
silently by certain people.
No matter what one intends,
in order to see it through...
...we must all have something
to believe in wholeheartedly.
Believe in...
Something worth believing in...
That would be...
The Simouns.
Whether their
mystique is valid or not...
...doesn't matter.
The Simouns
are machines, nothing more...
They are not
divine vessels by any means.
So it's done.
Yes.
But I found nothing inside.
At least, not anything
we'd be able to comprehend.
What's there is nothing but a helix.
The only thing we're
capable of understanding is...
Sibylla Dominüra...
It can't be...
You can...
You're able to see
something, aren't you?
You can see something!
What can you see?
Sibylla Dominüra!
That voice just now...
Dominüra...
Let's go see what happened.
She's on the flight deck!
Take Sibylla Dominüra to my room.
Yes, sir.
What happened? Is Dominüra...
She's all right!
Sibyllae, if you please...
Sibyllae, if you would
please step aside...
Huh? I just heard...
...somebody crying.
It is played by my wounds...
the song of prayer.
Let it ring out over
the grieving universe.
Can we change tomorrow?
Don't be afraid.
I want to let you know
how my heart's overflowing.
"I want to get closer to you."
"I want to feel your pulse."
I was too defiant,
and I took the long way around.
The blue moon is swaying silently.
My true heart's desire is you.
I can't reach you.
My tears of pain trickle down.
Soar away into the sky, song of prayer.
Carrying my love that came too late.
What can I do to change tomorrow?
Just hold on to "now" the way it is...
To Be Continued
Shoukoku's upgraded aircraft...
...are relentlessly threatening us,
and our forces are being scattered.
Next time on Simoun...
One, and Then Another
One, and Then Another.