The countless flowers,
enveloped in light...
...gaze at tomorrow
with unwavering eyes.
Everyone wishes for me to be pure...
...but what can I bring
with me to the frayed skies?
What I've made my own
by breaking off flowers in bloom...
All such sinful things...
Why did I stop making
promises with the future?
Because even if I try
to run far from all the pain...
...a cold wind rustles
my hair... Don't you see?
Where can I ever find the answer?
Hold on!
Big Sister...
I'm Para-sama's pair! You can't
just tell me to team up with Alty now.
Regarding Paraietta,
you can easily be replaced.
But no one can take
your place as sisters.
The Ri Majon you inscribe will show
some interesting results, I'm sure.
Sisters?
This is all for the sake of restoring
Chor Tempest to its former prestige.
We simply can't
afford another fiasco.
Sisters
Yun!
I can't believe you're pushing away
such tiny bits of onion like that!
Leave me alone.
Yun, I didn't know
you could be so cute!
So it really wasn't
such a big deal, huh?
Saying how in love you were, but
that's how much you care in the end.
Mastiff! You're so sweet!
Killing other people...
Kaim.
What? Don't lash out just because
your beloved Para-sama dumped you.
Wha...
Stop it right now!
Big Sister...
Oh, they're finally back to normal now.
Really... Putting up with
such barbarous treatment...
I'm proud of you!
Morinas, I can't let you get away
with using the word "barbarous."
Hey... That's unusual.
Floe...
Sorry.
My sister didn't mean to hurt you.
It's just that...
It's all right.
Because she's right
about how much I care.
I felt... like I was going
to burst inside, see...
I thought my heart
was just going to stop...
And yet...
It didn't stop.
But the thing is...
I just don't want to ever
forget about that night.
That's how I feel.
Not to forget... about that night...
Big Sister...
Come on, Floe. Left more.
Why's this boat leaking like this?
I'm sure the Messis is quite pleased
having Simoun sibyllae help out.
Unbelievable. I don't see how it flies.
My apologies.
Where's Kaim?
Still sulking.
She really is a pain in the butt.
There you are.
Kaim, about tomorrow's test flight...
They've decided to send Aer
and myself to accompany you.
Don't you even care, Para-sama?
That I'm not your pair anymore?
Calm down, Kaim.
Don't look at me like that!
I'm sorry.
It's not your fault.
Kaim...
But it's not my fault either!
Kaim!
She seems so upset.
Maybe I should've
at least accompanied her.
It wouldn't do any good for you to go.
Man, you busted it!
Freezing! Jeez, we got rid of the rusty
water, and now there's no hot water?
What a bummer.
Isn't that water cold?
It won't wash off.
I scrub and scrub...
But no matter how much...
...it just won't wash off.
Let's get some sleep now.
Rimone, aren't you scared?
You can come over to my bed.
I'm okay.
You don't have to be brave.
After all, you're still little...
The truth is you're
the one who's scared.
T-That's not true...
Proof that an eternal world exists...
...shall be revealed
by Tempus Spatium.
Rocking gently
until we awake tomorrow...
...protected by our mother.
What's the matter?
Nothing.
This is the first time, isn't it?
That we've flown together.
It's called "praying to the skies."
Big Sister... How did
we ever come to this?
We used to always do things together.
It was that night...
Shut up!
Aer, after them!
Aer, the communication cable!
Right.
Neviril, look!
What's happening?
Kaim! Alty!
Why? Why aren't their prayers
being heard by the Simoun gem?
They're in the clouds...
I won't lose them.
Big Sister!
Don't call me that!
I said stop calling me that!
I was right after all.
You were to blame after all.
Alty... It's all your fault.
That's right... It was all...
It was all because of you!
What could that be?
Wow... it's as
dilapidated as the Messis.
Still, what the heck is it?
It's Shoukoku's aerial base.
But who would've thought
a base this size even existed?
They don't seem to have spotted us,
even though we're so close.
Shall we explore?
No, it's risky. With the other Simoun's
oddness, let's return to the Messis...
It was useless from the start. Even
Dominüra should be able to see that.
We may be sisters, but still...
I'm going.
Alty?
I'll show Dominüra that it's
not impossible for us to be a team.
Leave it to me.
Aer and Kaim will wait in the Simouns.
We'll approach at a slow
pace and then move in.
If something happens...
It looks deserted.
You're right.
What's that?
A broken searchlight...
A base left unguarded...
So we're suffering at the hands
of people like this, aren't we?
Yes.
How can they even confront
our divine vessels in battle?
Maybe it's not a matter
of who's more powerful...
Do you think they're not afraid to die?
I don't think there's
anyone who isn't afraid to die.
Then they must be strong.
I'm envious.
Alty...
There's no need to be
the strong one all on your own.
It's all Alty's fault. That girl's always...
...always getting in my way.
But why?
Why does she always...
What happened
between you and Alty?
You two have this really weird vibe...
Even though you're sisters.
It's because we are sisters.
That night...
That night, I was feeling vulnerable.
I'd be going into my
first battle in the morning.
And I was scared. I wanted
to scream. I wanted to run away.
At that moment...
She took advantage of me.
I couldn't say no to her.
When Alty seduced me...
I don't really get it.
I don't blame you.
For sisters, it's an abominable sin.
That's not what I'm talking about.
Is it really a matter of who
was right and who was wrong?
But of course...
I can't tell from just hearing this.
Maybe you really did the seducing.
Seduced her? Me?
I seduced her? That's not possible.
I couldn't have...
Kaim?
I've got to make sure.
I've got to bring Alty back.
Hold on, Kaim!
Kaim!
When we were little,
I was always a little crybaby...
And whenever I cried...
...Big Sister would
always hold me close.
And I became stronger.
What I'd like to go back to isn't that
night but a warm, cozy afternoon.
What I want isn't the hand that
taught me sensations I'd never known.
It's the gentle hand that
held mine as we walked.
But... Big Sister...
I want to become a man someday...
So that next time,
I can hold her close.
To hold Big Sister tight...
Big Sister!
Big Sister! Jump!
Big Sister, what's the matter?
You don't have to worry!
Because I'll catch you
and hold you close!
Big Sister!
It's not my fault...
Kaim, as soon as we land,
act as Aer's sagitta.
Kaim! Got it?
Yes.
The Simoun gem was
unaffected by their prayers?
I see... Have you ever heard
of that happening before?
No, never.
As for Shoukoku's aerial base,
we can't very well ignore it.
Apparently there's a new
class of aircraft on that base.
To become strong by being held...
You're wrong about that, Alty.
It's only when you've
both become strong...
...that you can truly
hold each other close.
Aer, is my sister all right?
It was just a scrape.
Thanks.
Hey, you never got
to hold Amuria close, did you?
Don't worry. It'll happen with us.
The person you're
looking at right now...
...is someone who will never
grow old, and it's you yourself.
It's not me.
The same taste.
It is played by my wounds...
the song of prayer.
Let it ring out over
the grieving universe.
Can we change tomorrow?
Don't be afraid.
I want to let you know
how my heart's overflowing.
"I want to get closer to you."
"I want to feel your pulse."
I was too defiant,
and I took the long way around.
The blue moon is swaying silently.
My true heart's desire is you.
I can't reach you.
My tears of pain trickle down.
Soar away into the sky, song of prayer.
Carrying my love that came too late.
What can I do to change tomorrow?
Just hold on to "now" the way it is...
To Be Continued
Neviril screams, losing her
head over something Aer says.
Next time on Simoun...
Reason
Reason.