Junji and Asako's
Know-Your-Simoun Lecture
So anyway,
I'm Junji Nishimura. Nice to meet you.
I'm the character designer,
animation supervisor...
...and light comic
relief director, Asako Nishida.
Um, and I'm the director.
Let's see, episode one...
Well, I have to say that
episode one was all about quantity...
So that's what we
focused on... Sheer quantity.
Of enemies?
So what did you think
of the amount? Excessive?
I don't think so.
But you know how this scene
comes up in that clogged airspace?
Did you start this project
to shoot this scene?
Yes, I suppose you could say that.
Many people pointed out this would
never happen at such a moment.
Comments like "I'm sure
they had better things to do."
But I still wanted to do it.
And your reasons?
Well, you see...
When we were discussing how
realistic the story should be...
...I said this was what I wanted in
episode one, what I wanted to show.
The bizarre worldview, realistic
but at the same time contrived...
I wanted to do everything
I could in episode one.
But as far as the plot line went...
...I didn't want it
to follow a dramatic formula.
I wanted an "audience vs. me" feeling
and to remain conscious of that.
That was my plan for episode one.
So it seems the story got even more
confusing since little was explained.
But I thought that should be an aspect
of the overall Simoun worldview.
That's what I set out to do.
And this is how it turned out.
And I ended up getting mixed reviews.
So what did you think of episode one?
Oh, well... Let's see...
A lot of kissing scenes in Simoun
take place midair during battles...
Is that your experience?
Have I ever kissed
someone during an attack?
Was your first kiss a traumatic
experience or something?
No, mine happened
under a pine tree...
Under a pine tree?
So it wasn't like the show.
Proper, on a beautiful
beach, and with a pine tree.
Underthat tree.
Can your wife hearthat?
It'd be bad.
It'd be bad?
See this? This scene here?
This scene is what you'd call the
heart and essence of the entire series.
As a matter of fact.
Did you notice how forced it was
going to that overwhelming red sky?
Yes.
And when we were done
with this draft of episode one...
...we gave it to Katoh for processing,
and we'll talk about him later on...
...and he asked,
"Are you really okay with this?"
He spoke of how the worldview
was real yet dramatically contrived.
How should I put it?
A world depicted in images.
Battle scenes, for instance.
And a significant number of
them were depicted in that style.
Personally, I think it worked out when
I saw the episode one storyboards...
...and I neverthought I'd
see the use of "harmonies"...
We call the pastel
freeze-frame shots "harmonies."
I never thought
I'd see harmonies used.
Oh, really?
When I first watched the episode...
...my personal opinion was that
the harmonies didn't really fit in.
But I can see quite a lot of
motivation behind those shots...
In episode one, those harmonies
appeared at least twice.
Yes.
Why'd you do them?
It was an artistic decision...
that also got mixed reviews.
Why did you do
those mural paintings?
I was flooded with so
many comments about that.
But you see... I couldn't
advance the story without them.
There was no other way to link
the scenes. That's all I can say.
So it was a directorial decision?
I'd have to say yes.
There were people who asked me
if I was an Osamu Dezaki disciple.
Sure, I respect him,
but I'm not a disciple.
Well, let me ask you this.
The art director is Kobayashi-san...
So I was wondering if he was the one
with a real affinity for harmonies.
Well, of course he would
never say he wanted to do them.
Right.
But if I want to do harmonies,
and he does the artwork...
...there's no way we'd end up
without harmonies, you see.
That was yourthought as director?
Because after all, he...
He's a purist who holds on to
the old-school way of doing artwork.
Today, there's so much you
can do with digital processing...
...but he's the type who does all
he can to work in the old style.
And anotherthing... Today, you
never see cel animation anymore...
...but he still has them somehow.
He does?
And he turns in cels that he's drawn.
You wouldn't believe it...
Here we go.
She'll chop them off!
She'll create a huge scene.
We show the corpse in
a series of harmonies here too.
That's right.
You know, I really,
really love this scene.
Was that one
of your creative decisions?
To have her chop up the body?
No, actually... I didn't write this scene.
When the first script was turned in,
it was actually even more graphic.
Do you think it's
all right to describe it now?
Sure, why not.
Long story short...
...she chops off his fingers to remove
them from the steering wheel, right?
Either his fingers or his wrists.
But in the earlier version,
she actually mutilated...
Did she dismember his whole body?
That's right. She dismembers him
and disposes of him piece by piece.
The first draft was brutal.
And I wanted to keep that
quality as much as possible...
...but when I started considering
the Simoun worldview...
...I wasn't sure I could go that
far in terms of repulsive behavior.
It was really
a challenge in that respect.
But it was this scene that
made me see Aer as a young girl.
Oh, I see.
I read in the DVD's liner notes that
most dismemberment homicides...
...are committed by females
to an overwhelming degree.
Is that so?
Because women aren't
strong enough to carry corpses.
So we were on point.
Uh, we were just
talking about corpses...
...and suddenly we're seeing
someone get their nails done.
This is another scene that
didn't follow the original script.
She wasn't doing her nails.
What was it then?
Well, it was much simpler.
She was pouring tea for her.
I think that was how the scene went.
Then the episode director said, "No...
...it won't work unless
there's some touching involved."
Oh, you mean
to transition to the next scene?
He set that up?
Yes, he said that
to set up the next scene...
...we had to show
their hands touching.
But in that version of the script,
this scene... or was it the next?
When they're in
the maintenance hangar...
Going "pow-pow-pow-pow-pow!"
That scene originally happened
in one of the girls' rooms.
And then they fall on top of
one other, getting a little cozy...
That was supposed
to happen on a bed.
Originally.
Well, a bedroom
would've been fine too...
...but personally, I think it's more
appealing under that blue ceiling.
Oh? I'm very sorry about that.
Did you flinch?
Just a little, I think.
Really? Come on,
you've got to follow my lead.
But anyway, this scene really fits in
with the Simoun worldview, right?
Yes. It's pretty symbolic, isn't it?
What happens next when Kaim...
Seeing whether Paraietta sees
Kaim or not was really interesting.
You mean Alty?
Oh, sorry. Not Kaim, I mean Alty.
At this point, Alty is watching
all this unfold behind the curtain...
Right, it's a given she's watching.
But how about the other way around?
Is that why Paraietta stopped?
Didn't you theorize she held back
since she saw Alty watching?
Theorize...
I think you're pretty much on the nose.
l-Is that your official approval?
This is just so
well made, this scene...
But yesterday, you said Paraietta's
feelings were the easiest to get.
It's easiest to get Paraietta's feelings.
So for our information, you can't resist
a girl with glasses hitting on you?
Why do you keep turning
it into a personal thing?
My goal is to expose the director's
personality through his show.
Well, uh... it doesn't have
to be a girl with glasses.
You're so generous.
I have very liberal standards
when it comes to that.
Paraietta's braless from this angle.
This is... Wow.
"Wow."
We had the character designs. You
decided she'd have this body type...
...with her breasts
hanging down like that.
Yes, I designed her
that way without being asked.
And we're usually pressed for time,
so we tend to neglect those details...
...but everyone really stuck
to the script and designs.
I was so surprised...
The animation was so faithful.
They even kept the braless look!
That was really surprising.
And you know when different people
work on the same character...
...it can get inconsistent. But that
never happened with this show.
But when I was going over
the animation, I tweaked Kaim a lot.
Oh, so it did happen after all.
So it did.
But still, I think that
what we see onscreen...
...is largely what the character
designer had in mind.
You know that apron Mamina
was wearing just now?
That was one of your requests...
To have her wear her own apron.
Right, her own apron.
She packed her
own apron to go to war!
This was what gave
Mamina's image a real boost.
Even though she
cooked those mice?
She's deceiving you, guys.
In this scene, what's Yun...
What exactly is she observing?
Uh, that's a mystery, isn't it?
Yun happens to be
very mature. She's an adult.
She's actually thinking,
"I never got to do anything like that."
Oh, is that so?
So Yun is imagining herself in
Floe's place as she's drinking juice.
That's right.
So she's daydreaming.
Right.
The thing about Yun is that she
never got to do anything she wanted.
I guess you could
say she led a sad life.
But because of her principles
and those gorgeous looks...
...people think highly of her.
So is she one of those people whose
suppressed affections are later...
Later in the story...
Do they, like, explode?
You could say that.
Really now?
Hey, I was about to discuss
the war, but look where we are now!
I did hear about this yesterday...
This war has been going on for about
50 years, growing out of skirmishes.
It's been going on
in some fashion for a long time.
Ever since Neviril's dad,
Harukonf-sama, went into battle...
Or rather, he'd take off in
a Simoun, intimidate the enemies...
...and come back to base.
Is it all right if I draw
Harukonf when he was a sibylla?
Okay.
All right!
Then we need him to guest
star in Simoun episode 37.
I'll let him know.
Well, anyway, a lot of story
development happens in this episode...
Those hand gestures and facial
expressions started here, right?
Creative decisions.
I looked at them every time
the revised drafts came in.
I'd heard that the climactic
scene of this episode...
...was when Anglas goes,
"Aer!" and then boom!
So I was wondering
how to fool our viewers.
Sinister passions were stirred.
While I was drawing those
cute facial expressions.
And this is the harmony here.
This priestess named Anglas...
Later on in the show, another
Plumbum highland priestess...
Whoa, hey! It's over!
Featuring: Junji Nishimura
Asako Nishida
Whoa, hey! It's over!
Featuring: Junji Nishimura
Asako Nishida
Way too short!
Featuring: Junji Nishimura
Asako Nishida