The countless flowers,
enveloped in light...
...gaze at tomorrow
with unwavering eyes.
Everyone wishes for me to be pure...
...but what can I bring
with me to the frayed skies?
What I've made my own
by breaking off flowers in bloom...
All such sinful things...
Why did I stop making
promises with the future?
Because even if I try
to run far from all the pain...
...a cold wind rustles
my hair... Don't you see?
Where can I ever find the answer?
Get a move on!
You say it's a Simoun from Arcus Niger?
Military Councilor!
What's the meaning of this!
Arcus Niger...
...was shot down.
What?
Seven o'clock! Five ancient
Simouns approaching fast!
What in the world?
Sortie
Four o'clock! Multiple aircraft sighted!
Hurry, confirm that!
They appear to be
Shoukoku cruise missiles!
Vura, take one of the similes.
Right.
Which way should we head?
She's right. They say the
enemy Simouns are here too!
We're going to destroy the
missiles headed toward the city!
What about the Highland Simouns?
Arcus Prima and the Messis...
...will have to meet the
attack without our protection.
Para-sama...
Kaim...
We have to give it our best shot.
That's all we can do now!
Right!
Falcon Ri Majon!
Nine o'clock! More aircraft approaching!
Tell me what they are and how many!
Shoukoku cruise missiles!
Twenty of them!
Roatreamon! Three o'clock,
more missiles headed our way!
Right.
What's wrong?
Oh, it's nothing...
Whether it's a Ri Majon to
honor the souls of the dead...
...or a Ri Majon to repulse the enemy...
...a Ri Majon is still a Ri Majon.
That's what I used to believe.
Morinas...
Para-sama!
Come on!
Para-sama, the shrapnel
is falling over the town!
There's just too many of them!
Para-sama, look!
But now I know that's not true at all.
Yes, they're both Ri Majons, but they're
for a completely different purpose!
Hold on tight!
Morinas!
Are you two all right?
Morinas is hurt...
Don't worry. It's nothing. What about
you, Roatreamon? Are you all right?
Yes, I'm fine.
Paraietta, what about the enemy Simouns?
The thing is... I can't be sure, but...
They seem to have flown off.
What's that?
They're turning around and flying away.
Are you absolutely sure?
The Plumbum enemy Simouns
are about to leave our sights!
Why?
Why didn't the enemy Simouns attack us?
I know. But if they had attacked us,
they might have gotten us.
Guragief?
Yes?
Your quarters, please.
What?
Well?
What's going on?
Military Councilor?
Anubituf, what's going on?
The simile transporting Sibylla
Mamina's body never returned.
No...
I'm certain it was
intercepted by the enemy.
Needless to say, this happened
within the Kyuukoku borders.
Meaning we've already lost
control of our own airspace.
Then...
...what about Sibylla Mamina's body?
Guragief, that hardly matters anymore!
Can't you see we're in a state of...
So it's no concern of ours...
...what happens to Sibylla Mamina's
body. Is that what you're saying, sir?
Guragief...
You are not to inform the
sibyllae of this matter.
Anubituf!
I don't believe this! Even you...
The fact that the enemy Simouns
showed up in battle today...
...was a taunt to let us know
they can attack us at any time.
And that's exactly
what they're capable of.
No way...
I can't believe such a thing
could've happened while we were gone.
There must be something
we can do to help.
Right!
Come in!
How are you holding up, Sibylla Morinas?
Waporif!
Waporif, are you good
at wrapping bandages?
I had no idea Roatreamon
was so bad at this.
Please, allow me, Sibylla Roatreamon.
You see, the doctor was busy, so...
He's gone to the great temple,
tending to the injured civilians.
I see.
Well, I'm leaving her
in your hands then.
Fine.
Morinas...
We still have a lot of
things to do, don't we?
Sure.
Still, I like the Ri Majons
that we offer to Tempus Spatium.
Yeah, so do I.
And you know what? I bet
everyone else feels the same way!
Right!
How bad is the damage to the Simoun?
Looks like we'll only
have to replace the canopy.
We just finished repairing Sibylla
Aurea's Simoun, and now this...
I'm sorry.
Was there no other way?
No, there really wasn't.
I want you to take
better care of yourself.
All right, I will.
Promise me.
I promise.
Let me ask you one more time.
There is no longer any way to engage
the Shoukoku-highlands alliance...
Is that what you're saying?
You were the one...
...who took away three of the Simoun
sibyllae at such a critical time.
Let's be clear about
who's responsible for this!
I believe the situation is well
past the point of assigning blame.
We really should return to
the purpose of this meeting.
One hour ago, the
Shoukoku-highlands alliance...
...offered Simulacrum
Kyuukoku a cease-fire.
Now that they have a
clear advantage over us...
...they're actually suing for peace?
Don't tell me you've
already forgotten how...
...the highlands negotiated
peace the last time.
But it is our people's desire to bring
an end to this war as soon as possible!
Can't you see that their
offer is nothing but a sham?
Not again...
This wouldn't have happened...
...if you'd tried to negotiate peacefully.
I've had enough of your petty grudges!
How dare you!
I...
I'm not fit for this...
That's not true, Aer.
No matter what you may think
yourself, you are a Simoun sibylla.
All I know is war.
I don't know anything about praying.
Amuria...
She was a warrior too.
Even so, her prayers brought
solace to many people.
Everyone flocked to
Amuria to be blessed.
The priestesses are going
to protect us, right?
The priestesses are going to
strike down all the bad guys!
That's right. Just be
patient a little while longer.
Okay!
I'm so sorry. I didn't
think you'd be here.
That's all right.
Neviril and Aer are
blessing the people outside.
Yes, I know.
Who ever thought we'd
see Aer doing that?
Really!
You're the one we'd expect to
take the initiative... Oh...
Yes, that's true.
Mamina...
I think she should be by your side, Yun.
Why is that?
I can't really explain why...
...but I want you to
hold on to this for me.
So...
Yun, will you look after
Mamina for me from now on?
Fine.
I never thought you'd
hide anything from me.
Neither did I.
What is it that you want from me?
I just don't know anymore!
What do I want from you?
Emergency! Guys, it's an emergency!
Neviril! Aer!
Neviril!
Neviril! We just heard that they're
asking for another peace treaty.
Yes, Floe just told us.
But is that information true?
Yes, Sibylla Neviril.
Guragief...
Did the information come from you then?
Only a handful of
people are aware of this.
I took it upon myself to inform you all.
I see.
So is the war really
going to end this time?
I don't know about that.
Remember, Anglas was
supposed to be visiting...
...Kyuukoku as an interpreter
for the peace conference.
I know, but maybe this time around...
Yes.
It's possible that this time we'll be
able to release you sibyllae from battle.
Whatever happens, there's
nothing we can do about it.
That's right.
We can only do what we
have the power to do.
Guragief, I'd like to
discuss something with you...
Sibylla Aurea!
Yes?
Paraietta said the same thing just now!
Did she?
First off, to protect
ourselves from being invaded...
...from the mountains,
let us go out on patrol.
I understand it's a
state of emergency, but...
Just look at the size
of the Arcus Prima.
Yes.
I find it hard to believe that Arcus
Niger, a ship of the same dimensions...
...was actually shot down.
Yes, indeed.
Just as hard to believe as
seeing you at odds with Guragief!
So you noticed?
I can't imagine the
depth of your feelings...
...for each other that
neither of you can concede.
Guragief is...
...too single-minded.
That's for sure!
It's a shame that he
decided to become a man!
Anubituf...
Try to make peace with
Guragief as soon as you can.
You might not have a lot
of time left with him.
Right.
I have to get back to the bridge.
Para-sama!
Hurry, Kaim.
But why are they attacking us again?
They're going to keep at it
until they bend us to their will!
Let's go.
Para-sama!
Cast off the moorings!
Drop anchor!
Ascend at top speed! Hurry!
Ascending at top speed.
What's going on?
Seven o'clock! Five ancient
Simouns approaching!
Eleven o'clock, Shoukoku
midrange aircraft approaching!
Prepare the Simouns for takeoff!
Yes, sir!
Where are the priestesses
from Chor Tempest?
They're not here yet, sir.
What?
What are you waiting for, Anubituf?
Order Chor Tempest to go into battle!
Captain?
Pay no attention to him.
Anubituf!
Communications officer...
Send word for the sibyllae to
stand by on the flight deck.
I'm going to convey my orders in person.
Yes, sir!
Guragief, I'm leaving
you in charge for now.
The Arcus Prima will launch
the second wave of our attack.
You'll be directing
the Arcus Prima then.
Understood!
I'll be in command until
the captain returns.
Yes, sir!
What are you doing?
Get up there already!
Our orders are to stand
by on the flight deck.
What the!
Damn that Anubituf! What's he thinking?
Standing by at a time like this!
That old guy is so obnoxious!
Sorry to keep you waiting, sibyllae.
Hold on, you...
Surprised?
It may be hard to believe, but I too
was once a sibylla just like all of you.
You're going to fly a Simile, then?
Yes. We're going to have to meet the
enemy attack with only five Simouns.
I'm going up in a Simile and will
give you direct orders in the sky.
Please follow those orders.
Yes, sir! Understood!
Sibylla Morinas...
How is your wound?
I was given impeccable
treatment, sir. Everything is fine!
Get that Simile ready to go. Now!
Yes, sir!
Sibyllae...
The time has come for
us to take you out...
...of this war that you've
been fighting for us.
But only because we have failed...
We thank you, Captain Anubituf.
No matter what happens, we
shall never forget your words.
Yeah, no need to worry!
We've already made up our minds!
We're just going to
give it our best shot...
What we have the power to do!
We're hopelessly outnumbered.
We're going to draw them
in as close as we can...
...then make a sudden
dive and strike them hard!
This first attack will
decide the course of battle!
Let's go!
Follow me!
Foreign
All batteries, fire at will!
They're escaping!
That'll show you, losers!
Right?
Hey...
How do you like that, jerks?
Both of you, watch your language!
You heard us?
No, but we were just saying that
you two were probably talking vulgar!
Thanks a lot!
Good work, everyone.
Hey, what's going on?
Yes, tell us!
I'll bet it's just Floe making
another one of her absurd comments.
Yeah, that's probably
it, huh, Para-sama?
That's insulting!
I never said anything like that!
Is Chor Tempest always like this?
Pretty much.
The Captain's Simile, approaching!
Everybody, hats off!
Despite Chor Tempest's efforts...
...the center determined that
the war was now a lost cause.
And several days later...
...accepted the peace treaty offered
by the Plumbum highlands and Shoukoku.
It is played by my wounds...
the song of prayer.
Let it ring out over
the grieving universe.
Can we change tomorrow?
Don't be afraid.
I want to let you know
how my heart's overflowing.
I want to get closer to you.
I want to feel your pulse.
I was too defiant,
and I took the long way around.
The blue moon is swaying silently.
My true heart's desire is you.
I can't reach you.
My tears of pain trickle down.
Soar away into the sky, song of prayer.
Carrying my love that came too late.
What can I do to change tomorrow?
Just hold on to "now" the way it is...
To Be Continued
As alliance soldiers take
control of the Arcus Prima...
...Chor Tempest is disbanded.
Next time on Simoun...
Eternal Maidens
Eternal Maidens.