The countless flowers,
enveloped in light...
...gaze at tomorrow
with unwavering eyes.
Everyone wishes for me to be pure...
...but what can I bring
with me to the frayed skies?
What I've made my own
by breaking off flowers in bloom...
All such sinful things...
Why did I stop making
promises with the future?
Because even if I try
to run far from all the pain...
...a cold wind rustles
my hair... Don't you see?
Where can I ever find the answer?
Making another unauthorized
flight, Chor Tempest?
Vura!
Dux Guragief ordered us to go
on a special training mission.
You're all busy with
regular duties, right?
Yeah, we're tired. Night patrol requires
far more vigilance than day patrol.
And enemy encounters are likelier.
It's easier to just float
around during the day.
But your chor used to do
nothing but daytime patrol.
The night shift was always our job.
But that's not the case now.
The top chor on
Arcus Prima is now us, Rubor.
If you don't like it,
then prove you're still worthy.
Step aside. We're exhausted.
Everyone, let them pass.
By the way, which Ri Majon?
The Dandelion Ri Majon.
Dandelion?
The ceremonial Ri Majon
used for diplomatic purposes.
Why use
an old-fashioned Ri Majon like that?
Vura!
Help yourself to
the leftover candy on my desk!
Don't wake me coming back!
Over International Waters
Wow!
Look how spotless you are now.
These kids worked hard.
It's quite an antique,
so they had a rough time.
Thanks.
My grandpa flew this
when he was young.
Your grandfather
was a Simoun sibylla too?
So after he went to the Spring and
stopped flying, he still treasured this.
They're jealous that we always
used to be assigned night patrol.
When Chor Rubor used to run into
Neviril, they'd just look on from afar.
Be proud of yourselves.
As a member of Chor Tempest, I plan
to take this chor right back to the top.
Right. As far as wanting to see
Tempest back on top, I'm with her.
Well, I guess you're right.
Since we won't have to go to the
Spring as long as we keep winning?
Well, I can't wait to go.
Then what's stopping you?
I want to go with
the person I care about.
Then when I emerge from
the Spring, I'll be a man.
And she'll be a woman...
And you'll consummate
things then and there?
Quiet down.
Listen up, everybody.
There are two obstacles
to becoming the best chor.
Unless we get two new members...
...we won't be able
to fly six Simouns at once.
What's the other thing?
Neviril...
If Neviril and Aer flew as a pair...
...it wouldn't be a stretch
to see our chor back on top!
Para-sama...
...you're giving up on Neviril?
Let's do it in front of the Arcus Prima!
So that the dux and Neviril can see.
Morinas-san, higher!
Am I not good enough
for Sibylla Aurea?
Morinas-san, please concentrate!
Okay, okay.
You have to lead the others.
Right.
So who's this loved one?
Floe, I'm hearing bad
things about you lately.
No way! It's not true, is it, Alty?
Of course it's true.
I'm so happy...
Para-sama,
you're responding to my feelings.
What are you talking about?
I was sure you hated me.
Since the other day...
Be specific!
Huh?
Arcus Niger? We're not
supposed to rendezvous till later.
That's the Niger. No mistake.
An emergency, perhaps?
I'm sure they're just being
rushed by the higher-ups.
You should summon
the Tempest girls back.
Arcus Niger!
Niger?
They're supposed to be west
of the great temple... Why...
A Simile Simoun!
A messenger?
Even so...
How lame is that pilot?
Missing the cable like that!
No, they're avoiding it on purpose.
Hey!
Talk!
You're supposed to be Chor Tempest?
Since the Plumbum highlands and
our nation share similar customs...
...I didn't think the decor
here would offend you.
Let's have
Tempus Spatium be scarce.
That would undermine
our authority severely...
The highlanders worship
a deity named Animus.
Historically speaking...
...Animus and Tempus Spatium
are in fact the same god.
The highlands and Kyuukoku
do not acknowledge this.
It's best to avoid
unnecessary stimulation?
For the sake of peace.
Tempus Spatium would
be glad to be concealed.
Peace conference?
Right. It's fair to say we're battling
all our neighboring countries.
Each one,
because of economic strife...
They want the Simouns.
No matter what.
Right.
To be more precise,
they're after the helical motors.
Unearthed only from ruins,
the wings that give Simouns flight.
But now the Plumbum highlands
have come to broker a peace deal.
It's been decided the first conference
will be held in international waters.
In utmost secrecy of course.
So they'll hold this conference
on the Arcus Prima, huh?
Who cares about politics?
Are we free to use the maju pool?
I think they'll say not
to act without permission.
Hey, it's them.
The ones flying that Simile before.
Why are they
wandering around here?
They're headed this way.
Why are they on our ship?
The most obvious reason is
that they're new members...
Hey, I bet she'll say something like,
"Chor Tempest sure is a letdown."
Right, right.
Sorry for earlier,
members of Chor Tempest.
So it was you two after all.
Still, you sure are a letdown.
Is it that funny, my lady Roatreamon?
I don't blame you
for not remembering.
I just lived on your estate...
...as the daughter of two
of your many servants.
Come now, Mamina.
Mamina?
I am honored that
you remember me, my lady.
As of today,
I've been ordered to transfer...
...from Arcus Niger's
Chor Ignus to Chor Tempest.
I'm Sibylla Mamina. I'm pleased
to make your acquaintance.
And I'm Yun.
I'm also joining Chor Tempest.
I have one thing to say. I despise war.
That's all.
Somebody!
Somebody, please help us!
Sibylla Aurea's room...
What's this about Neviril?
Neviril!
Paraietta...
What's going on?
What do you think you're doing?
Sibylla Aurea sleeps
alone in her room.
That's a privilege
granted to her alone! Hey!
Starting today,
she's sharing her room.
Father!
Para, it's been a while.
Yes, it has, Vice Chancellor.
Neviril, I think this is a good way to
immediately bond with your new pair.
New pair?
Then that's my bed.
A "new pair"...Father.
Yes, I'm assigning Mamina.
Mamina?
Excuse me.
Pairs should be formed out of mutual
need and according to the natural flow.
You were once a sibylla, Father,
so you should be well aware of that.
Neviril, in this day and age,
it doesn't work that way anymore.
You must take this step now
or your name will be tarnished.
I was an auriga,
but if I can pair with you...
...I'd be happy to fly as a sagitta.
Mamina is not from
a family befitting a sibylla.
But of all the great temple's
candidates, she scored the highest.
As far as the Wave Crest
and Tsunami Ri Majons...
...I can pray better than anyone.
Those are all highly dangerous.
Which enable us to annihilate
more enemies in one blow.
All I want is for you to snap out of it.
Granted, a tragedy occurred.
But you shall overcome that and
regain your glory as Sibylla Aurea.
Meaning that your standing in
the council will be safe, Father?
I don't understand what's
going on in your head, Neviril.
If you're put off by battle,
then you should go to the Spring.
You'll surely become a lovely woman.
But if you're put off by the Spring and
refuse to fly a Simoun, what then?
You're telling me
to give you an answer.
You're old enough now.
Is Neviril coming back?
Hey, Aer, you should
pair with me after all.
I like Neviril.
Neviril really is popular.
I think I'll give up on her.
What will you do?
I'll pair with someone. But even so,
I'll still despise what we do.
If so, then just hurry on to the Spring.
I couldn't do that!
Already, many of my friends,
despite being priestesses...
...were sent to the battlefield since
they could fly Simouns and perished.
I couldn't run away
from that just on my own!
That reason sounds like a death wish.
Paraietta.
I always thought you and Neviril
would fly as a pair one day.
Vice Chancellor...
No matter what, I will protect Neviril.
Mamina, I'm sorry.
I'm still...
Sibylla Aurea,
I want you to be my pair...
...body and soul.
Sibylla Mamina, even if you
take my body by force...
...you will never be my pair.
Neviril, try to understand.
I've got to pair up with you,
no matter what it takes.
Aer!
You actually used that rope
to come through the window?
You're such a funny girl.
All six Simouns will be needed
for the Dandelion Ri Majon.
As Chor Tempest is now...
We've already bolstered the ranks.
Is that not enough?
It's about whether it can be
done with those new members.
It's a prayer for a key event, the
peace conference with the highlands.
We cannot risk failure of any kind.
All I'm asking for is a Ri Majon
performed by Chor Tempest.
If you cannot comply
with my request...
What will you do?
I don't want my daughter
to suffer any more humiliation.
I don't want her to get hurt.
Mamina! You want to challenge
me in the maju pool too?
Challenge you?
To decide who'll pair up with Neviril.
It's not a matter of challenging you.
What are you doing?
As long as we have these outfits on...
...the helical motors activate, allowing
us to float! But if it's removed...
You crazy?
Say you'll give up on her!
Cut it out!
I'm going to pair with her!
Same for me! But that's up to her!
You're of low birth and only made it
here because you can fly a Simoun!
One such as you is unworthy of her!
The same goes for you too!
Let go of me!
Aer!
As long as such breaches
of conduct continue...
...we can only conclude
Chor Tempest no longer functions.
By that, do you mean...
Once the peace conference
is over, I want Chor Tempest...
...to disband.
Please wait, Vice Chancellor!
Then what of your daughter?
That's the point.
I can't leave her in this chor. She'll go
to the Spring before she's hurt further.
U-Um, then what about me?
You've disappointed me.
It is played by my wounds...
the song of prayer.
Let it ring out over
the grieving universe.
Can we change tomorrow?
Don't be afraid.
I want to let you know
how my heart's overflowing.
"I want to get closer to you."
"I want to feel your pulse."
I was too defiant,
and I took the long way around.
The blue moon is swaying silently.
My true heart's desire is you.
I can't reach you.
My tears of pain trickle down.
Soar away into the sky, song of prayer.
Carrying my love that came too late.
What can I do to change tomorrow?
Just hold on to "now" the way it is...
To Be Continued
The highland priestess named Anglas...
...will be staying with
Chor Tempest for the time being.
Prayer
Next time on Simoun...
Prayer.
Prayer