The countless flowers,
enveloped in light...
...gaze at tomorrow
with unwavering eyes.
Everyone wishes for me to be pure...
...but what can I bring
with me to the frayed skies?
What I've made my own
by breaking off flowers in bloom...
All such sinful things...
Why did I stop making
promises with the future?
Because even if I try
to run far from all the pain...
...a cold wind rustles
my hair... Don't you see?
Where can I ever find the answer?
Rimone...
Rimone, the elder is summoning you.
Aira and Hanna are going
to give it a try today!
Ah, here she is now.
Rimone!
Aira, Hanna...
Are you really sure you want to do this?
Of course!
You know how long we've been
practicing towards this day!
I'm so glad they chose me!
It's always been my dream to
be like you and Dominüra...
...and to do the Emerald Ri Majon!
Sibylla Dominüra and Sibylla Rimone...
It was they who bestowed us
with the Emerald Ri Majon.
And now our young girls
have taken to the skies.
We have seen flowers blooming
that had never bloomed before...
...and we are now reaping the
harvest of our barren crops.
And now today, we shall
send off two more girls.
I am certain that they, too,
shall bring us great fortune!
Their Portraits
Get a move on! Let's not keep
the client waiting forever!
Morinas...
Well, what is it, Wauf?
Listen to me.
It doesn't matter if
you're a man or a woman...
...or even a former sibylla,
for that matter.
You work for me now! And I'm
not cutting you any slack.
Right, right, so what's up?
Are you telling me to pick up the pace?
You need to go easy on yourself.
Daddy!
Hey, what is it, sweetheart?
Mommy said...
...to ask you what you wanted for lunch.
Well, everything your
mommy makes is so delicious.
She said you're not
allowed to say "anything"!
She did? All right, that's
going to be a tough one then.
So listen, this is the
most critical time for you!
I don't want Waporif coming
after me if you overdo it.
I've heard that if you just keep moving,
you can pop out the baby, 1-2-3!
Is that right?
But thanks.
So what are we having for lunch, Daddy?
Hm, let's see now...
Morinas!
Hey, good work.
Hold on a second, didn't you
just finish your night shift?
Well, we don't have a choice.
The highlands and Shoukoku
are already waging a cold war.
They could void the peace treaty any
day, and then they'll drag us into it!
War again, huh?
Eliph! Let's go!
Okay!
See you!
They saved us back there, didn't they?
Yes, they did.
Floe was crying.
I know.
Do you think we'll succeed?
The Emerald Ri Majon?
Yes.
You've stolen a Simoun and
allowed the sibyllae to escape.
Do you realize the magnitude
of what you've done?
Foreign
If they should revolt
against our country...
You've got the wrong idea.
All they're going to do...
...is carry themselves away.
To the Land of Hope.
Paraietta!
Play with us!
I have a guest to tend to now, so
it'll have to be a little later.
Everyone, try to get along now!
Yes, ma'am!
Such lively children!
I know. It's all I can
do to keep up with them.
Paraietta, I'm so sorry.
I tried to negotiate with them, but...
...there's not much more I can do.
Roatreamon...
...this place wouldn't even
exist without your help.
And I'm so grateful for that.
Well, there has to be
another way. I'll find one.
Once war is officially declared...
...there will be more and more
victims like these children.
They're not really victims though.
Right. They've lost a
lot because of the war...
...but they still have
so much to live for!
They're our seeds of hope.
Their footsteps will one day
ring out across the Land of Hope.
Of Hope...
"The Land of Hope."
For someone who was once
a priestess long ago...
...those words have
such a nostalgic ring.
I thought it was only a legend.
Foreign
But even if the legend is true...
...what purpose could there be in
performing the Emerald Ri Majon now?
There's no longer any
value to the word "purpose."
Anubituf...
Yes, if we looked hard enough,
we might find such a purpose.
But even if we'd found one...
...the girls would never
have chosen it themselves.
Foreign
What?
The Simouns...
Take our Simouns and pursue
the Sibylla Aurea's Simoun!
Are you insane? Do you
intend to shoot them down?
Chief!
Our hands are tied. There's
nothing we can do now.
We're going to go back to our jobs now!
Yes, sir!
It will be all right, Floe.
They'll be fine.
Even if they go after them now...
But, but...
I'm sure that Aer and
Neviril will make it in time.
It's going to be all right.
Here, your nose is running!
Really, since when are
you such a crybaby, Floe?
But, but...
Floe, there's no need to worry.
Don't cry.
Yeah, come on. I'm
sure Aer and Neviril...
Huh? What?
Para-sama, you're breathing on me...
What? Oh no!
Okay! I'm gonna get
all touchy-feely too!
Oh? Then let's do that too!
Para-sama!
Me too!
Come on! Stop it, Alty!
Me, too!
Big Sister, was that...
Yes.
Big Sister! Hurry, hurry!
Dad's clothes! Alty! Get that one!
Oh, brother. All that time
we spent doing laundry...
This weather's so weird. Guess we'll
just have to wash everything again.
Hey, all you do is sit
there and watch, Big Sister!
Well, that's my job.
Dummy!
Dominüra...
Are you feeling any better?
Thank you. My fever has gone down.
That's good.
Is something the matter?
I think I finally understand...
...what you meant after all this time.
They're all going to fly off.
Into a sky where nothing
is ever certain...
Towards a hope that they
can't even be sure exists.
I made everyone learn how
to do the Emerald Ri Majon...
...yet I don't even
take to the skies myself.
I...
Rimone...
Do you want to fly again?
Yes.
But if you don't want
to do it, Dominüra...
I'll never fly with anyone as my pair...
...but you, Dominüra.
I'm going to do it for you.
The Emerald Ri Majon.
Simouns!
They're coming after us!
Neviril!
Yes.
Let's hurry! They're
going to catch up to us.
Wait.
What?
They're going to do a Ri Majon!
We'd better hurry up then!
No. That's...
What is it?
I've never seen that Ri Majon before.
The Morning Calm Ri Majon.
Morning Calm?
I read about that one
once in an old book.
It's performed to bid farewell to
comrades about to depart on a journey.
To bid farewell to comrades
departing on a journey...
But that's...
The Morning Calm Ri Majon?
Foreign
There was also a time in my life...
Long ago, we were all maidens too.
Let's do it.
Yes.
Let's do it now.
Let's go now, Aer...
To a place where you and I can be free!
Yes. Let's go, Neviril!
Forgive me for bringing
you here, Rimone.
That's all right. What is it?
You see, I want you to pair up with me.
I already told you no once.
I'll only...
I know that.
But does Dominüra ever intend
to fly again? I wonder...
I'm sorry.
Still...
Um, wasn't that a Simoun?
Aer!
Huh? What's that?
Is that a name?
The ultimate form of love.
Love?
That's right.
Dominüra!
The ultimate love.
Which sky shall we journey towards next?
Dominüra!
Hey! You got here early, Vura!
No, wait. I mean Vuraf.
It's awkward for you
to call me that, right?
You can just call me Vura.
All right, Vura. Why
don't you come inside?
Sure.
Did you get one too, Vura?
Yeah.
The war hasn't even started yet!
I guess former sibyllae...
...have the honor of being the first
to be shipped out at times like these.
Which side?
My hometown is on the
other side of the border.
I'll be fighting for Shoukoku.
So we're going to be enemies then?
Yeah.
Never mind. Here, have some of our
local vegetables! New strain, you know.
I need to make a killing on these...
...and find myself a lovely bride.
I can't die till I've done that!
Becoming a man hasn't
changed you at all, Floef!
It's hard to say, isn't it?
You can just call me Floe too.
Is that the Arcus Prima?
Yeah. I thought I might as well
live where I can always see it.
That's why I picked this spot.
A sunken luxury liner?
I suppose there's an allure to that.
See you then.
Yeah, see you later.
Wait, that might be bad luck to say.
I don't want to see
you on the battlefield.
All right then. How's goodbye?
Right. Goodbye.
Bye.
I wonder why none of us could let it go?
The idea of sending Aer and
Neviril off to that other world?
Was it because we wanted to defy
the inescapable flow of time?
We were afraid to grow up.
We wanted to stay the way
we were as young girls.
Did we project those feelings
on to Aer and Neviril?
No, I'm sure that's not it.
All we wanted to do
was to leave our mark.
To prove that we once
existed, right here.
We wanted to shout that
out to the whole world.
The fact that we were
once really here...
We wanted to leave our mark.
We wanted to raise our voices.
Aer...
Neviril...
I wonder where you are right now?
Where are you, our eternal maidens?
Such a nice breeze.
Yes.
It certainly is a nice breeze.
It is played by my wounds...
the song of prayer.
Let it ring out over
the grieving universe.
Can we change tomorrow?
Don't be afraid.
I want to let you know
how my heart's overflowing.
I want to get closer to you.
I want to feel your pulse.
I was too defiant,
and I took the long way around.
The blue moon is swaying silently.
My true heart's desire is you.
I can't reach you.
My tears of pain trickle down.
Soar away into the sky, song of prayer.
Carrying my love that came too late.
What can I do to change tomorrow?
Just hold on to "now" the way it is...