Wait!
Nee-san...
I'm Para-sama's pair!
To put me with Alti at this point...
This is all for the sake of regaining Chor Tempest's honour.
Neviril, look!
What? It's...
Why is their prayer having no effect on the Simoun Gem?
Kaimu!
Nee-san!
Don't call me that!
Reason
Prayer?
Yes, the chariots of the gods are activated by the prayers of the Simoun sibyllae.
Two priestesses unite their hearts in praise of Tempus Spatium.
To reject one's pair is to reject the Simoun.
This is unbelievable. I've never heard of such a thing.
All of this is guesswork.
But thanks to the two of you, we've discovered a hidden aspect of the Simoun.
You've done well, although you probably don't appreciate my saying so.
So that means... that I probably won't be able to pair... with Nee-san any more.
You understand, don't you?
The enemy hasn't shown up.
We've been lying around so much that I'm almost gathering dust.
So would you rather be fighting?
I didn't say that!
I just meant that there's nothing to do.
You should consider your words carefully,
or else keep them to yourself.
Ahhhhhh!
Rodoreamon can get really scary when she's mad.
What are you thinking about?
Something other than you.
I see.
The Emerald Ri Maajon?
Yeah, it's the greatest Ri Maajon that a Simoun can perform.
The ultimate...
You were imitating the Emerald Ri Maajon on purpose.
Huh? Did I do some kind of Ri Maajon?
Oh, so that's what that was about!
Aaeru?
Tell me, what would happen?
Sorry. I'm afraid I've never seen it.
Neviril and Amuria did the Emerald Ri Maajon?
Well...
I get it! They tried but they couldn't do it.
I see. So she and Amuria...
Wow, you're so thorough.
Tempus Spatium likes cleanliness and shuns places that are dirty.
You're amazing, Mamiina! You know a lot that I don't.
Maybe it suits me.
Being here has felt like a dream.
Ah, it's stuck and it won't come off. If only we could get citrus fruit...
Citrus fruit?
The acid in the juice would dissolve the stain.
You really are amazing!
This is delicious!
Neviril!
Do the Emerald Ri Maajon with me!
Aaeru, what are you—
I get it! You and Amuria failed at it.
But with me, I bet you can do it. Come on, Neviril, let's try the Em—
Stop it!
Wait.
I'll go get a mop.
Neviril, are you okay?
Drop it, Aaeru.
Why?
That topic is...
What, because it makes her remember Amuria's death?
Neviril!
That was in spectacularly bad taste.
Poor Neviril.
I never met Amuria, but you shouldn't speak ill of the dead.
What? I didn't—
C'mere.
Aaeru...
Why'd you drag me all the way down here?
Sheesh! So tell me, do you like Neviril?
Sure, I like her.
That's not what I mean.
Huh?
Do you wanna talk with her as long as you can? Feel her warmth as you hold her? Are you filled with love and desire for her? That kind of "like," I mean.
Sure, I want Neviril!
I can fly higher with her than with anyone else.
Aaeru!
How did that feel?
How did what feel?
What I just did!
Well, we're not about to fly into battle, so it's kind of weird.
If you really liked someone, you'd feel differently. Neviril like-liked Amuria that way. Get it?
What does that have to do with the Emerald Ri Maajon?
It's a lot better if you like each other, okay?
Neviril!
Neviril...
Neviril.
It'll be all right... if you do that with me.
We can do it, if we're together.
The Emerald Ri Maajon!
Because... because it makes her remember Amuria's death.
Nooooooooo!
Neviril, what's going on? Neviril!
I'll open the window.
It's dusty in here, but this must be better than sharing a room with Aaeru—with the others.
Yes, thanks.
Get some rest, then.
The Emerald Ri Maajon...
It must be really great.
Yeah.
I want to try it too.
With Dominura?
It doesn't matter who my partner is...
Do you like Dominura?
I don't know.
They say if you really like somebody, you want to kiss her even when you're not flying a Simoun.
Apparently, a lot of things are better if you like your pair.
A lot?
Yep. A lot.
What did Central Command say?
They said that unless the enemy shows signs of activity, we should just watch them for now.
That enemy base ship was almost impossible to find.
Do they think we should just leave it alone?
They've apparently been distracted by unexpected problems with the Arcus Prima.
As I thought, they're missing the forest for the trees. If things go on this way, our Holy Land will...
Sibylla Dominura, you look uneasy. It may be out of line for a man in my position to offer advice to a sibylla, but—
Yes, it certainly is.
Limone, what is it? Is something wrong?
Yes?
How did that feel?
Did you feel that you liked me?
Run along.
Amuria... is dead.
I finally found you!
W-Why?
Whew!
What are you...?
Are you sick?
C'mon, look at me.
You can't feel the wind in here. It's so stuffy and full of old junk.
There's nothing here but a bunch of useless memories.
Let's go outside.
Come on, let's open the door together, Neviril.
What are you doing?!
Hey, that hurts!
Neviril is tired. Get out of here!
What? But...
Get out!
Neviril, I don't think Aaeru means any harm, but—
I would like to sleep for a while. Is that all right?
Where's Aaeru?
No idea.
That was surprising.
Yes.
Not just for Neviril.
The rest of us have avoided talking about it, too.
I felt that mentioning it would keep us from moving on.
Amuria was strong.
She was always aiming higher, and never doubted herself.
Yes, I thought the war was too much for me but...
When Amuria was with us, it felt as though we were invincible,
so I was afraid to admit that she was gone.
No, even now I don't want to. But—
What happened to my...?
You caught me.
What's up?
What is that?
What sort of creature is that supposed to be?
Oh, that's funny!
Come on! I sewed it as well as I could! I know it's a bit ugly, but...
Its face is all misshapen.
It's fine. This is adorable!
It's certainly unique... just like its maker.
Hey!
I didn't mean to hurt Neviril.
I just thought that we could do anything if we were together.
How can you be so confident?
Haven't you ever felt despair?
If I told you, what difference would it make?
Maybe it was a mistake to entrust Neviril to you.
We can't wait for the brass any longer.
We should scout out the base ship while the enemy remains quiet.
Neviril, Aaeru, it's up to you.
Wait, those two are...
The two of them are the best pair in Chor Tempest at the moment. Is there a problem?
But...!
Dominura, I can't pair with Aaeru right now.
Yesterday, you said the Simoun are—
Yes, and that is why.
People's feelings aren't toys! How can you just assume—
Neviril.
I want to fly.
Neviril, I guess you don't want to, but I...
Neviril, please consider the interests of the nation above all else.
We are Simoun sibyllae.
Are you worried?
This is pointless.
It's not pointless.
Not pointless at all. We can fly. We can!
Their prayer seems to have been heard.
I guess feelings don't matter after all.
They do matter. We must conclude that Neviril...
Neviril...
Why?
I was right. You do want me!
You can fly with me.
Anything is possible when you're with me!
Do I want Aaeru?
No, it can't be. I'm... I'm...
I'm... afraid of Aaeru.
Next Episode
Are you ordering me to dismantle a Simoun, Sibylla Dominura?
Next time, on Simoun:
That Which Must Not Be Violated
That Which Must Not Be Violated.