Wait!
Nee-san...
I'm Para-sama's pair!
To put me with Alti at this point...
There are plenty of people for Paraietta to fly with,
but you only have one sister.
The Ri Maajons you two draw together will certainly reflect that.
Because we're sisters?
This is all for the sake of regaining Chor Tempest's honour.
From now on, no more disgraceful conduct will be permitted.
Sisters
Yun!
Are you picking out all of your onions?
Leave me alone.
Yun, I didn't know you could be so cute!
So I guess it wasn't anything special, then?
Huh?
You were all "Oh, I'm in love!", and look at you now.
— Mastif, you're so sweet.
— What about killing people, though?
Kaimu!
Don't take it out on me just because your beloved Para-sama dumped you!
Cut it out!
Nee-san.
Ah! Back to normal at last!
I'm so proud of you for putting up with all the inhuman things they did to you.
You guys are awesome!
Morinas, I can't pretend I didn't hear you say "inhuman."
Now there's a rare sight...
Floe.
I'm sorry.
Nee-san didn't say that just to be mean to you.
It's just...
It's okay.
Anyway, she's got a point.
My chest was going all "waaah!"
I thought my heart would stop.
But...
But it didn't.
It's just that...
I don't ever want to forget what happened that night.
Not forget...
what happened that night.
Nee-san!
Hey, Floe, more to the left.
Why are we leaking?
Simoun sibyllae, the Messis is honoured that you're helping us.
Unbelievable! How can this thing fly?
My deepest apologies.
Where's Kaimu?
Still sulking. What a sourpuss!
Here you are.
Kaimu, Aaeru and I will be coming with you on tomorrow's patrol.
Para-sama, don't you care at all? We're not going to be a pair any more!
Settle down, Kaimu.
Don't look at me like that!
Sorry.
Para-sama, you haven't done anything wrong!
Kaimu.
And I haven't done anything wrong, either!
Kaimu!
She's terribly confused.
Perhaps I should go with them.
No, not you.
Uh oh! She broke it!
Yikes, that's cold!
I thought it would be all right when the rust was gone, but now this!
I give up!
Aren't you cold?
It won't come off.
No matter how much I wash and wash,
it won't come off.
Let's just go to sleep now.
Limone, you must be scared.
You can come and sleep in my bed if you'd like.
Nope. I'm fine.
Don't push yourself. You're still little, so—
You're the one who's scared.
I... I am not!
What's the matter?
Mm.
This is the first time that we've flown together, isn't it?
We're just "praying to the sky."
Nee-san...
How did we get like this?
I mean, we used to be together all the time.
It must be because of that night.
Shut up!
After them, Aaeru!
Aaeru! The speaker cable!
Neviril, look!
It's...!
Kaimu! Alti!
Why?
Why is their prayer having no effect on the Simoun Gem?
If they go into the clouds...
...we'll lose sight of them.
Nee-san!
Don't call me that!
Do not call me that!
I knew it.
Everything really is your fault.
Alti, you're the one who screwed everything up.
Yes, everything!
It was all your fault!
What is that?
Eh? She's just as beat-up as the Messis.
But what is she?
She's an Argentine logistical base ship.
But I had no idea that they could make them so large!
We're awfully close, but it doesn't look like they've spotted us yet.
Wanna go have a look?
No. It's too dangerous.
And there's something wrong with one of our Simoun.
We should go back to the Messis and...
This was ridiculous from the beginning.
Even Dominura should understand...
Just because we're sisters...
I... will go.
Alti?
Nee-san and I... we can make it work.
I want Dominura to know that.
Leave this to me.
Aaeru and Kaimu will wait with the Simoun.
We'll approach cautiously and get inside.
If anything happens...
Yes.
There's no one here.
No.
What's that?
A broken searchlight, and no guard.
People like this are causing us so much pain?
Us.
Yes.
They're using this to go up against the chariots of the gods.
Doesn't it matter to them that they're outmatched?
Aren't they afraid of dying?
I don't think there's anyone who doesn't fear death.
So. They're strong, then.
I envy them.
Alti.
You don't need to be strong by yourself.
It's her fault.
She's always...
She's always getting in my way.
Why?
Why does she...?
What happened between you and Alti?
You two are weird. I mean, you're sisters, but—
It's because we're sisters.
That night...
That night, I was weak.
When morning came, it was going to be my first battle.
I was scared.
I wanted to cry out, to run away...
It was then...
...that she came on to me.
I couldn't resist what Alti was offering.
I dunno, I don't get it.
Of course not. Between sisters, it's an abominable sin.
That's not what I mean.
In things like that, it's hard to say who's right and who's wrong.
What?
I can't tell just from hearing about it.
Maybe you were the one who led her on.
Led her on? Me?
Me? No!
I...
Kaimu?
I have to make sure.
I'm going to get Alti.
Wait, Kaimu! Kaimu!
When we were little, I was always crying.
But every time, Nee-san would hold me.
And I felt stronger.
It's not that night that I want to get back to,
It's those warm afternoons.
What I want are not the hands that gave me sensations I'd never felt before,
but rather the gentle hand that held mine as we walked.
But Nee-san...
Someday I'll become a man.
Then it will be my turn to hold Nee-san in my arms, as tightly as I can.
Nee-san...
Nee-san!
Nee-san! Jump!
Nee-san! What is it?
Don't worry, you'll land in my arms!
Nee-san!
It's not... my... fault...
Kaimu, when we get there, go straight to Aaeru's sagitta seat.
Kaimu! Do you understand?
Yeah.
Their prayer had no effect on the Simoun Gem.
I see. And something like this, you've...
...never heard of before.
The Argentine base ship—we can't just leave it.
They had a new class of fighter based there.
To get stronger through someone else's embrace...
That's not the right way, Alti.
Only when both of you are strong can you really embrace each other.
Aaeru, how's Nee-san?
Just some scrapes and scratches.
Thanks.
Hey, didn't you and Amuria ever embrace each other?
It'll be all right... if you do that with me.
The reflection in your eyes...
...is an image of yourself, never growing older.
Not me.
It tastes just like hers.
Next Episode
Aaeru's words make Neviril fall to pieces.
Next time, on Simoun:
Reason
Reason.