Hurry!
A Simoun from the Arcus Niger?
Minister!
What.. what is this? What's going on?
The Arcus Niger...
...has gone down.
What?
Seven o'clock high! Five ancient Simoun, closing in fast!
Sortie
Four o'clock level! Aircraft silhouettes sighted!
Confirm that, quickly!
They appear to be Argentine cruise missiles!
Vyura, you take a Simile.
Right.
What should we...?
Yeah, I heard the enemy Simoun are here too!
We'll destroy the missiles headed for the city.
And the Highlands' Simoun?
The Arcus Prima and the Messis...
...will have to deal with them on their own.
Para-sama...
Kaimu.
Right now, we need to do what we can, with all our might!
Yeah!
Falcon Ri Maajon!
Nine o'clock low!
More aeroplane silhouettes!
Identify them! How many?
Argentine cruise missiles!
Number: twenty!
Rodoreamon!
Three o'clock low, more missiles incoming!
Yes...
What's wrong?
Oh no, it's nothing...
Whether we perform Ri Maajons to send off the souls of the dead, or to drive away the enemy,
it doesn't change the fact that we're performing Ri Maajons.
At least, that's what I used to think...
Morinas...
Para-sama!
Let's go!
Para-sama, the shrapnel is going to fall on the city!
There are too many of them!
Para-sama, look!
...but I don't believe that any more.
The Ri Maajons are the same,
but their meaning is totally different!
Hang on tight!
Morinas!
Are you two all right?
Morinas, she...!
It's nothing...
Rodoreamon, how about you? Are you okay?
Me? Yes.
Paraietta, what about the enemy Simoun?
Actually... I'm not sure.
They seem to have run away.
What did you say?
They're turning around and flying away.
Are you certain of that?
The enemy's Highland Simoun will soon be out of visual range, sir!
Why?
Why didn't the enemy Simoun attack?
If they had attacked us...
...we would have been wiped out.
Guragief.
Yes?
Your quarters, please.
What?
Well?
What's going on?
The Defence Minister?
Anubituf, what is the meaning of this?
The Simile which was carrying Sibylla Mamiina's body...
...has not returned.
Are you serious?
It was almost certainly intercepted by the enemy.
It goes without saying, but the incident took place within our Holy Land.
We no longer have control of our own airspace.
Then...
What of Sibylla Mamiina's body?
Guragief, we have no time for such trivial matters.
The situation is already—
Did you just say that Sibylla Mamiina's body is a trivial matter?
Minister, did I really just hear you say that?
Guragief.
You are not to inform the sibyllae of this situation.
Anubituf!
You too?
The appearance of the Simoun among the Argentine forces today...
...was a show of force, to prove to us that they can attack whenever they please.
And that really is what they're capable of doing.
This is awful.
I can't believe that this could have happened while we were gone.
There has to be something we can do to help.
Yeah!
Come in!
How is your wound, Sibylla Morinas?
Wapourif!
Wapourif, do you know how to wrap a bandage?
Really, Rodoreamon's lack of skill is shocking.
Please, allow me, Sibylla Rodoreamon.
The flight surgeon was busy, so...
The doc's at the Grand Temple, tending to the people who were hurt.
I see.
Well, I'll leave her in your capable hands, Wapourif!
Yes, ma'am.
Morinas.
There are still a lot of things that we'll have to do, aren't there?
Yeah.
But... I like the Ri Maajons that we offer to Tempus Spatium.
Yeah, me too.
And you know, I think everyone else feels the same.
Yes!
How's the damage to the Simoun?
I believe that we will only need to replace the canopy.
Really, we just finished repairing the Sibylla Aurea's Simoun, and now this.
Sorry.
Was there no other way?
Yeah... it was the only thing we could do.
Would you please take better care of yourself?
Yeah, I will.
Promise me.
I promise.
I will ask you once more.
Do we really have no way to repel the combined forces of the Highlands and the Archipelago?
Is that the situation?
At such a critical time,
you were the one responsible for carrying off three of our Simoun sibyllae!
I think that we are well past the time for recriminations.
Please, let us return to the object of this meeting.
One hour ago, the Highlands and Archipelago proposed a ceasefire between their alliance and our Simulacrum Theocracy.
To think they are suing for peace,
when they have the power to defeat us.
I hope you haven't forgotten the Highlanders' previous method of "negotiating" a peace agreement.
Yes, but the people are voicing their desire for an end to this war!
Can't you see that these "proposals" of theirs are just lies?
Not again...
If we had opened peace talks earlier, we would have—
I am sick of hearing about your grudges against us.
How dare you!
I...
I can't do this.
That's not true, Aaeru.
No matter how you think of yourself, you are a Simoun sibylla.
I don't know about anything but fighting.
I don't know how to pray.
Amuria...
...she was a fighter, too.
But her prayers blessed many people.
The people looked to her.
The priestesses will protect us, right?
The priestesses will defeat all the bad guys!
That's right... so you must be patient, little ones.
Okay!
That's a good child.
Sibylla-sama...
I'm so sorry. I didn't think you would be here...
I don't mind.
Neviril and Aaeru are blessing the people below.
Yes, I know.
To think that Aaeru's participating, eh?
Really!
I would have expected you to be the first to do that.
Yes. That's true.
Mamiina...
I think she belongs by your side, Yun.
Why me?
I don't really understand why,
but I feel that you should have this.
So...
Hmm?
Yun, would you take care of Mamiina for me from now on?
I understand.
I never thought that you would keep something secret from me.
Neither did I.
I just don't understand what you want any more!
What I want, eh?
Emergency!
Guys, it's an emergency!
Neviril!
Aaeru!
Neviril! It seems that they're pushing for another peace treaty.
Yes, I heard about it from Floe.
Is this information reliable?
Yes, Sibylla Neviril.
Guragief...
Were you the one who told her?
Only a handful of people know of this.
I decided that you deserved to be told.
I see.
Will the war really end this time?
I wonder.
Angulas came to us pretending to be a translator for the peace conference.
Yeah, but... maybe this time it's for real?
Yes...
It is possible that you will all be able to leave the battlefield.
Well, whatever. There's nothing we can really do about it.
Yes, you're right.
We can only do... what we can.
Guragief, about our operational plan...
Sibylla Aurea!
Oh?
A little while ago, Paraietta said the very same thing.
...and we'll help with that, too.
Is that so?
To guard against incursions from the mountain sector,
I'd like to send out rotating patrols.
I understand we're in the middle of a crisis, but...
The Arcus Prima is so big!
Yes.
To think that the Arcus Niger, a ship of the same class, has gone down.
It's shocking. Almost unbelievable.
Yes, indeed.
It's almost as hard to believe as you and Guragief fighting with each other!
You're aware of that?
You both have strong feelings... that you're unwilling to concede.
Guragief is... too earnest.
Yes, he sure can be.
It's a shame that you both decided to be men.
Anubituf...
You should patch things up with Guragief as quickly as you can.
You never know when your time will be up.
Yes.
I have to get back to the ship!
Para-sama!
Hurry, Kaimu.
But why are they attacking us again?
Like they say, "they won't quit until we make them."
Let's go!
Para-sama!
Cast off the moonrings!
Casting off the moonrings!
Up ship! Climb at full speed!
Ascending at full speed!
Situation report!
Seven o'clock high! Five ancient Simoun approaching!
Eleven o'clock level, several Argentine medium fighters!
Ready the Simoun for immediate takeoff!
Yes, sir!
Where are the priestesses from Chor Tempest?
They're not here yet, sir.
What?
What are you waiting for, Anubituf?
Order Chor Tempest to sortie!
The enemy is almost upon us!
Captain?
Ignore him.
Anubituf!
Send word for the sibyllae to stand by on the port flight deck.
I'll give their orders to them in person.
Yes, sir!
Guragief, I need to ask you to take over here.
The Arcus Prima will be the second wave of our attack.
I'll leave you to direct our offensive from above.
Understood.
Until the Captain returns, I have the conn!
Sir!
What are they doing? Go! Fly!
Our orders are to stand by on the port flight deck.
What in the world?
Damn that Anubituf! What is that sly bastard plotting?
That geezer is so freakin' annoying!
Standing by at a time like this!
Sorry for making you wait, Sibyllae.
Wait, are you...!
Surprised?
Even though it may not look like it,
I used to be a sibylla, just like all of you.
Then you're going to fly a Simile?
Yes. We have only five Simoun with which to intercept the enemy attack.
I shall fly a Simile, and issue orders directly to you all from the sky.
I will need you to follow those orders.
Yes, sir!
Understood!
Sibylla Morinas, how is your wound?
It's been very carefully treated. Everything is fine, sir!
What?
G-Get a Simile ready, now!
Yes, sir!
Sibyllae, a word if you please.
We have dragged you into this war... and that must come to an end.
I very much regret that we have not been able to do so.
Thank you, Captain Anubituf.
No matter what happens, I shall never forget your words.
Nah, you guys don't need to worry!
We already decided, didn't we?
What we can do now...
...we will do with all our might!
We are drastically outnumbered.
We shall pull them towards us as much as we can, dive rapidly, and then hit them hard.
The course of the battle will be decided by this first attack!
Here we go!
Follow me!
All batteries, fire at will!
They're running away!
Go to hell, suckers!
Right?
Right.
We showed those losers.
The two of you, watch your mouths!
Y-You heard us?
Of course not! We were just talking about you two, and figured that you were probably saying something filthy.
You're terrible!
Good work, everyone.
Hey! What's going on?
Yes, do tell!
Probably another inane comment from Floe, eh?
Yeah, that's likely, isn't it, Para-sama?
Hey!
I didn't say anything like that!
Is Chor Tempest always like this?
Alti's the one who always—
What? Floe!
I suppose so.
The Captain's Simile, approaching!
All hands, salute!
Despite Chor Tempest's actions, Central Command concluded that the war was a lost cause...
...and accepted the peace treaty offered by Plumbum and Argentum a few days later.
Next Episode
As Alliance soldiers take control of the Arcus Prima,
Chor Tempest is disbanded.
Next time, on Simoun:
The Eternal Maiden
The Eternal Maiden.