You said it yourself that day: "Take apart a Simoun."
The only thing that's in there is a helix.
All we can understand about it is...
You do see something! What? What are you seeing?
One By One
What're those for?
I'm collecting them to make a cradle.
A cradle?
Back where I grew up, we always used to put out cradles in the springtime.
They're an offering to grant peaceful rest to the souls of those who died before their time.
That one's too thick.
How is Dominura?
I don't know what could have left her in that state, but...
Limone, it would be good for you to stay by her side.
Why?
Out of all of us, you're the one closest to her.
It's Aaeru!
Neviril, did anything happen?
No, nothing.
We were unable to find the enemy base ship.
I don't know why they've gone, but...
Nothing else happened?
No.
What?
C'mon.
Tell me, what was it that Dominura saw?
I was right.
We should not have touched such sacred things.
I should not have touched them...
As you wish. I'll never let you touch them again!
It's warm...
You should rest till tomorrow.
But...
Since Dominura is...
Well...
What's happening?
We've sighted the enemy at 11 o'clock.
They don't seem to be attacking, but—
And Dominura?
I regret to say that she remains indisposed.
Please excuse me!
Let's go, Paraietta.
Let's go, Neviril!
What?
Hold it.
Neviril is exhausted.
She's in no condition to pray right now.
But...
With Dominura unable to pray as well, for now you'll be taking orders from me.
"Orders?"
It's like we're in the military.
Okay, I understand.
We're only continuing our reconnaissance. There's no reason for Neviril to go.
Kaimu!
Okay.
I can't believe Aaeru just gave up back there.
Yes, I was quite taken aback by that.
Yeah, in the past she'd've dragged her off by the hand, right?
Bleah! I don't want to see Aaeru like this!
Aaeru, you know...
She's cool because she's so positive that it's overbearing!
Being so weirdly considerate... it's totally not like her.
Are you jealous?
H-Huh? What are you talking about?
I don't feel that way about Aaeru!
Oh, Limone, where's Aaeru?
Hmm? I just saw her go outside, but...
Outside, huh?
I wonder what she could be doing?
Who knows?
Huh?
Don't get the wrong idea!
I was just thinking that I'd take a shower or something.
No one asked you anything.
Sheesh!
I'm sorry.
Why are you apologizing?
Huh?
You don't even know why you're apologizing.
You're just bowing your head for no reason.
I do have a reason!
It's my fault that you're feeling bad.
I don't understand why, but...
I just know it's because of me.
So—
Don't you dare be so conceited!
Floe?
That was so uncool!
Please forgive my impertinence, Sibylla Aurea.
That was insolent of me.
They are the same...
What?
Amuria and that girl.
She was never looking at me.
Yes.
Aaeru made me see the truth.
To both of them I am just...
Just a tool. A tool to take them "higher."
Neviril...
I think... I've made a big mistake.
If I were with you—
Stop!
I'm not the person you think I am.
What?
If you say what I think you're going to...
...then I know...
...that my shell will break.
You're very tired.
You're not really yourself right now. So—
I'm so sorry.
How could I say such things?
I'm so sorry, Paraietta.
I'm so sorry!
Neviril...
Again?
I'll go, too.
No, you mustn't!
But—
Neviril.
I'll go!
The air around here really stinks.
The air?
Is that okay, Alti?
Well, if Floe really wants to...
Mamiina, Rodoreamon, back them up.
Understood.
I wonder...
Aaeru?
Yun and the others haven't come back yet.
The enemy isn't attacking, so to just go out without a plan like that—
Are you saying I made a bad decision?
I didn't say that!
I can't always be by your side,
but I can still try to protect you.
Neviril.
Quiet, isn't it?
You're not going to go look at the Simoun today?
Huh? Well, no.
Hey, wanna play hide-and-seek?
That's kid stuff!
How about it, Aaeru?
Sure! Sounds fun.
All right, Morinas, count to a hundred!
Don't be cheating on us, okay?
Yeah, yeah. Here I go!
1... 2... 3... 4... 5...
Hide, Limone!
6... 7... 8... 9... 10...
This way!
The clouds still shine white
In the blackness of the shadows.
The red light of the fires...
That song...
It's the same as Aaeru's music box!
"The Door to a New World."
Huh?!
It's the song of the migrants, who were searching for a land of peace.
Tempus Spatium took us in when we had been wandering without rest.
Chor Dextra was created to perform the Emerald Ri Maajon.
We were warriors chosen in the knowledge that we would die...
...and I was fine with that.
In exchange for my death, the Holy Land gave my life meaning.
I wanted to be needed.
I always have. Always!
That's why...
You are needed!
I want to do the Emerald Ri Maajon.
I want to do it with you, Dominura.
Why?
Because... you're my pair.
Sibylla Paraietta!
The rain is getting worse.
Please, come back inside before it affects your health.
What is it?
Do you need to talk to Dominura?
No.
Why am I so indecisive?
When I'm like this, I...
Neviril...
Again?
You know, this is very weird.
Maybe it's better to wait until Dominura comes back?
Are you saying we can't do anything without her giving instructions?
Hey, this is no time to be petty.
"Petty," you say?
You know, if we keep on like this...
Aaeru!
You're going to pair with me.
What?
You and I are going to go on a reconnaissance mission.
And from now on—
No.
I'll be the one to go.
Neviril?
Morinas, you're with me.
Huh? Me?
Neviril, no! You're still—
Please, let me go, Paraietta.
I'm...
worthless.
What should we do about our game?
She's going to die.
Huh?
Dominura.
What?
Those are the eyes of someone who's about to die.
Limone...
Dominura!
Dominura, I want to hear your advice on this matter.
What do you think about the situation?
Dominura!
Beats me.
Is your judgement so unreliable that you'd rather listen to someone who's been asleep?
Dominura...
More, please.
The Emerald Ri Maajon.
By dismantling the Simoun,
I feel as though I saw what lies beyond it.
But you don't know if you really saw it?
Until you actually do it, you won't know for sure.
It certainly seems like it, doesn't it?
You were always told to fly higher, weren't you?
To draw Ri Maajons in the heavens.
So to deny you that would be to deny you your very self.
You know, we're so much alike.
I chose you,
and you chose me.
That connection is what creates the Ri Maajon.
Just for you, I want to draw...
...the Emerald Ri Maajon.
Next Episode
The Messis comes under an all-out attack from the Archipelago's fighters.
Next time, on Simoun:
The Emerald Ri Maajon
The Emerald Ri Maajon.