The countless flowers,
enveloped in light…
…gaze at tomorrow
with unwavering eyes.
Everyone wishes for me to be pure…
…but what can I bring
with me to the frayed skies?
What I’ve made my own
by breaking off flowers in bloom…
All such sinful things…
Why did I stop making
promises with the future?
Because even if I try
to run far from all the pain…
…a cold wind rustles
my hair… Don’t you see?
Where can I ever find the answer?
The Door to a New World
How dare they do that
right in front of us?
This is exactly why I was against disbanding Chor Rubor and Chor Caput!
Chor Tempest can’t be the
only ones we can depend on.
Gather all the troops and the Simile!
The reconnaissance Simile and the cruising Simile! All of them!
Yes, sir!
What foolishness!
I hope you realize that fighting leads absolutely nowhere.
Onashia…
Wow, look at that!
Come on, look!
I am!
Over here, hurry up!
I said no playing on the Simoun!
Huh? Why not?
Yeah, why?
Well… because…
Ummm…
Wow!
What is it?
“Booooou…!”
It’s making a noise!
Like, “booooou!”
No way!
Wow, it is!
Like, “booooou!”
It sounds like a flute!
C’mon! You too, Limone!
Well, well?
“Booooou…”
That’s what it sounds like.
Maybe there’s something inside!
I see.
So the day has come.
Would you give us
a little more time, please?
Would it be okay for us to come after we’ve finished our meal?
Did the meeting end badly?
Onashia is the symbol of
the Simulacrum Theocracy.
I’m sure the authorities have been enjoying her continuing silence.
But if she decides to act…
I take no pleasure in warfare. However…
To bring her here
for a reason like this…
I can’t fathom what
Her Eminence is thinking.
Guragief.
If I should…
Nothing.
Never in history has anyone flown out in a Simoun without orders!
Have you no sense of responsibility?
Responsibility?
Our responsibility as Simoun sibyllae…
…to take pride in what we are.
I believe we all do.
Is that all, sir?
In that case, please excuse us.
Why, those little…!
Paraietta?
Vyura!
And… Rodoreamon and Alti as well?
You too, Paraietta?
Couldn’t sleep, eh?
Same here.
Para-sama!
Hey, it looks like everyone’s here.
The Messis will bear
Onashia to her destination.
Sibylla Neviril, Sibylla Aaeru.
Would you care to accompany her?
And would you like to know
about… another world?
Could I also…
…come along?
Um…
No. We’d be too many.
Please.
Is it good?
Um…
Good…
…isn’t the word I’d use.
It’s bitter.
Kind of, I think.
And it’s sweet too… I guess.
But it’s not a taste I really hate.
I think…
…I can finish eating it.
“Dunno.”
You never say that any more, Limone.
Yes.
I realized that if I really think about something,
there isn’t much I don’t understand.
That’s why…
I’m the opposite.
The more I think,
the more confused I become.
Dominura?
Well, we should get going
as soon as we’ve finished eating.
Where to?
Dunno.
Her Eminence has ordered us
to avoid “flying recklessly.”
I wonder where we’re going?
Yes?
Excuse me…
Onashia-sama is currently resting.
It’s all right.
Onashia.
I wonder how “another world”
is connected with all this?
I feel really uneasy
around the High Priestess.
The Defence Minister is kind of a bastard, but Her Eminence…
How should I put it?
What?
Your hands…
They’re so small.
Stop treating me like a kid!
This war… it makes such
obvious things hard to see.
Onashia…
You have something
you wish to ask me.
You told me that you
can hear Mamiina’s voice.
If so… what about my comrades?
Have their souls been set free?
You are the one who wants
to be set free, aren’t you?
You keep trying to live close to the time
and place where your friends died.
Yet at the same time, you long to escape
to a place far away from there.
Onashia-sama.
It seems we have arrived.
Why have we come to the Ruins?
It’s doing it again.
“The Door to a New World.”
It’s the melody played
by that music box.
And the unintended destination
of those who perished here.
Yes.
This place was once the training
ground for Chor Dextra.
Chor… Dextra?
Sibylla Aaeru, your grandfather was the regina of that choir.
Grandpa… was the regina?
Can I ask you something?
Yes.
What happened back then?
When do you mean?
On the Messis.
Everything just poured into me…
When I looked inside the helical motor,
it was as though I saw someone’s…
…or something’s memories.
The only thing in there is a helix.
All we can understand about it is…
Sibylla Dominura?
Dominura?
We became obsessed with
Ri Maajons… with the Simoun.
But that was because the Simoun were all that we could rely on.
Yes. If the Simoun had never
existed in the first place…
Or if they had existed,
but no one had been around to explain how they worked, what would have happened?
Huh? Well…
Ummm…
Well…
Uhh…
We brought them! They’re here!
A long, long time ago…
…there was a civilization
vastly more advanced than ours.
It is said that the Simoun
are relics from those days.
But an unending series of wars
broke out, and left the world in ruins.
With everything destroyed,
the land became worthless,
and further war became pointless.
The Simoun were of no use
to the starving masses,
and the reason for their
existence was forgotten.
The people could do nothing more than wait for death to claim them.
And then, from the sky, it is said that
a Simoun came flying from another world.
Within it rode a pair of maidens, descending from heaven.
Those girls…
They introduced themselves
as “Simoun sibyllae.”
And then…
…they shared the secret
of the Emerald Ri Maajon.
The Emerald Ri Maajon?
Yes.
Another world—
No.
Another time, that’s where the ultimate Ri Maajon can take you.
It is a divine gift that we have been granted, a great “what if?”.
If the people of that time had been told
that there would be another war…
If the Simoun didn’t exist,
perhaps I wouldn’t exist, either.
If, at that time, someone had explained to the people the need for the Simoun…
But if I didn’t exist,
then this pain I feel
wouldn’t exist either.
…then our present, with all its extreme distress and poverty, might change.
By travelling through time and space…
…we can take this
“what if?” to another age.
That is the purpose of the Simoun,
and of the Emerald Ri Maajon.
“Travelling through time and space?”
Unbelievable! How could…
Wait! This “Chor Dextra”
that Grandpa commanded…?
Chor Dextra was a choir created specifically to complete the Emerald Ri Maajon.
Someone you all know very well once belonged to that choir.
Sibylla Dominura.
She is the only surviving
member of Chor Dextra.
Dominura?
Yes. I finally realized…
…that everything happened
because I started it!
I…
I’ve been thinking about what you said earlier, Dominura.
“What if the Simoun didn’t exist?”
If they had never existed?
Yes.
Then I would never have met
everyone in Chor Tempest.
And I wouldn’t have met
you either, Dominura.
Why are you crying?
Why indeed?
U-ummm…
Because you’re sad?
Because you’re lonely?
Because it hurts?
What else…
Ummm…
Because you’re… happy?
That’s right.
I’m happy!
Let’s go.
You still don’t know
where we will go?
No.
Now I know.
Under the blue sky.
Beyond the white clouds.
It’s as blue as a tear.
As white as a lily.
In the pitch-black darkness.
The light of a red flame.
Sibylla Dominura has probably completed the Emerald Ri Maajon.
Then that means…
…that she is alive,
in some other time.
Sibylla Dominura and
Sibylla Limone are alive?
I am certain of it.
Then…
…Amuria too…?
Does that mean…
…Amuria could be alive as well?
The Emerald Ri Maajon is the one hope
given to us by Tempus Spatium.
Whether it takes you into the future or into the past is beyond anyone’s control.
However, the Simoun exist through the will of Tempus Spatium.
And it is not likely
that the gods would err.
Tempus Spatium will undoubtedly open the door to the right time.
Sibylla Neviril, Sibylla Aaeru.
I want to entrust this to you:
The Emerald Ri Maajon.
Hurry!
A Simoun from the Arcus Niger?
Minister!
What is the meaning of this?
The Arcus Niger…
…has fallen.
Seven o’clock high!
Five ancient Simoun, closing in fast!
What?
It is played by my wounds…
the song of prayer.
Let it ring out over
the grieving universe.
Can we change tomorrow?
Don’t be afraid.
I want to let you know
how my heart’s overflowing.
“I want to get closer to you.”
“I want to feel your pulse.”
I was too defiant,
and I took the long way around.
The blue moon is swaying silently.
My true heart’s desire is you.
I can’t reach you.
My tears of pain trickle down.
Soar away into the
sky, song of prayer.
Carrying my love that came too late.
What can I do to change tomorrow?
Just hold on to “now” the way it is…
Next Episode
The allied forces of Plumbum and Argentum attack the Holy Land in greater numbers than ever before.
Next time, on Simoun:
Sortie
Sortie.