The countless flowers,
enveloped in light…
…gaze at tomorrow
with unwavering eyes.
Everyone wishes for me to be pure…
…but what can I bring
with me to the frayed skies?
What I’ve made my own
by breaking off flowers in bloom…
All such sinful things…
Why did I stop making
promises with the future?
Because even if I try
to run far from all the pain…
…a cold wind rustles
my hair… Don’t you see?
Where can I ever find the answer?
Neviril! We need to be stronger!
Neviril, don’t look! If you see their eyes,
you won’t be able to kill them!
Neviril!
Amuria?
Amuria!
Wounds and Pain
Hey, Alti, let’s follow
those birds! Come on!
We’re in the middle
of a mission right now.
Oh, who cares about that?
It’s not like the enemy’s around, anyway.
We’re only out here
because they’re paranoid.
I suppose…
They’ve been flying for
a long time, haven’t they?
I wonder how far they’re going?
It’s not like they’ve been
flying the whole time.
They rest their wings
when they get tired,
and they have to eat sometime, right?
What on earth are they doing?
We’re in the middle of a mission!
It seems like everyone’s
been really distracted lately.
Yeah, I know.
Even though we finally managed to get put back on duty, everyone’s still a little out of it.
Even Aaeru isn’t flying right now.
Para-sama?
Hm?
How’s the Sibylla Aurea
been doing lately?
The same, huh…
Does that worry you?
Not really.
I just don’t like the feeling of being somehow incomplete.
And I’m starting to get used
to the others being gone.
I guess we can’t go back to being the old Chor Tempest after all, can we?
Para-sama, I’ve only ever
had my eyes on you, so…
Just kidding.
Come along, Limone.
We’re going to the pool now.
I’m not going.
You have to!
You’re still small, so you need to build up your stamina—
I’m hungry.
What? Limone!
You come back here this instant!
Why…
Why don’t we all sit down
and eat together first?
Is something wrong,
Sibylla Paraietta?
Isn’t this… the Sibylla Aurea’s?
She’s still being repaired.
We’ve had to rebuild her
almost from the ground up,
and it’s been hard to get
all the parts we’ve needed.
Your wounds still
haven’t healed, have they?
It’s been a long time
since you’ve flown.
Neviril! Hey, Neviril!
Instead of hiding in there all the time, pull yourself together and get out here!
Because you haven’t come back,
Chor Tempest only gets sent
on pointless missions!
We can’t go on like this!
And we can’t fly
if we’re stuck in here!
Do you hear me, Neviril?
Neviril!
Why, that pig-headed…
I swear, what a childish thing to do.
I suppose I’m in no position to talk…
I’m sorry.
You really didn’t need to do that.
No, it’s all right.
Really, Aaeru is such a troublesome girl.
She must be getting on your nerves.
Should I make her stop?
However, that might
require drastic measures.
Neviril.
Don’t you think it’s time
you made a decision?
About what?
Whatever you’re going to do. Things can’t go on like this.
Are you going to come
back to the choir or not?
If you intend to go to the Spring,
then this time, I will go with you.
I’m sorry.
I still don’t know.
Whether to go to the Spring, or to keep flying the Simoun,
I still can’t decide.
But…
I realize I have to make a decision.
But… whichever choice I make, it feels like it will be a betrayal.
A betrayal?
That’s the feeling I get.
Of Amuria?
Neviril.
I have been at your side
ever since we were children.
I’ve walked beside you all this time.
That is why I can tell you this:
you are meant to fly a Simoun,
even if that means betraying Amuria.
Don’t talk about it
like you understand!
It’s not that simple.
Get out.
So that’s how it is.
She just doesn’t give an inch, does she?
Even though you’ve been
so worried about her.
But why doesn’t she try
to understand how you feel?
I can’t stand Neviril
when she’s like this.
Don’t talk about her
like you understand.
I do understand.
Isn’t she basically just
acting like a spoiled child?
That’s not it.
Then what is it?
I mean, I know losing Amuria
has been hard for her,
but she’s not the only one
who misses her, you know?
Shutting herself away like that is just a big pain for everyone around her.
Kaimu.
I’m sorry. I went too far.
Para-sama?
What happened to your nails?
Oh, I was just doing a little cleaning.
You can’t just leave them like that!
I know! Wait a minute, okay?
O-Okay.
Well, it looks like
they’re starting to sparkle.
Aren’t they?
Since you have such beautiful nails, you have to take good care of them.
Tempus Spatium-sama
will scold you if you don’t.
You look like you’re having fun.
It’s because I can do something
to help you, Para-sama.
And I get to touch you while I do it…
Just kidding!
I think… she’s probably lonely.
Everyone must be.
Everyone on board…
…is probably lonely.
I’m sorry.
Hey, Para-sama…
Are you lonely?
Does my face give it away?
That’s not it.
It’s just that… I’m lonely, too.
Para-sama…
My, isn’t it hot in here?
Then shall we go someplace cooler?
Still no change from our princess?
Unfortunately not.
Well, this certainly
brings back memories.
Does she remind you of anyone?
It’s hardly uncommon for a sibylla to have doubts about flying.
I reached out to you
back then, as I recall.
I haven’t forgotten.
Still more of you coming?
Hmpf! I’m not afraid
of an attack like that!
If you think you can hit us,
go ahead and try!
Ah, Para-sama! Enemy to starboard!
Fire the machine guns!
Hurry!
Here goes!
You’re incredible, Para-sama!
Not a single miss!
Here come more of them,
through the clouds!
Stingray Ri Maajon!
Kaimu…
Hey, Para-sama…
Let’s do a Ri Maajon.
It’s funny.
We do this all the time, but…
Oh, no, we have to shut it off, or…
Kaimu!
Nee-san…
Kaimu-nee-san…
We were always together.
I decided I’d stay with her forever.
Being with her seemed like the most natural thing in the world.
I was conceited.
I thought I was the only one
who could take care of her.
I thought that was obvious.
I wasn’t the only one
who was hurt back then.
Maybe that’s why…
Para-sama?
We should stop.
But why?
Because you’re still a child, Kaimu.
What? I’m not a child!
Yes, you are.
I am not!
All of us are children.
That’s why, when we try
to heal each other’s wounds,
we just end up inflicting more.
I’m leaving now. Good night, Kaimu.
Why…?
Why can’t you understand, Para-sama?
Neviril! Neviril!
Just listen to me for a minute!
Neviril?
Neviril!
That does it. Stubborn or not,
I’m going to drag you out myself!
Paraietta?
Aaeru, we need to talk.
Huh?
Somehow, I get the feeling that talking isn’t what you had in mind.
Didn’t you know?
The Maaju Pool can
also be used for this!
So, why do I have to do this with you?
Here I come!
Amuria isn’t the only reason
Neviril is refusing to make a decision.
I understand now.
She was thinking about me as well!
Neviril, I’m sorry.
I didn’t understand anything.
But at least let me tell you this.
I haven’t ever felt
that you betrayed me!
I’m grateful that
you worried about me.
So…
So I’ll entrust you to someone who could be
even better for you than Amuria!
What the…?
Over here!
Gotcha!
What!?
Had enough?
Aaeru, you have to become Neviril’s pair!
You don’t need to tell me that!
Hey, Floe?
What?
What do you suppose
happens to them after that?
What are you talking about?
Birds that rest their wings.
You said they couldn’t
keep flying forever.
They’ll start flying again, of course.
Is that so?
Yeah. Flying through the sky is what they’re born to do, after all.
What they’re born to do…
If they’re just resting
their wings, then that’s fine.
But a bird that’s too badly hurt to fly…
…won’t be able to go on living.
It is played by my wounds…
the song of prayer.
Let it ring out over
the grieving universe.
Can we change tomorrow?
Don’t be afraid.
I want to let you know
how my heart’s overflowing.
“I want to get closer to you.”
“I want to feel your pulse.”
I was too defiant,
and I took the long way around.
The blue moon is swaying silently.
My true heart’s desire is you.
I can’t reach you.
My tears of pain trickle down.
Soar away into the sky, song of prayer.
Carrying my love that came too late.
What can I do to change tomorrow?
Just hold on to “now” the way it is…
Next Episode
In order to sign a ceasefire agreement,
Highlander diplomats come aboard the Arcus Prima.
Next time, on Simoun:
Over International Waters