Nearby War
...and that concludes the patrol flight schedule.
Chor Tempest?
Did they have permission to take off?
We're going to keep flying?
Weren't you the one who said that if we didn't fly a Simoun together,
we wouldn't know whether we were compatible or not?
This is plenty!
You're amazing, Aaeru.
So can't we—
We haven't done a Ri Maajon yet.
Let's do the Stingray Ri Maajon.
Way to go, Aaeru!
Morinas!
I don't get it! It's too confusing!
Morinas, concentrate!
I know!
Wait, wait...
I thought I ordered Chor Tempest to stand down until the rest of the new recruits arrive, Sibylla Aaeru.
If we don't practice while we can, we won't be ready for the real thing.
Then we'll really be in trouble.
Then use a Simile—and get permission first!
Aaeru! Morinas!
Why were you offering prayers without permission?
That was no prayer.
We were training for battle.
Why are you yelling at us, Paraietta?
You're not Chor Tempest's regina.
Our choir's regina, Neviril, is not feeling well.
Until she recovers, I am acting in her stead.
Oh?
Do Paraietta and the Sibylla Aurea have that kind of special relationship?
Aaeru! You forgot something!
A kiss of gratitude, to thank Tempus Spatium after a Simoun flight.
I don't care about stuff like that.
You don't like doing it with me?
Wapourif... I'm sorry.
I hope they don't get mad at you too.
When a sibylla tells us to let her fly, letting her fly is part of our job.
Awfully cold, isn't she?
She's just a kid. You don't have to tease her.
Tease her?
What do you mean?
But you know...
Flying with her was sooo wonderful...
Aaeru!
That was great, Aaeru!
Which Ri Maajon were you trying to do?
Aaeru, please don't do things like that any more.
Why?
Is everyone really okay with the way things are right now?
When is Chor Tempest going to rejoin the other choirs on the shift rotation?
If things don't change...
If they don't, we'll just go back to being regular Simoun sibyllae,
offering prayers and waiting for our turn to visit the Spring.
When my day comes, I'm going to choose to become a man.
I can't wait! Can you, Nee-san?
I'm also planning to become a man, Alti.
Is that how you all feel?
That it's okay if you never go into battle?
Looks like Chor Rubor has returned safely again...
You were trying to do the Stingray Ri Maajon, weren't you?
Spoken like a true prodigy!
You couldn't even pull off a simple thing like that.
Is this really Chor Tempest?
Are you like the rest of them, Neviril?
D'you think it's fine if you never go to battle or something?
There isn't a person alive who likes war, is there?
Aaeru, we only want to perform our duties as priestesses in service to Tempus Spatium.
Then get out here and perform them!
I'll tell you this, Aaeru.
You and I will never be a pair.
I'm Vyura, from Chor Rubor.
They said I'm to room with you starting today.
I see.
I'm Aaeru, from Chor Tempest.
You're s'posed to be an auriga, right?
Same as me.
You know, for the longest time, Neviril has been—
Look, since Chor Tempest has been off duty,
our choir has been split into two shifts,
and we've been flying patrols around the clock.
We're in no position to slack off and play around like you.
Just let me sleep.
I could show you the kind of flying that would satisfy even you.
Maybe you could.
C'mon, then!
If we go now, then everyone should be in the cafeteria.
But...
It's be fine.
If it's dinner you're worried about, I brought plenty.
That's not the problem!
What a pain.
Here, this is your share.
And one more thing...
Let's go.
Which Ri Maajon shall we start with?
Which ones do you like?
I don't know...
There's got to be something, right?
The Silver Ri Maajon, I guess...
Yeah, that's a good one!
But since we're going to all this trouble anyway, let's go find the enemy before we do it.
You're planning to get into a fight?
If we do, they can't keep our choir off duty forever, right?
You think so?
Aaeru!
Isn't that...
Yeah.
It's a Simoun.
The ones on patrol right now are the reservists from Chor Caput, right?
What would they be doing down there?
They might have been attacked by the enemy.
Then they'll have information about the enemy.
Let's make sure that the area is secure first.
There's only one of them!
Fortune is smiling on me.
This will be my final—
It was Aaeru after all!
And this time she took Limone with her!
Limone?
But she's my pair...
I got dumped, too.
It's not really about being dumped...
Flying without permission again?
Must be nice to be in a choir with so much free time.
Chor Tempest is going to get dissolved for this.
Looks like we're going to get busier.
Shouldn't we report this to the dux?
If we don't bring them back, we'll all be held responsible.
Why don't we just leave them be?
If they want to fly, then let them.
They're sure to be back by morning, right?
The Arcus Prima can't go anywhere at the moment regardless.
Just what kind of priestess is this Aaeru, anyway?
All I'm sure of is that she has a good reason.
A good reason for being here, that is.
A fake?
Limone!
Aaeru!
You bastard...!
That's right, we're Simoun sibyllae.
The pollution is eating into our bodies.
We need new technologies.
The secret of the Simoun, kept hidden by the Theocracy...
If we can obtain that...
...we can say goodbye to this technology that poisons our skies.
I've done it!
I've captured a Simoun!
I'm not just going to retire from the military...
Glory to the Archipelago!
I'm telling you, it won't work!
You Islanders don't have the divine protection of Tempus Spatium!
The only ones who can pilot a Simoun are priestesses who haven't gone to the Spring!
Those like us, who haven't chosen whether to be male or female!
Aaeru, what are we going to do?
Take back our Simoun.
Keep your voice down!
It's not like he can understand us.
The Archipelago wants our Simoun,
because a Simoun is the only machine that can move through the sky with complete freedom.
But we're not going to let them have it.
Aaeru...
My friends have all gone to the Spring.
I'm the only one from my village who hasn't gone.
Why don't you want to go?
Because I don't know what to choose.
Do I want to become a man, or stay a woman?
If you can't decide, Onashia can decide for you.
It's even worse if someone decides for me!
No! No way! Absolutely not!
I can't afford to make any mistakes right now!
I have to become the best Simoun sibylla of them all,
because as long as I fly a Simoun,
I won't have to go to the Spring.
Hey, young ladies,
how does it feel?
To be neither a man nor a woman?
Even if I ask, you can't understand me, can you?
Hormones and surgery made me male right after I was born.
That's how it's always done in the Archipelago.
So, I don't understand...
Being born with a female body,
and being able to decide for yourself whether to become a man or a woman,
what's it like?
Is he... sick?
Move, damn it! Fly! Please!
What the hell is wrong with you, you demon? Why won't you fly?
I'm sorry, ladies...
I can't give this back.
It's mine.
If I can just get this home, it will mean...
The skies... will clear...
I have to... no matter what...
I told you, you can't make the Simoun fly.
His Islander friends might come to pick him up, using their aircraft...
I won't hand the Simoun over to them, ever.
Help me get him out.
We need to hurry back.
He's gotten really stiff...
Let go, let go, let go!
Stop it! You're going to break something!
Someone will probably come looking for us.
When they get here, they'll be able to—
No.
We don't know when the enemy will show up.
We've got to get back in the air as soon as we can!
Besides, there's no way I can report that I let myself get captured.
If I cut his hands off the controls...
There's nothing else we can do, is there?
It can't be helped.
Limone, go wait over there, okay?
Hurry! Get out of here!
Limone! Limone!
Help me move him, Limone!
Are you still awake?
Limone! Limone!
I've screwed things up for you again, haven't I?
We'll do the cleanup ourselves, to apologize to you.
You don't have to do that, Sibylla Aaeru.
That's okay—we want to do it!
Limone, let's get started.
I see that they're cleaning off the Simoun by themselves.
It looks like they're starting to see themselves as priestesses.
I'm sorry for getting you so dirty.
Next Episode
Will Dominura really be able to guide Limone?
Next time, on Simoun:
White Solitude
White Solitude.