With the death of Sibylla Mamiina,
and the ancient Simoun having fallen
into the hands of the Islanders,
they’re now on an
equal footing with us.
Rather, because of their
expertise in warfare,
they are now a serious threat.
I still believe…
…it may have been reckless to send Chor Tempest out like that.
But didn’t Chor Tempest deliver a crippling blow to their airborne base?
They’ll need time
to reorganize their forces.
The enemy will be unable
to attack us any time soon.
The sibylla’s death has at least bought us some time. Is that not so?
Let me remind you that Tempus Spatium
is watching everything you do.
Elegy
Dominura… Limone…
I bet they’re dead too!
Floe…
All of them…
They all died!
It’s gonna be our turn next!
Every last one of us!
We’re gonna die, I just know it!
— You’re appalling.
— What?
War is nothing but mass murder.
If you can’t live with that, then I suggest you go to the Spring immediately.
I wonder why… it had to be Mamiina?
I can’t even cry.
When Amuria died…
Perhaps, at that moment,
my heart died with her.
I’ve been hurting everyone’s feelings,
and pushing everyone away.
But despite everything,
I can’t shed even a single tear.
I just live on with my
heart dead inside me.
Yes.
If I had died in Mamiina’s place…
The Emerald…?
Have you been here all this time?
Are you crying?
If I… had been stronger,
Mamiina wouldn’t have died.
If I’d…
No. If anyone is to blame,
it’s me. I was her pair.
It had nothing to do with you.
Don’t say it has nothing to do with me!
Aaeru…
Why are you crying?
Didn’t you tell me that
you weren’t afraid of anything?
Amuria!
That’s why we need to get stronger!
You understand, don’t you, Neviril?
We can do it.
I have to live.
I… have to live.
I have to!
But the one who lies behind me is the Simulacrum Theocracy’s most revered sibylla,
Sibylla Aurea Neviril!
She’s going to get out of here safely,
and I won’t let you lay a finger on her!
You’re right.
We must live on.
Shall I get you a drink?
“Again?”
You make it sound like
we used to be friends.
The truth is that one of us was always meant to be on top, and the other below.
That’s not true!
Sheesh, what were you
thinking back then?
I wanted to be friends…
Give me a break!
I truly want to be friends with everyone.
Mamiina!
So please stop saying “but we are friends!” and stuff like that.
I’m a little sensitive about it, okay?
I understand.
I have called for
Onashia from the Spring.
And the Defence Ministry?
As you have ordered,
they are unaware of this.
They look forward to fighting
with such eager eyes.
How terribly sad.
This world has been
defiled by hatred.
Yet they cling to this sterile land…
…and persist in their foolish desire to fight until they annihilate each other.
Now, we must not
waste any more time!
We must crawl out from
this accursed place!
We must follow the path of Tempus Spatium,
and open the door to the New World!
The New World?
Yes, and to achieve this, Anubituf,
I may have to ask a great deal of you.
To begin with, the legendary choir,
Chor Dextra, must be revived.
Our Simoun outperform it
by a small margin in several areas,
but it doesn’t look like there are any really significant differences.
Sibylla Morinas?
Is Neviril’s Simoun…?
Not yet.
Taking apart the ancient
Simoun comes first?
Everything else will
have to wait, I guess.
Not that I’m blaming you!
It’s not like you can
disobey your orders.
Actually…
I wanted to do this first, too.
Sibylla Morinas…
Won’t you please go to the Spring?
I can’t right now.
The Simoun are cursed!
I don’t really care
about the Simoun.
Sibylla…
“As long as I can fly a Simoun,
I don’t care about anything else!”
“I don’t have to care about my choirmates!” That’s what I thought until now.
Things aren’t like that any more.
You’ve changed.
You too.
Now that we’ve lost Mamiina,
I wonder if they’re gonna
rearrange our pairs again?
Yes, probably.
Unless we get another person, someone will have to be left behind.
What do you think, Para-sama?
Hey, Para-sama?
Don’t ask me.
I… don’t have the answers.
Para-sama…
How can I apologize
to Mamiina, who died?
I was so preoccupied with myself…
…that I didn’t perform properly as a member of Chor Tempest!
I’m so useless.
When did it happen?
How?
How did I sink so low?
Why?
Para-sama.
Alti?
It doesn’t matter if it’s a lie.
As long as you’re always
“Para-sama,” I mean.
It doesn’t matter if you’re wrong, so long as you make firm decisions!
I know you’re suffering too, Paraietta!
But… as long as you’re
“our gallant Para-sama,”
you give everyone hope.
When you say “everyone,”
you mean Kaimu, right?
Why do you go so far for her?
I wanted to see her smile again.
That’s why I wanted to become a man. That’s why I wanted to become stronger.
It’s all because I wanted
to make her happy.
But I realized something.
She won’t be happy as long as
I keep getting in her way.
That being the case,
there’s only one thing I can do.
For my sister’s sake,
I will distance myself from her.
Paraietta-sama!
Sibylla Floe is—!
Floe?
What is it?
Floe!
Floe! What are you doing
with that suitcase?
I’m leaving!
— What do you mean, leaving?
— I’m going to the Spring!
Don’t bother trying to stop me!
I want nothing to do
with this “war” thing!
And I have no intention to die!
Hey, wait! Let’s talk this
over with everyone first.
Rodoreamon…
Isn’t that…?
What the hell?
Isn’t that… a reconnaissance Simile?
Where are they going
at this time of night?
Mamiina!
Sibylla Mamiina’s remains are being sent
to the lands where she was raised.
Why? Why did you…?
Those are Her Eminence’s wishes.
To console Sibylla Mamiina’s spirit,
it was her belief that she should be returned
to the land which was dear to her.
But that could have been done after her funeral
was performed here, on the Arcus Prima!
You’re absolutely right.
She died honourably,
as befits a Simoun sibylla.
It should have been our duty
to give her a proper burial.
Died… honourably?
Enter.
Vyura?
Sibylla Vyura.
In place of Mamiina, she will now be piloting a Simoun with you.
What?
We will have to reorganize
the pairs immediately.
We will choose the pairs which can create the strongest Ri Maajons…
Minister!
We have just lost
our beloved comrade!
To perform any Ri Maajon,
our spirits must be clear.
It is an act performed
with the purity of the mind!
We’re still—
What a carefree thing to say!
What?
Do you want Sibylla Mamiina’s
sacrifice to go to waste?
You’re…
It’s terrible!
I can’t believe they won’t
even let us say goodbye!
The Defence Minister’s
just like that, too.
The war is all he thinks about.
They don’t care about
Mamiina’s death at all!
Mamiina… She didn’t come
from a sibylla family.
Mamiina was right!
I really am just “Her Little Ladyship!”
Mamiina’s feelings…
I wanted to understand them!
But…
I didn’t understand at all!
You wish to understand?
Yun?
Mamiina’s feelings are right here.
Sibylla Mamiina’s soul is here.
Her soul accepts the end of her life.
What?
To her, her death had meaning.
You…
You must not touch Onashia-sama!
Bring it forth.
Yes, milady.
Accepts the end of her life?
I hate things like that!
Floe…
Is it supposed to
make us feel better?
How can anyone know
how the dead feel?
Rodoreamon?
You know…
I always envied
those braids of yours.
But this…
…was the way your parents
told you to do it.
It wasn’t something that
a child would have understood.
It was just Her Little Ladyship’s hairstyle.
Back then, I…
I just wanted to truly be friends with Mamiina. That’s why I…
Wh-What in the world are you doing?
That’s why I…
She honestly wanted to be
friends with everyone.
Mamiina!
Mamiina is a Simoun sibylla!
Yes!
And Simoun sibyllae
aren’t just here to fight!
Right!
Rodoreamon!
Let’s go!
If everyone’s going,
won’t you need another pair?
Vyura!
Everyone else from
Chor Rubor went to the Spring.
Why do you think I stayed behind?
For the same reason as Mamiina!
It’s because I wanted
to stay a Simoun sibylla.
Vyura, thank you!
Sibylla!
Please!
How dare they?
Who is responsible for
this insubordination?
What are they doing, in the middle of a state of emergency?
We’ll start off with Mamiina’s specialty,
the Ri Maajon of the Raging Sea!
Roger!
Next, let’s do the Dandelion Ri Maajon!
So this is who we are…
Yes!
Yeah! We’re…!
Aa… eru.
Sibyllae!
We draw our prayers
upon the heavens.
Sibyllae.
For the tomorrows
that will never cease,
and for the yesterdays which have already been spun, we offer our prayers!
Sibyllae…
Yes.
We are!
Next Episode
Tempus Spatium grants
us another possibility.
Next time, on Simoun:
The Door to a New World.
The Door to a New World