I'm still not certain, either.
To be a priestess, and to go out and fight...
Is that really right?
You and I are completely different in every way.
But in one respect, we're just the same.
Stand up, Aaeru.
I am your pair.
Everyone, to the port hangar! Hurry!
Hurry!
Got it!
Mamiina, let's go!
Our Simoun is waiting.
That's what we're here for, isn't it?
The Hearing
They took my sister hostage.
I'll make them suffer for that!
I can't bear to see everyone's feelings torn apart again!
Are you scared?
I'm not scared at all!
Well, I'm scared.
C'mon, let's hurry.
The one way Neviril and I are the same...
What could it be?
Oh well, it doesn't matter.
Whatever it is, from now on I'm Neviril's pair!
Try to level the ship off for a moment! The Simoun are taking off!
But Rubor and Caput were both destroyed!
It's Chor Tempest that's launching!
Did you hear that?
While Chor Tempest is taking off, bring the ship level and return fire!
Don't worry about your aim!
Just pour it into them!
Is this...?
Yes, it was Amuria's and mine.
Looks like they've fixed it.
Let's go.
You're the Sibylla Aurea's auriga now.
Be worthy of it!
Sure!
Darn it, our guns aren't hitting them at all!
With that kind of aiming, of course they aren't!
We're going in, Yun!
To your left!
Neviril is...
Protect the Arcus Prima!
Diamond Ri Maajon!
The Diamond Ri Maajon...
With the Diamond Ri Maajon up, the enemy can't hurt us.
Yes, out of all the defensive Ri Maajons, this one is particularly effective.
The ship's helical motors are barely functioning.
Will we have to let them tow us back?
Leave it to them.
Chor Tempest will come through!
Keep the Diamond Ri Maajon going,
and withdraw from the enemy warship's bombardment range.
Right, got it!
The hearing is set for this afternoon, as soon as we arrive.
We don't have much time to prepare.
While we have the opportunity, I'd like to go over the situation with you one more time, Sibylla Neviril.
Your father, Halconf, is going to meet us there.
You and I are completely different in every way.
But in one respect, we're just the same.
Stand up, Aaeru.
I am your pair.
I wonder if Neviril's gonna come back.
Even if she did, what good would it do?
Why, you...!
We finally got twelve people together.
I had hoped we would finally all be able to fly together again.
That doesn't mean anyone still blames you, Mamiina.
That wasn't what I meant!
And Dominura's gone, too.
Limone, do you know where she is?
No idea.
Even if Neviril does come back, that won't mean Chor Tempest can stay together.
Just that we can all be present when it's dissolved.
Oh, so this is where you guys are!
We've been looking for you.
Sibyllae of Chor Tempest, the ceremony is about to begin.
Please make your preparations.
It is regrettable that the task proved to be beyond your abilities.
Please give me more time.
Chor Tempest still has great potential.
Oh? In what way?
Neviril has returned, and the new recruits, Limone and Aaeru...
I believe that their latent ability surpasses that of all previous sibyllae.
Limone is that pet sibylla of yours from your report, isn't she?
Two other sibyllae, Sibylla Mamiina and Sibylla Yun,
were transferred to Chor Tempest under Halconf's sponsorship.
Yes.
No matter what you tell us, they're about to decide everything in there.
Under the circumstances, wouldn't it be better to simply proceed to Plan B as quickly as possible?
But aren't they the ones who let those Highlander agents aboard the Arcus Prima?
Dominura!
This conversation is over.
I'm sorry, Neviril.
But I'm doing this for your own good.
And for your own, too, Father.
It is true that Chor Tempest has many glorious achievements to its name.
However, its own members have rendered those achievements meaningless.
They are priestesses of Tempus Spatium, and yet they insulted and fought with one another,
putting on a shameful display which demonstrates a complete lack of discipline.
This is unacceptable.
But what about our responsibility?
We never saw that the peace conference was a ruse,
and we allowed dangerous enemy agents to get aboard.
It was Chor Tempest that rescued the Arcus Prima from the trap.
If it hadn't been for them, I wouldn't be standing here today.
We—
Wait, Sibylla Neviril.
You have not been given permission to speak.
Please speak.
Onashia!
Sibylla Neviril,
I still clearly remember Erii's cries of grief.
I'm scared...
Please let everyone hear what you have to say.
Yes, ma'am.
We are priestesses serving Tempus Spatium.
Sibyllae.
We hear the voices of the Simoun, and we draw Ri Maajons in the sky.
Soldiers from neighbouring countries have been invading our Holy Land of Simulacrum,
and we have killed a great many of them.
Go on.
"Slaughtered" them, you might say.
When we first encountered the air fleet from the Archipelago, in that battle...
That was not a "battle!"
For a sibylla to speak such words—
...we lost three of our beloved companions.
From Chor Caput, eleven sibyllae gave their lives.
A Highland priestess gave her life in a destructive plot against the Arcus Prima,
taking the lives of even more people.
There was no falsehood in that girl's devotion to her god.
As fellow priestesses, what are we supposed to think about that? What should we do?
Right now, what we're doing is fighting the war.
That's enough.
That's enough, Neviril.
Now we must say a painful farewell to friends whom we remember so fondly.
They... were our travelling companions. Our comrades in battle.
Even though we are at war,
their leaving on this journey was sudden and unexpected.
This is our real job, isn't it?
Their departure leaves a great hole in our hearts that we cannot fill.
Offering perfect Ri Maajons to Tempus Spatium?
We've returned to our true duties, haven't we?
But somehow, it doesn't feel the same.
Huh? You mean you wanted to do funeral ceremonies for the dead?
And perhaps it should never be filled.
Aaeru!
That wasn't what I meant at all!
This is our last Ri Maajon as Chor Tempest.
Despite our sadness and loneliness at losing them,
Don't forget that.
It is our duty to carry on.
Do we even have the right to do their funeral ceremony?
It's not a matter of right.
It's our duty.
I just want to get it over with.
That's all.
Sibylla Paraietta,
please offer the memorial ceremony for these comrades who have sacrificed their lives for their countrymen.
Yes, sir!
We offer the Ri Maajon of the Fields.
I'm not trying to lay blame for these days of fighting.
It has been painful and heartbreaking, and perhaps this is fate.
It may even be the will of Tempus Spatium.
But right now, I don't care what it is.
Right now, I don't care about "the will of God."
I just have one question I'd like to ask you all:
In spite of that... am I still a Simoun sibylla?
Sibylla Neviril, despite your misgivings,
you will remain a Simoun sibylla for as long as you wish it.
Yes, ma'am.
Wait!
The things you have said are inexcusable!
To say you do not care about the divine will...
We cannot simply allow that to pass!
Wait a minute, please!
Everyone, I have something to say.
You're from Chor Rubor, aren't you?
My name is Vyura.
I asked her to come.
Guragief! To abuse your position on this way...
What do you wish to say?
Sibylla Vyura, please speak to us.
Onashia...!
Yes, ma'am.
All of the other Simoun sibyllae love and respect Chor Tempest.
We're proud of them.
They are the best choir of all.
In the name of all Simoun sibyllae,
I request that Chor Tempest remain in service.
Do you mean the Chor Tempest who act as priestesses,
or the Chor Tempest who "fight" in "battle" as a unit?
Which Chor Tempest is it that you want us to keep?
They are twelve sibyllae who form pairs and draw Ri Maajons in the sky.
There can be only one Chor Tempest.
Three o'clock level!
It's the enemy.
Para-sama, over there!
I see them.
What are they?
I've never seen anything like them.
Are they some kind of new artillery shell? Then—
Those aren't shells!
They're heading straight for the Grand Temple.
Let's go, Limone!
We'll destroy them with a Ri Maajon.
Damn them all, every single one of them!
It's like they just want us to suffer!
"Us?"
So it comes to this after all.
We're still doing a Ri Maajon. That hasn't changed at all!
Mamiina! Over there!
There's so many of them!
With that many of them, only the Iron Ri Maajon will work.
That's impossible! We need all six Simoun to do the Iron Ri Maajon!
The Iron Ri Maajon?
Neviril!
What a lovely breeze.
Vyura!
Welcome back, Neviril!
I'm home, everyone!
I have some good news: Chor Tempest will go on.
Hurray!
That's great, Mamiina!
Yes, that's wonderful!
Eh? What's wrong?
I'm just so happy!
I can keep flying Simoun with everyone!
Isn't that great, Para-sama?
We can keep flying together!
What could have happened at Headquarters?
Well, something sure happened, eh?
Neviril! Vyura!
With Chor Tempest's survival decided, Arcus Prima should be repaired right away.
I just wanted you to move on with your life.
You embarrassed a lot of council members back there.
They won't just let Chor Tempest carry on as it did before.
While the Arcus Prima is being repaired, Chor Tempest will be stationed aboard the Messis.
You will fly patrols and reconnaissance missions near the border.
Wait... you mean we're going to fly on that thing?
Isn't it a little...?
Don't get greedy. We're lucky they're letting Chor Tempest survive at all.
That's right!
It's great. Even the ship.
I'm not complaining at all!
Next Episode
Chor Tempest boards the old warship Messis and heads for the borderlands.
Next time, on Simoun:
Birds in a Cage
Birds in a Cage.