I have lived for all these years... without ever making a decision.
This... is my penance.
I was unable to become an Eternal Maiden.
Nor was I able to go to another world.
I remained here.
Never to touch another.
Never to be held by another. Yet still...
I remain here.
Why?
But why did your body have to become like that?
Because I refused to choose a sex,
I was chosen to become the keeper of the Spring.
Because you wouldn't choose?
So that future maidens would not err the way I have erred.
To continue to stand here...
This is my punishment for continuing to run from reality.
Choices
Chor Tempest is to be formally disbanded.
Sibyllae, we have decided that you must now go to the Spring.
What?
Wait a moment, please.
Why must we also give up our standing as sibyllae?
All of your duties will be taken over by priestesses from the Highlands.
No way!
Father!
We're not even allowed to be Simoun sibyllae anymore? So that means...
We can't stay here on the Arcus Prima, then.
Is that correct?
Well... forcing them to make such a choice all of a sudden...
How can they be expected to decide so quickly?
They need to prepare.
There is no time.
We are asking only for a little time.
Compared to the long history of the Simulacrum Theocracy,
it is but a moment.
Sibylla Morinas.
You heard about what happened to us, right?
Yes.
Happy now?
Actually...
I'm going to be leaving the Arcus Prima as well.
The Holy Land has no desire to fly the Simoun any longer.
To demonstrate the fact, our entire maintenance crew is being relocated to the Highlands.
What?
Wherever we end up, it's all the same.
The Simoun are the holy chariots of the gods.
However...
No matter how hard I try to get close...
No. The truth is that I've realized something.
I don't care about the Simoun any more!
I'll be happy as long as you are safe.
I can understand if you despise me.
They've gotten smaller, haven't they?
What?
I wanted to become a man and tinker with the Simoun with you, but...
What are you going to choose?
Huh?
I guess you always wanted to be a man, huh?
I bet you don't even care that they're forcing us to go to the Spring.
Yeah, you're always—
That's not true!
Huh?
I'm scared too!
It's scary becoming an adult!
I want someone to help me...
I want to be protected! But even so...
Alti?
Forget it, you dummy!
You're such a dummy, Nee-san!
Dummy...
Dummy... dummy... dummy... dummy!
Fighting with your sister?
Really, you guys are so childish!
You're still kids. It's too early for you to become adults.
Hey, Vyura, everyone in Rubor already chose their sex, right?
The ones who were going to inherit a family business became men.
The rest... well, you know, it depends.
What about you, Floe?
Me? Whatever. I don't really care which sex I end up.
Well, I'm sure I wouldn't be saying that if I had a lover, but...
Oh? But everyone told me that you liked Aaeru.
Yeah, and I keep telling them that's not true!
Seriously, it doesn't really matter.
But... I dunno...
It feels kinda lonely.
That's what... becoming an adult is like.
I see... so becoming an adult is a lonely thing...
I just remembered something.
Alti's an idiot.
Jeez, that's why I told you not to come!
You're always such a drag!
You're a dummy, Nee-san.
Who're you calling a dummy? Dodo-legs!
Dummy!
Fine! Go back on your own then, loser!
Du-Dummy!
Du... mmy!
Dummy!
You're a dummy, Nee-san!
Even when we quarrelled,
she couldn't even think of words to insult me.
So all she ever said was "dummy."
And you know, she just never gave up, and kept tagging along.
Seriously... what a dummy I have for a little sister.
I wonder when Alti...
...stopped being such an idiot.
I'll be the one to protect you, Nee-san.
She got this determined look in her eyes.
Her arms and legs grew longer, and it was almost like... she became more of an adult than me.
Lots of things were happening all the time, so I didn't even notice.
That Alti...
...she's still the same old idiot.
I kept looking the other way.
I didn't want to believe it.
But... even so, I...
She'll forgive you.
There are things that you can still do,
even if you're no longer a sibylla.
Such as forgiveness.
To forgive a fault...
...and to be forgiven.
If we can do that,
I think we can still be sibyllae even after we choose our sex.
You know,
I really do like you, Para-sama.
My feelings won't change whether I become a man or a woman.
I think I'll never stop respecting you!
Thank you.
I've heard that the High Priestess has left the Arcus Prima.
Aaeru, we don't have much time.
You—
What do you want me to say?
What?
No, don't bother answering. I know.
But I can tell you this. There's no way I'll do it!
Aaeru?
Going to another world just 'cause you wanna see Amuria again?
That's all you care about! So I can't do a Ri Maajon with you!
Why did Onashia show me that?
Never to be held by another. Yet still...
I remain here.
Onashia... will she have to stand there forever?
Never to be forgiven by anyone?
Never to be saved?
Yun?
I thought that perhaps I should take some of Mamiina's belongings with me.
Oh. Her suitcase is under her bed.
When I return home, Mamiina's mother will be there, so...
I was thinking that I could give these to her then.
It still smells like Mamiina...
I hope this will comfort her mother, even if only a little.
Can we even... save anyone anymore?
Huh?
I think it will be very difficult.
We struggle so much just to save ourselves.
But... perhaps if we try really, really hard...
...maybe we can save at least one person.
One... person.
Yun, do you have somebody?
That one person?
Yun... disappeared?
Yeah. I heard that the Highland soldiers are looking for her, but...
Yun... why?
Maybe she didn't wanna become an adult?
No. Yun, she...
She must have found...
Hm?
It's nothing.
Whatever. She's so standoffish!
Just leaving like that, without even saying anything.
Yeah... but once Chor Tempest is disbanded, we're all gonna go our separate ways anyway.
There is something that I need to tell you all.
About another world.
That's crazy! To think the Emerald Ri Maajon did that...!
Yes, but it will save us.
Soon, we will all choose our sex.
Our lives here on the Arcus Prima will come to an end.
But those two... they won't choose a sex, and they'll stay the way they are now.
Not choose their sex...
...and stay the way they are now?
When we all become adults,
and the feelings that we have now fade away,
in some other time, those two...
will stand in the shining lands, looking just as they do now.
There's something I need to tell you.
I see. So those two will...
Yes.
Even if we all become adults...
...they'll remain as they are now, forever.
The eternal now...
If you don't want to, you don't have to go to the other world.
No matter what we decide, we should at least tell the others.
That we've not going to the Spring.
You don't need to tell me that!
I want to know what happened to Amuria.
I want to see her again.
Those are my true feelings.
But...
The one I love...
...is you.
What?
I love you, who strive for life in spite of death.
I love you, who saved me from the darkness.
I'm scared of going to another world.
But if I'm with you, I think—
Wait!
I didn't want... to hear your feelings... about liking me and stuff, you know?
You don't need to give me an answer.
Huh?
I just thought that I should tell you.
No.
I just wanted to tell you.
That's all.
That was so sudden! I...
I don't get it.
The one I love... is you.
Why?
Why does it hurt?
I wanted to save the wandering spirits of my comrades.
That was the thought that kept me going.
But... I always knew the truth.
That the dead can no longer be saved.
But...
I can...
No. I realized that there's one soul that only I can save.
I had secretly hoped...
...that you would say those words to me.
Long ago, I decided not to choose a sex.
However, my heart was unable to stay a maiden's heart.
Now... I am trying to run away, once again,
while pushing all my responsibilities onto you.
No.
You are beautiful.
You are... beautiful.
It sounds very lively out there.
That voice... that has to be Sibylla Floe.
Huh? Uwaa!
Aaeru, were you ever planning to wake up?
It's our last day on the Arcus Prima!
Wait! Alti!
Nah, don't think so!
Please, wait!
Up here!
The view is amazing!
C'mon, let's dance, Aaeru!
Huh? Uh, I...
Hey! Is that...?
Please, let the Messis carry you to the Spring.
Nah, it's okay.
I've always wanted to ride on a helical motor train.
I understand.
May I ask what has happened to Sibylla Neviril and Sibylla Aaeru?
They said that they wished for a little more time.
Understood.
Well then.
Farewell.
After I'm an adult, I'll come visit again!
Wow!
The mountains are getting closer!
It should be lunchtime soon.
Oh! I almost forgot.
I asked for some snacks before we left.
Is anyone hungry?
Those look yummy!
Me too, me too!
I want the veggie one.
What do you want, Rodore?
I'll have meat, please!
Me, too, please.
Boy, am I hungry!
Mmm, delicious!
Okay, this is Rodore's, and here you go, Paraietta.
Thank you.
Man, if you had sandwiches, you should've told us earlier!
Oh, Floe.
That's...
Yun!
Next Episode
And so, the girls head towards adulthood,
and Neviril and Aaeru towards their "eternal now."
Next time, on Simoun:
Pair
Pair.