We will proceed as planned. Chor Tempest will enter at low altitude, with our speaker cables attached.
Our mission objective is to protect the Ruins from the Alliance between Plumbum and Argentum!
It's the enemy!
Funeral Procession
Her soul was bound by sin.
However, through the compassion of Tempus Spatium,
and the benevolence of the Holy Land, we forgive and receive her.
Why was Angulas's body inside that ancient Simoun?
She was definitely...
AA - E - RU ! ! !
They were unable to find so much as a single splinter of bone.
She has received the protection of Tempus Spatium.
For the one departing upon a new journey, we offer a prayer.
A Highland priestess who acted as a covert operative!
I'm surprised they would allow her funeral to be held here on the Arcus Prima.
That was what Her Eminence wanted.
And the Defence Minister?
Because of Plumbum and Argentum's new alliance, the Ministry claims that they cannot even risk returning her body.
Despite their apparent hostility towards each other?
I certainly didn't expect the two of them to agree about this.
That's what worries me.
The wind won't blow in here.
Neviril!
Who'd have thought that you'd start a conversation with me?
What happened at the Ruins...
Yeah.
Huh? What?
The Spring?
The Spring was inside the Ruins, and Onashia was there as well.
This place... this place is the Spring!
It's just like Grandpa said!
And Angulas, who we thought had been blown up in the explosion, was inside the ancient Simoun.
I think Angulas went somewhere.
What?
You know, back then...
At the instant the Simoun exploded,
she went to another world.
Another... world?
We finally get back to the Arcus Prima,
and now all this weird stuff keeps happening!
I know. Can't we even relax for a second?
No, there's no time to relax.
I heard that we're supposed to meet at the Maaju Pool right after this.
I like doing Maaju, but it sucks to do it just 'cause we're ordered to.
Hey, isn't that Neviril and Aaeru?
Oh? I guess they got over their differences.
What do you mean, "got over?"
It was just Neviril being an idiot!
W-Wait, Aaeru. What's...?
It's like Grandpa always said.
Come on! Over here!
Come on, Grandpa! Hurry up!
Aaeru.
This is as far as I can go.
Huh?
But you, you have to keep going.
You see, growing old means that you have to make a few decisions along the way.
And once you've made those decisions, those possibilities are gone forever.
I don't understand!
A Simoun lets you see what's to come.
"What's to come?"
Another world!
I don't know what he meant by that.
But Grandpa always longed to go there.
Aaeru, is that the reason you didn't want to choose your sex?
The helical motors...
It is said that they manipulate time and space.
But I always thought that was just a fairy tale,
told to make the Simoun seem sacred.
"I am everywhere, and I am nowhere."
If Onashia is like that,
and Angulas was like that,
and the Simoun are like that...
Then...
...Limone and Dominura might be too?
What we've just discussed...
It must remain a secret between us.
We'll keep it a secret, then?
Just the two of us.
Yes.
Why didn't you go to Angulas's funeral?
That was the decision.
"No one from a low-born family like yours can be permitted to attend such a holy ceremony."
Wh-Why? Until now, we've always...
Things change.
Besides, Central Command is all screwed up.
But they even approved the funeral of an enemy priestess, so...
Hey, that's not the sort of thing I'd expect you to say.
Didn't you like Angulas?
But... but...
I expected at least this much discrimination.
What?
It was only because of the Vice-Chairman's influence that I was able to remain a Simoun sibylla.
Mamiina...
The Vice-Chairman has changed.
Now he's just a regular old geezer!
Oh! Mamiina, please!
Living on the Messis was so much fun!
Especially the mouse stew!
What?
All the noble priestesses were happily feasting on it,
and I thought, "Hah! We're all the same!"
Yes, we are!
No. We really are different.
Mamiina...
Wait, please!
The Maaju Pool is under the jurisdiction of the Interior Ministry.
If the military authorities set foot here,
Her Eminence will—
I don't care.
Please accept my apologies, Minister,
but such a large audience will disturb our prayers.
Maaju are not prayers.
What?
They're military training, Sibylla Aurea.
We would like to see you perform the most powerful Ri Maajon...
...that Chor Tempest is capable of drawing.
What beautiful lines!
The Dandelion Ri Maajon?
It doesn't hurt anyone.
It doesn't deceive anyone.
It's purely for the sake of ceremony.
Everything has gone well.
I made the right decision...
...to entrust Neviril to Aaeru as her pair.
Yes! Everything went well!
You don't understand a thing!
Is your judgement so unreliable that you'd rather listen to someone who's been asleep?
Thinking that she needs a nobody like you to protect her...
That's damned arrogant of you!
I... Neviril...
I think... I've made a big mistake.
If I were with you—
Stop!
I think... I've made a big mistake.
I want to be your pair.
Yes.
I'll be the one to protect you.
"Dismantle a Simoun."
I never thought I'd hear those words from anyone else,
Sibylla Dominura...
Wapourif, forget about that day.
That is my final word.
I cannot forget.
"Someone who has nothing to believe in has no firm ground to stand on."
That's what you told me.
Have you found it?
What should I do?
The thing that I believe in...
I have assigned my maintenance crew to dismantle the ancient Simoun, as you instructed.
Dismantling a chariot of the gods?
That is a mortal sin!
We're sinful? We're not the ones who defiled the temple of Tempus Spatium with a foreigner's body.
Today's agenda is to decide what to do about the enemy's airborne base ship.
Most of the ancient Simoun have fallen into the hands of the Highlanders.
It would be too dangerous to send Chor Tempest on a reconnaissance mission...
When, might I ask, will it be safe to give them such a mission?
I understand your concern for the well-being of your daughter.
However, if another problem arises,
You will be forced to consider your position, Mr. Vice-Chairman.
Who is Sibylla Neviril's pair?
That would be Sibylla Aaeru, sir.
Her skills as an auriga are outstanding even among the members of Chor Tempest.
Sibylla Aaeru?
Wasn't her grandfather...?
Yes, but she...
What is going on here?
Um, my apologies, ma'am.
Where are you taking her?
Sibylla Yun.
Angulas's funeral is over.
Shouldn't she be buried without delay?
These are the Defence Minister's orders.
The Defence Minister?
Mocking the souls of the dead like this is unforgivable!
Without your Simoun, you girls are powerless.
It would be dangerous to ignore the airborne base ship.
Chor Tempest will fly reconnaissance in order to locate it.
The Messis will serve as your relay station.
Aw, come on! I thought we finally got away from that mouldy dump!
I will do my best to accomodate you again, Sibylla-sama.
Eww...
And what should we do if we find the base ship?
If you judge that the circumstances—
Given the circumstances, we should completely annihilate it!
With the whereabouts of Sibylla Dominura and Sibylla Limone unknown,
we feel it necessary to reorganize the current pairs.
Sibylla Paraietta,
Sibylla Kaimu.
Sibylla Alti,
Sibylla Floe.
Sibylla Rodoreamon,
Sibylla Morinas.
Sibylla Neviril,
Sibylla Mamiina.
What?
Sibylla Yun, Sibylla Aaeru.
The two of you will not be participating in this mission.
What the—! Why the hell do I have to stay behind?
She is my pair.
I demand a satisfactory explanation.
Neviril...
Please, do not cause more trouble for me.
Having trouble sleeping?
Neviril.
Yes.
Your Maaju this afternoon was remarkable.
Thank you.
Will you dance with me? Just one song?
I'm sorry, but right now I...
What?
I never expected to see you stand up for Aaeru.
It isn't as if I've opened my heart to her.
But facing Aaeru is like facing Amuria,
and doing that has forced me to face myself.
I think that's what I was afraid of.
I was just running away.
I was relying too much on everyone else.
Why not let yourself?
What?
Paraietta?
Rely on me.
But if I keep going, there's a whole other world...
I'm sorry. It's nothing.
Another world?
If you want to see another world, I'll show it to you.
What is it?
You're awake?
I think Yun is asleep.
I thought you might be too nervous to sleep.
To be the pair of the Sibylla Aurea...
I always saw that as the quickest way to reach my goal.
But don't get the wrong idea.
Huh?
I honestly want to be on the same level as the rest of you,
but my reasons are different now.
I truly want to be friends with everyone.
Mamiina!
So please stop saying "but we are friends!" and stuff like that.
I'm a little sensitive about it, okay?
I understand.
Mamiina, would you like me to sing you a lullaby?
The one you were singing for Limone?
Aw, don't. I'm not a child.
And on they echo, the swirls of light.
Of course, she's not listening.
Such blessed happiness they give to us.
Proof of a world that will never be destroyed.
The priestesses of Tempus Spatium
Will rock the cradle until the morning wakes you.
Why do you think you were taken off the mission?
I have an idea.
I see.
And you?
Under the Great Mother's care,
There's something that might be the reason.
And that is?
I can't say.
I promised not to.
I see.
Under white wings.
That's a wise decision.
Promises are meant to be kept.
I have to go.
So do I.
Next Episode
Neviril is shot down,
and forced to make an emergency landing
on the Argentine base ship.
Next time, on Simoun:
Sibylla
Sibylla.