The Door to a New World
How dare they do that right in front of us?
This is exactly why I was against Chor Rubor and Chor Caput being disbanded!
We can't have Chor Tempest be the only ones we can depend on.
Gather all the troops and the Simile!
The reconnaissance Simile and the cruising Simile! All of them!
Yes, sir!
What foolishness!
I hope you realize that fighting leads absolutely nowhere.
Onashia...
Wow, look at that!
Come one, look!
I am!
Over here, hurry up!
I said no playing on the Simoun!
Huh?
Why not?
Yeah c'mon, why?
Well... because...
Ummm...
Wow!
What is it?
"Booooou...!"
It's making a noise!
Like, "booooou!"
No way!
Wow, it is!
Like, "booooou!"
It sounds like a flute!
C'mon!
You too, Limone!
Well, well?
"Booooou..."
That's what it sounds like.
Told ya!
Maybe there's something inside!
I see.
So the day has come.
Would you please give us a little more time?
Would it be okay for us to come after we've finished our meal?
Did the meeting end badly?
Onashia is the symbol of the Simulacrum Theocracy.
I'm sure the authorities have been enjoying her continuing silence.
But if she decides to act...
I take no pleasure in warfare.
However...
To bring her here for a reason like this...
I can't fathom what Her Eminence is thinking.
Guragief.
If I should...
Hm?
Nothing.
Never in history has anyone flown out in a Simoun without orders!
Have you no sense of responsibility?
Responsibility?
Our responsibility as Simoun sibyllae.
Pride in what we are. That which each of us bears.
Was that all that you wanted to say to us, sir?
In that case, please excuse us.
Why, those little...!
Paraietta?
Vyura!
And... Rodoreamon and Alti as well?
You too, Paraietta?
Couldn't sleep, eh?
Us, too.
Para-sama!
Hey, it looks like everyone's here.
The Messis will bear Onashia to her destination.
Sibylla Neviril,
Sibylla Aaeru.
Would you care to accompany her?
And would you like to know about... another world?
Could I...
...come along, too?
Um...
No.
Those we have will suffice.
Please.
Is it good?
Um...
Good...
...isn't the word I'd use.
It's bitter.
Kind of, I think.
And it's sweet too... I guess.
Bit it's not a taste I really hate.
I'll probably...
...be able to finish eating it.
"Dunno."
Huh?
You never say that any more, Limone.
I started thinking about things more, and I feel like... there isn't much I don't understand.
So...
I'm the opposite.
The more I think, the more confused I become.
Dominura?
Well, we'd best get going as soon as we've finished eating.
Where to?
Dunno.
Her Eminence has ordered us to avoid "flying recklessly."
I wonder where we're going?
Yes?
Excuse me...
Onashia-sama is currently resting.
It's all right.
Onashia.
I wonder how "another world" is connected to all this?
I feel really uneasy around the High Priestess.
The Defence Minister is kind of a bastard, but...
Her Eminence...
Hmm, how should I put it?
What?
Your hands...
They're so small.
Stop treating me like a kid!
This war... it makes such obvious things hard to see.
Onashia...
You have something you wish to ask me.
You told me that you can hear Mamiina's voice.
If so, then...
...what about my comrades?
Have their souls... been set free?
You are the one who wants to be set free, aren't you?
You keep trying to live close to the time and place where your friends died.
Yet at the same time, you long to escape to a place far away from there.
Onashia-sama.
It seems that we have arrived.
Why have we come to the Ruins?
It's doing it again.
"The Door to a New World."
It's the melody played by that music box.
And the unsuspected goal of those who perished here.
What?
Yes.
This place was once the training ground for Chor Dextra.
Chor... Dextra?
Sibylla Aaeru, your grandfather was the regina of that choir.
Grandpa... was the regina?
Can I ask you something?
Yes.
What happened back then?
When do you mean?
On the Messis.
Everything just poured into me...
Huh?
When I looked inside the helical motor,
it was as though I saw someone's...
...or something's memories.
The only thing that's in there is a helix.
All we can understand about it is...
Sibylla Dominura?
Dominura?
We became obsessed by the Ri Maajon... by the Simoun.
But that was because the Simoun were all that we had to rely on.
Yes. If the Simoun had never existed in the first place...
Or if they had existed, but no one had been around to explain how they worked, what would have happened?
Huh? Well...
Ummm...
Well...
They'd...
We brought them!
They're here!
A long, long time ago...
...there was a civilization vastly more advanced than ours.
It is said that the Simoun are relics from those days.
But an unending series of wars broke out, and left the world in ruins.
With everything destroyed, the land became worthless,
and further war became pointless.
The Simoun were of no use to the starving masses,
and the reason for their existence was forgotten.
The people could do nothing more than wait for death to claim them.
And then, from the sky, it is said that a Simoun appeared from another world.
Within it rode a pair of maidens, descending from heaven.
Those girls...
They introduced themselves as "Simoun sibyllae."
And then...
they imparted the secret of the Emerald Ri Maajon.
The Emerald Ri Maajon?
Yes.
Another world...
No.
The ultimate Ri Maajon transports you to another time.
It is a divine gift that we have been granted—a great "what if?".
If the people of that time had been told that there would be another war...
If the Simoun didn't exist...
Perhaps I wouldn't exist, either.
If, at that time, someone had been able to prevent people from relying on the Simoun...
But if I didn't exist,
then this pain I feel wouldn't have to exist.
...then our present, with all its extreme distress and poverty, might be very different.
By travelling through time and space...
...we can take this power of "what if?" to another age.
That is the purpose of the Simoun,
and of the Emerald Ri Maajon.
"Travelling across time and space...?"
Unbelievable!
That's amazing.
Wait!
Then this "Chor Dextra" that Grandpa commanded...?
Chor Dextra was a choir created specifically to complete the Emerald Ri Maajon.
Someone you all know very well once belonged to that choir.
Huh?
Sibylla Dominura.
She is the only surviving member of Chor Dextra.
Dominura?
Yes. I finally realised...
...that everything happened because I started it!
I...
I've been thinking about what you said before, Dominura.
About "what if the Simoun didn't exist?"
If they had never existed?
Uh huh.
Then... I would never have met everyone in Chor Tempest.
And... I wouldn't have met you either, Dominura.
Why are you crying?
Yes, why am I?
U-ummm...
Because you're sad?
Because you're lonely?
Because it hurts?
Or, um...
Ummm...
Because you're... happy?
That's right.
I'm happy!
Let's go.
You still don't know where we're gonna go?
No.
Now I know.
Under the skies of blue,
Beyond the clouds of white,
You'll find the blue of tears
In the whiteness of the dragon's belly.
In the blackness of the shadows,
The red light of the fires
In the sky...
Sibylla Dominura has probably completed the Emerald Ri Maajon.
Then that means...
...that she is alive, in some other time.
What?
Sibylla Dominura and Sibylla Limone are alive?
I do not believe that I am mistaken about this.
Then...
Amuria might be too?
Huh?
Does that mean...
...that it's possible that Amuria is still alive?
The Emerald Ri Maajon is the one hope given to us by Tempus Spatium.
Whether it takes you into the future or into the past is beyond anyone's control.
However, the Simoun exist through the will of Tempus Spatium.
And it is not likely that the gods would err.
Tempus Spatium will undoubtedly open the door to the right time.
Sibylla Neviril,
Sibylla Aaeru.
I want to entrust this to you:
The Emerald Ri Maajon.
Hurry!
A Simoun from the Arcus Niger?
Minister!
What... what is this? What's going on?
The Arcus Niger...
...has gone down.
Seven o'clock high! Five ancient Simoun, closing in fast!
What?
Next Episode
The allied forces of Plumbum and Argentum attack the Holy Land in greater numbers than ever before.
Next time, on Simoun:
Sortie
Sortie.