Wait!
Nee-san…
I’m Para-sama’s pair!
To put me with Alti at this point…
This is all for the sake of regaining
Chor Tempest’s honour.
Neviril, look!
That’s…
Why is their prayer having
no effect on the Simoun Gem?
Kaimu!
Nee-san!
Don’t call me that!
Do not call me that!
Reason
Prayer?
Yes, the chariots of the gods are activated by the prayers of the Simoun sibyllae.
Two priestesses unite their hearts in praise of Tempus Spatium.
To reject one’s pair
is to reject the Simoun.
This is unbelievable.
I’ve never heard of such a thing.
All of this is guesswork.
But thanks to the two of you, we’ve discovered a hidden aspect of the Simoun.
You’ve done well, although you probably don’t appreciate my saying so.
So that means… that I probably won’t be able to pair… with Nee-san any more.
You understand, don’t you?
The enemy hasn’t shown up.
We’ve been lying around so much that I’m almost gathering dust.
So would you rather be fighting?
I didn’t say that!
I just meant that
there’s nothing to do.
You should consider your words carefully,
or else keep them to yourself.
Ahhhhhh! I’m just soooo bored!
Rodoreamon can get really scary when she’s mad. I’m gonna stay out of this.
What are you thinking about?
Something other than you.
I see.
The Emerald Ri Maajon?
Yeah, it’s the greatest Ri Maajon that a Simoun can perform.
It’s said it can bring about
the ultimate miracle.
Ultimate…
You were imitating the
Emerald Ri Maajon on purpose.
Just how do you think Neviril
would feel if she saw that?
Huh? Did I do some kind of Ri Maajon?
Oh, so that’s what that was about!
Aaeru?
Tell me, what would happen?
Sorry. I’m afraid I’ve never seen it.
Wapourif, didn’t Neviril and Amuria—
Neviril and Amuria did
the Emerald Ri Maajon?
Well…
I get it! They tried but
they couldn’t do it.
Yes.
I see. So she and Amuria…
Wow, you’re so thorough.
Tempus Spatium likes cleanliness and shuns places that are dirty.
My mother always said that a dirty kitchen or bathroom brings misfortune.
You’re amazing, Mamiina!
You know a lot that I don’t.
Maybe it suits me.
Cooking and cleaning like this, I mean.
Being here has felt like a dream.
Ah, it’s stuck and it won’t come off. If only we could get citrus fruit…
Citrus fruit?
The acid in the juice
would dissolve the stain.
You really are amazing!
This is delicious!
Neviril!
Do the Emerald Ri Maajon with me!
Aaeru, what are you—
I get it! You and Amuria failed at it.
But with me, I bet you can do it. Come on, Neviril, let’s try the Em—
Stop it!
Wait.
I’ll go get a mop.
Neviril, are you okay?
Drop it, Aaeru.
Why?
That topic is…
Because it makes her
remember Amuria’s death?
Neviril!
That was in spectacularly bad taste.
Poor Neviril.
I never met Amuria, but you shouldn’t speak ill of the dead.
What? I didn’t—
C’mere.
Aaeru…
Why’d you drag me
all the way down here?
Sheesh! Tell me, do you like Neviril?
Sure, I like her.
That’s not what I mean.
Huh?
Do you wanna talk with her as long as
you can? Feel her warmth as you hold her?
Are you filled with love and desire for her? That kind of “like,” I mean.
Sure, I want Neviril!
I can fly higher with her
than with anyone else.
Aaeru!
How did that feel?
How did what feel?
What I just did!
Well, we’re not about to fly into battle, so it’s kind of weird.
If you really liked someone,
you’d feel differently.
Neviril like-liked Amuria that way. Get it?
What does that have to do
with the Emerald Ri Maajon?
It’s a lot better if you
like each other, okay?
Neviril!
Neviril…
Neviril.
It’ll be all right…
if you do that with me.
We can do it, if we’re together.
The Emerald Ri Maajon!
Because… because it makes her remember Amuria’s death.
Nooooooooo!
Neviril, what’s going on? Neviril!
Neviril!
I’ll open the window.
It’s dusty in here, but this must be better than sharing a room with Aaeru—with the others.
Yes, thanks.
Get some rest, then.
The Emerald Ri Maajon…
It must be really great.
Yeah.
I want to try it too.
With Dominura?
It doesn’t matter
who my partner is…
Do you like Dominura?
I don’t know.
They say if you really like somebody, you want to kiss her even when you’re not flying a Simoun.
Apparently, a lot of things
are better if you like your pair.
A lot?
Yep. A lot.
What did Central Command say?
Unless the enemy shows signs of activity,
we should just watch them for now.
That enemy base ship was almost impossible to find.
Do they think we should just leave it alone?
They’ve apparently been distracted by unexpected problems with the Arcus Prima.
As I thought, they’re missing the forest for the trees.
If things go on this way, our Holy Land will…
Sibylla Dominura, you look uneasy.
It may be out of line for a man in my position to offer advice to a sibylla, but—
Yes, it certainly is.
Limone, what is it?
Is something wrong?
Yes?
How did that feel?
Did you feel that you liked me?
Run along.
Amuria… is dead.
Neviril!
I finally found you!
W-Why?
Whew!
What are you…?
Are you sick?
C’mon, look at me.
You can’t feel the wind in here. It’s so stuffy and full of old junk.
There’s nothing here but
a bunch of useless memories.
Let’s go outside.
Come on, let’s open
the door together, Neviril.
Neviril.
What are you doing?!
Hey, that hurts!
Neviril is tired. Get out of here!
What? But…
Get out!
Neviril, I don’t think Aaeru
means any harm, but—
I would like to sleep
for a while. Is that all right?
Where’s Aaeru?
No idea.
That was surprising.
Yes.
Not just for Neviril.
The rest of us have avoided
talking about it, too.
I felt that mentioning it
would keep us from moving on.
Amuria was strong.
She was always aiming higher, and never doubted herself.
Yes, I thought the war
was too much for me but…
When Amuria was with us,
it felt like we were invincible,
so I was afraid to admit
that she was gone.
No, even now I don’t want to. But—
What happened to my…?
You caught me.
What’s up?
What is that?
What sort of creature
is that supposed to be?
Oh, that’s funny!
Come on! I sewed it as well as I could!
I know it’s a bit ugly, but…
Its face is all misshapen.
It’s fine. This is adorable!
It’s certainly unique… just like its maker.
Hey!
I didn’t mean to hurt Neviril.
I just thought that we could do anything if we were together.
How can you be so confident?
Haven’t you ever felt despair?
If I told you,
what difference would it make?
Maybe it was a mistake
to entrust Neviril to you.
We can’t wait for the brass any longer.
We should scout out the base ship while the enemy remains quiet.
Neviril, Aaeru, it’s up to you.
Wait, those two are…
The two of them are the best pair in Chor Tempest at the moment. Is there a problem?
But…!
Dominura, I can’t pair
with Aaeru right now.
Yesterday, you said
the Simoun are—
Yes, and that is why.
People’s feelings aren’t toys!
How can you just assume—
Neviril.
I want to fly.
Neviril, I guess you don’t want to, but I…
Neviril, please consider the interests of the nation above all else.
We are Simoun sibyllae.
Are you worried?
— This is pointless.
— It’s not pointless.
Not pointless at all.
We can fly. We can!
Their prayer seems
to have been heard.
I guess feelings
don’t matter after all.
They do matter.
We must conclude that Neviril…
Neviril…
Why?
I was right. You do want me!
You can fly with me.
Anything is possible
when you’re with me!
Do I want Aaeru?
No, it can’t be. I’m… I’m…
I’m… afraid of Aaeru.
Next Episode
Are you ordering me to dismantle a Simoun, Sibylla Dominura?
Next time, on Simoun:
That Which Must Not Be Violated
That Which Must Not Be Violated.