The Argentum Archipelago
Our Archipelago has the best science and technology on Daikuuriku.
However, we have been unable to develop an airship that can fly above the clouds.
A single lightning strike would incinerate one in an instant.
Despite the risk, we have no choice but to fly far across the raging sea.
The Holy Land is a quiet and beautiful country that hides a secret.
Our country has tried repeatedly to invade theirs to learn it.
But every time we've tried, they've stopped us.
This is the Holy Land's secret: demons. Simoun.
Nothing else on Daikuuriku can fly that freely in the sky.
Fallen Wings
The Holy Land of Simulacrum
It's only a routine deterrence patrol.
Neviril-sama!
You should address her as "Sibylla Aurea!"
You can almost see the golden glow around her.
Was you father well, Neviril?
Amuria, you're terrible!
There are several hundred Ri Maajon shapes, and we can combine them in an infinite number of ways.
Many of the meanings have been lost over the years, but the Simoun sibyllae are constantly working to rediscover them.
Your daughter's flying is every bit as good as I've heard.
Now that she's come of age, I can finally breathe a sigh of relief.
She has become the best Simoun sibylla, has she not? The one they call "Sibylla Aurea?"
No matter how magnificently a prayer is offered, using it in war can only hurt our traditions.
Your Eminence...
Prayers are meant to be offerings. To use them for war, of all things...
By sending the Simoun to patrol the borders, we can demonstrate the power of Tempus Spatium, and convince these insolent invaders to withdraw peacefully.
Would that not be in accordance with the divine will?
My father specifically asked for Chor Tempest to fly today's patrol.
Well, Chor Tempest is the best choir, after all...
Amuria, flying the Simoun isn't about being the "best."
That's not true!
When we fly, it's to offer prayers, not for our own glory.
We have to get stronger.
A lot stronger.
Stronger? Why?
Neviril!
Isn't that...?
This is Neviril of Chor Tempest. Are you okay?
Shot down? Whose Simoun was shot down?
They all were!
Chor Caput has been wiped out.
We're the only ones left.
Hurry! You must send word to Guragief-sama.
Sibylla Aurea, please be careful.
I thought it was impossible for a Simoun to be shot down.
Calm down, Neviril.
We knew a day like this would come eventually, that we'd have to take the Simoun into battle.
No, Amuria, Simoun are the chariots of the gods.
No man-made aircraft can possibly outperform these heavenly craft!
That's why, when the enemy sees a Simoun, they'll run away.
When they see us, they'll run away!
Milady?
Huh? Did I say something?
Are we going to die?
Oh well, if I'm with you, Para-sama, I won't mind.
I have better things to do than die.
Do you mean Neviril?
Did she give you permission to omit her title, Kaimu?
Oh, so you're the one I need permission from?
I wonder what the enemy's like.
The Archipelago use those floaty airships, don't they?
There must be some mistake.
Everyone knows that a Simoun can't be shot down.
All we have to do is fly around and the enemy flees in terror...
...from these beautiful butterflies.
Neviril, let's try the Emerald Ri Maajon.
That again? That's one of the old Ri Maajons that hasn't been analyzed!
According to legend, the sibyllae who successfully completed the Emerald Ri Maajon were taken to serve at the right hand of Tempus Spatium.
If we succeed at it, we can too!
Don't be so impatient! Let's not worry about that for now.
But I want us to get stronger!
We've reached the border. I'm taking us down.
Simoun are the chariots of the gods.
They certainly perform a lot better than anything we can build.
If we could learn their secret, our country's fortunes would improve.
Falcon Ri Maajon.
They invaded our country, and they're not leaving!
That's just normal flight. It's not like the Simoun at all.
The Simoun draw patterns in the sky with the shining trails they leave in their wake.
They call it "Ri Maajon."
No one knows why it holds such power.
If we could learn the secret, it would greatly advance our country's technology.
But the Holy Land has kept the secrets of the Simoun closely guarded for a long time.
It is said that those who try to learn these secrets will be cast into hell by the Simoun themselves.
But what of it? The Simoun are just machines, and there's no such place as hell.
There are so many of them!
The Simoun aren't "the chariots of the gods." They're just machines.
Therefore, they can be shot down.
We can bring them down!
Someday the secret of the Ri Maajon will be revealed,
and the Holy Land's monopoly of the Simoun technology will come to an end.
Oh, who cares how many of them there are?
We'll get rid of them all! Shark Ri Maajon!
Iron Ri Maajon, all six of us!
Understood!
They're erasing our trails!
How can they do that?
If they can't draw the pattern with their trails, the Simoun can't perform a Ri Maajon.
We have to try the Emerald Ri Maajon, Neviril! A miracle is sure to happen!
No, Amuria. We don't know what will happen.
I want to get stronger.
We need to get stronger, Neviril!
I don't want things to be like this!
Look at all of these people trying to interfere with us!
They're trying to take our wings from us!
That's why we have to fight them!
Amuria!
That's why we need to get stronger.
We can do it.
Let's go... to the place where we can be free.
Neviril! We're going to be much stronger!
Yes.
She was so beautiful...
Neviril! Don't look at them!
If you look them in the eye, you won't be able to kill them!
Neviril!
The Emerald Ri Maajon... failed.
What is that?
Neviril!
It's the wrath of Tempus Spatium!
Simoun are just machines!
They're not "the chariots of the gods!"
Our country will learn these demons' secrets!
But... what if... they really are...?
Huh?
The Sibylla Aurea is tired. I'll listen to what you have to say.
Paraietta-sama...
Um, we...
You want to leave the ship?
Yes.
We're thinking of going to the Spring to meet with Onashia.
If you go to the Spring, you can no longer be a sibylla.
You'll never be able to touch a Simoun again.
Are you okay with that?
Yes.
I'm planning to become a man.
I want to be as gallant as you, Paraietta-sama.
Your wish for the Spring isn't something to be shared with others.
Go on, then.
Are you going to sit here and watch her door all day, senpai?
There's nothing that I can do to heal that sibylla's pain...
A cadet?
This is the sibyllae's area. Get out!
Are the priestesses feeling any better?
They say that when the moon is covered by clouds, the stars are, too.
Neviril lost her beloved pair. It's to be expected.
Three sibyllae from Chor Tempest died in the battle, and more are leaving to go to the Spring.
They're no longer the elite, are they?
Dux!
What's wrong, Sibylla Floe, Sibylla Limone?
The thing is, this kid—wait, she's a sybilla? But...!
She may be young, but she has special permission to join Chor Tempest.
Isn't it a little strange for a cadet that young to become a sibylla?
If we aren't willing to go even that far, we won't be able to protect the Simoun.
So that little doll is the only replacement we're getting?
No, we'll get one more before we leave.
Another special exception?
No, she's normal, Captain.
Who is that?
Wow, so that's a Simoun! I've never seen the real thing before!
Sibylla Aaeru? We've been waiting for you!
The Archipelago's airships are once again violating our borders.
We're going to send out Chor Tempest.
I don't think that's possible.
I'm pretty sure Neviril won't want to.
I think so too.
Neviril?
For that matter, Paraietta isn't here, either.
We're in no state to fly right now.
I'm scared.
We don't have anything but the Simoun to fight with.
But would Tempus Spatium forgive us if we did such a thing?
I can fly.
I'll go!
Wait! Sibylla Aaeru!
There's no way she's a priestess.
That's one of the practice Simile, isn't it?
She can't perform Ri Maajons with that!
You guys can stay behind and pray. I came here to fight!
Next Episode
The Simoun should never have fallen, but they did.
Next time, on Simoun:
The Blue Spring
The Blue Spring.