Bell Ri Maajon!
Let's go, Kaimu!
Yes, Para-sama.
Limone! We're slipping off!
They blew it.
Another failure!
You're not getting away!
We did it!
Those two have been acting strangely lately.
I wonder what happened...
That was totally Limone's fault!
They let her join us because she was supposed to be a great prodigy.
Floe...
I feel sorry for Aaeru.
White Solitude
I had hoped that Chor Tempest would have recovered by now, but they haven't.
You've seen what Chor Tempest is like now.
You were the only survivor from Chor Dextra. I'd like to hear your thoughts.
The situation certainly doesn't look good.
I can see that they're a far cry from the elite choir that they once were.
In their current state, they can barely handle daytime shifts.
It doesn't look like we'll be able to return them to night duty for a while.
We need them back at full strength right away.
That's why we called you here.
Can you do it, Sibylla Dominura?
That's why I came here.
Hurry up and run checks on the helical motors!
And don't forget to clean the Simoun gems as well!
Hey! Limone, what were you doing?
Don't screw Aaeru up like that! If you're not going to do it right, you should quit.
I... was told that I had to be here.
Why, you...
Isn't that...
You're new, aren't you? Are you... Dominura?
You're Limone, right?
Sibylla Limone, your talent as a cadet was second to none.
At the Academy, you broke most of the records for someone your age
both in written and practical tests, and you became the highest-ranked sagitta.
The Central Command recognized your abilities and made a special exception for you:
you were accepted as the youngest Sibylla in history,
and assigned to Chor Tempest.
But you have zero experience in real combat.
A few days ago, you went out on an unauthorized flight. Why?
Why are you asking?
Because I've taken an interest in you.
Needless to say, you have an outstanding record.
The way Chor Tempest has ended up... doesn't it bother you?
I'll bet you never thought being a Sibylla would be like this!
What are you trying to say?
I want to help you.
It won't be anything bad.
All you have to do is listen to what I tell you.
If you do, you can go back to how things used to be.
You can reclaim the heights that a prodigy like you deserves.
Dominura seems to be using Limone to try to revive Chor Tempest.
Ah, well... taking care of the choirs is your job.
I don't understand that part.
You don't understand?
Let's just say...
What those kids think is far beyond any adult's understanding.
You're talking about trying to understand the youngest of them.
Are you seriously telling me that you can do that?
Guragief, let me tell you one thing:
What is it?
What we're doing out here... it's war.
Even those kids understand that.
Yeah?
Who's there?
Hey, this is a surprise! I didn't expect you to come visit me.
Um...
If we were to break up as a pair, how would that make you feel?
No problem!
Huh?
If that's what you want, it's fine by me.
But I don't really...
Was that all you wanted to ask me?
If I cut his hands off the controls...
There's nothing else we can do, is there?
It can't be helped.
Limone, go wait over there, okay?
Hurry! Get out of here!
Coming here wasn't because of any decision I made.
I was just doing what other people told me to,
and before I knew it, I was here.
So...
I was hoping that you could tell me what to do.
What would you do if you were told to kill somebody?
Um, I don't really know.
I'm not going to tell you what to do.
I'm here because I'm trying to avoid making a decision.
If you're afraid of fighting, it's okay to quit being a Sibylla.
If you're not going to keep flying the Simoun, they aren't going to let you stay here.
If you really don't have a reason to stay here, you can always leave, can't you?
What should I do?
Limone, you are so wonderful!
I know you're going to be a splendid Simoun Sibylla someday.
Limone, you need to be more considerate toward your teammates.
There isn't anyone who can follow you like this.
You're just a kid!
Don't butt in just because you can fly a little!
I just...
Sibylla Aurea, why don't you fly the Simoun any more?
Are you scared?
That's not it.
It's just that...
Well, right now, I...
Sibylla Aurea, what in the world are we supposed to be?
You're...
I'm sure that you know what to do. Please, you must tell me!
Right now... I don't have any strength to offer you.
Limone!
After all this time...
After all this time, I haven't changed a bit.
A reconnaissance mission?
There have been reports of possible large-scale military activities in the north.
The north? From the Plumbum Highlands?
They're more interested in how well Limone and Dominura are suited for each other.
Alti and Floe are going with them as well.
Did they become a pair?
I've heard that Dominura decided that.
What kind of woman is she, I wonder?
Wait, Limone!
Huh?
You go over here.
Me? The auriga?
Absolutely.
This seat should be yours.
But...
I know all about that.
It's for your own good.
If you know, then why...
As I said, it's for your own good.
Ever since that incident,
you have been unconsciously suppressing your talent.
I want you to set it free.
Didn't I tell you that I know you better than anyone?
Just let me handle it.
Everything will be all right.
Huh?
She had Limone fly as her auriga?
It looks like she's up to something.
How is it? Are you getting a feel for it?
We'll be over the target soon.
Keep the communicator attached, and start the patrol.
Understood.
Hey, Limone, tell me something...
Can you really handle being an auriga?
Or are you just doing as you're told again?
Cut the chatter, please, and focus on the mission.
And don't ever ask Limone a question like that again!
Yes, ma'am!
Huh?
It's snowing!
It must be getting pretty cold out there.
All clear to starboard.
All clear dead ahead, as well.
Enemy tanks! Three o'clock low!
Wow, there are a lot of them!
We're going in, too, Limone!
Limone!
Stop it, Limone!
Doing the Silver Ri Maajon all of a sudden is too dangerous!
No, I can do it.
That's impossible! Listen to me!
I can do it.
This is so easy!
Is she still holding on to what happened to her as a cadet?
This snow is terrible.
It's a blizzard.
They're late. Shouldn't they be back by now?
Oh! There are just too many of them!
This situation is no good.
In this blizzard, we can barely even fly, let alone do a Ri Maajon.
If the two of us are having this much trouble, then that brand new pair...
Limone, we have to withdraw!
We can't do anything if we can't draw a Ri Maajon.
This is a reconnaissance mission! We have to warn the others about this!
Limone, answer me!
Limone!
Aaeru!
What are you doing here?
You're late, so we came to fetch you.
What's the situation?
We're withdrawing immediately.
Limone!
What are you going to do, Limone?
I...
Limone, listen to what I'm telling you!
You need to figure it out for yourself.
Are you just doing what you're told again?
Limone!
Silver Ri Maajon!
Aaeru, let's do it together.
Roger that. We'll take them all out at once!
That's suicide! Hardly anyone can do that Ri Maajon, and in these conditions...!
Silver Ri Maajon!
It's impossible! Stop it!
That's right! What I've wanted to do all along...
is to make the most perfect Ri Maajons!
She did it?
All of the enemy tanks are destroyed?
It's as I thought: that girl really is a genius.
So I wasn't wrong, after all...
Episode Preview
I'm Kaimu, and I'm Sibylla Paraietta's—Para-sama's—pair.
Next time, on Simoun:
Wounds and Pain