Are you planning to go out and buzz around again, Chor Tempest?
Vyura!
We have a training assignment from Dux Guragief.
Aren’t you guys busy with your own duties?
Yes, and we’re exhausted!
On night patrols, we have to be more careful than in daytime, and we run into the enemy more.
Fluttering around in daytime is child’s play.
But you guys… before…
You only flew daytime patrols, didn’t you?
Weren’t we always the ones who took the night shift?
Well, things are different now.
We’re the top choir on the Arcus Prima now. Us. Chor Rubor.
If you don’t like it, you’re welcome to try to prove yourselves again.
Get out of the way. We’re tired.
Let them by, everyone.
By the way, which Ri Maajon are you planning to do?
The Dandelion Ri Maajon.
The Dandelion?
It’s a ceremonial Ri Maajon used to show diplomatic courtesy.
What’s the use of practicing an old-fashioned thing like that?
Vyura!
I left some snacks on my desk.
Go ahead and eat them, if you want.
Don’t wake me up when you get back.
Over International Waters
Hey, they’ve fixed her up beautifully!
These kids really worked hard at it.
She’s a real antique, but it looks like they did a good job.
Thank you!
Grandpa flew her when he was young.
Your grandfather was a Simoun sibylla, too?
Yep.
After he went to the Spring, this old Simile was his prized possession.
When we used to have night duty, those guys were always jealous.
Chor Rubor…
They used to make way for us whenever they saw Neviril coming.
Take pride in who you are.
As a member of Chor Tempest,
I want to make this choir the best.
That’s right.
I want to make Tempest the best choir, too.
Yeah, that’s right.
Because you won’t have to go to the Spring as long as we’re a success?
I want to go right away.
Then just go, already!
I want to go there with the one who’s most important to me.
And then, when we came out of the Spring, I’d be a man, and she would be a woman.
And the two of you could just do it right there on the floor, eh?
Quiet!
Listen, everyone.
If we want to be the best choir, we’ll need two things.
Unless we get two more members, we won’t be able to fly six Simoun.
What’s the other thing?
Neviril.
With Neviril and Aaeru as a pair,
we’d have a good shot at being the best choir again.
Para-sama, are you giving up on Neviril?
Let’s do it in front of Arcus Prima, where Neviril and the dux can see it.
Morinas, we’re supposed to be higher!
I guess I’m just not good enough for the Sibylla Aurea.
Please concentrate, Morinas!
Yes, ma’am.
You lead everyone up.
Okay.
So, who’s the one you like?
You know, Floe, you’ve really been developing a bad rep lately.
What? No way!
That’s not true, Alti!
Do you really need to ask?
I’m so happy!
So you feel the same way about me, Para-sama?
What are you talking about?
I thought you didn’t like me, after what happened.
Concentrate on your flying!
What?
Arcus Niger!
But we can’t be at the rendezvous yet.
It’s definitely the Niger.
Maybe there’s an emergency.
Maybe there are some VIPs who are in a hurry.
We’d better get the kids from Tempest back on board.
It’s Arcus Niger!
Niger?
She’s supposed to be stationed west of the Grand Temple.
What’s going on?
It’s a Simile Simoun!
Is this some kind of drill?
Even so…
What’s up with these guys? They suck!
They can’t even catch the speaker cable!
No!
They’re doing it on purpose.
Hey!
Answer me!
What?
Is this Chor Tempest?
The Plumbum Highlanders have similar customs to our Holy Land.
I doubt that there is anything in our decorations to offend them.
This Tempus Spatium image should be covered up.
But won’t that make us look weak?
The Highlanders worship a god called Animus.
Historically, Animus and Tempus Spatium
may well have been the same deity,
but neither the Theocracy nor the Highland government recognizes that.
I suppose we should remove any unnecessary irritants.
For the sake of peace, Tempus Spatium will be happy to be covered up.
A peace… conference?
Right.
Right now, our country is at war with all of the other countries around us.
All of them are in a bad shape economically, so…
They want our Simoun.
They’ll do anything to get them.
Right.
More precisely, it’s the helical motors inside that they want.
We’ve only been able to dig them up from the ancient ruins, and they’re what let the Simoun fly.
Anyway, the peace proposal came from the Plumbum Highlands, to the north.
The first peace talks will be held over the ocean, in international waters.
Naturally, it will be kept secret from the other countries.
And the conference will be held on the Arcus Prima?
It doesn’t matter what the politicians do.
We’ll still be free to do Maaju in the pool… I hope.
But they might confine us to our quarters.
Hey! It’s them.
Those are the guys who were in that Simile.
What are they doing wandering around here?
They’re coming over here.
Why are they on our ship?
Under normal circumstances, I’d say they were replacements.
Hey, everybody, I bet she’ll say something like
“Chor Tempest, you don’t live up to your reputation.”
Members of Chor Tempest, I apologize for my earlier behaviour.
It really was you, then.
But I can see that you don’t live up to your reputation.
Is something funny… Lady Rodoreamon?
Of course you wouldn’t remember me.
I was just one girl among dozens of servants in your house.
Here, Mamiina.
Mamiina!
Ah, you remember me. I’m honoured…
Milady.
We have been transferred from Chor Ignis on the Arcus Niger
as replacements for Chor Tempest’s losses.
Sibylla Mamiina, reporting as ordered!
Please treat me as one of your own.
I’m Yun.
I’ve been transferred to Chor Tempest, too.
I’ve got just one thing to say:
I hate war.
That’s all.
Help! Please, somebody help!
The Sibylla Aurea’s room…
What’s happened to Neviril?
Neviril-sama.
What should we do?
Neviril!
Paraietta.
What’s going on?
What are you doing?
The Sibylla Aurea is allowed a private stateroom.
That is recognized as her privilege.
From now on, she’ll have a roommate.
Father!
Para, it’s been a long time.
Y-Yes. My apologies for not calling on you, Mr. Vice Chairman.
Neviril.
I think this is a good way for you and your new pair to become close as soon as possible.
New pair…?
Oh, then that’s my bed!
“New pair!”
Father!
Yes. I’m giving you Mamiina.
Mamiina?
My apologies.
Pairs form naturally, and only when both partners agree.
You were a sibylla too, Father.
You must know that.
But Neviril, those days are over.
You need a new pair.
If you carry on like this, your reputation will suffer.
Although I have been always an auriga,
if I could be your pair, I would have no objection to being the sagitta.
Mamiina does not come from sibylla family.
But of all the sibyllae at the Grand Temple, she had the best record.
The Ri Maajon of the Raging Sea.
The Tsunami Ri Maajon.
I can do them more perfectly than anyone else.
But those Ri Maajons are the dangerous ones!
They can kill the largest number of the enemy.
It’s time for you to wake up.
I understand that you’ve been through a lot.
But I know you can get past that and shine again as the Sibylla Aurea.
And if I do, your position will be secure, won’t it, Father?
I just don’t understand your feelings, Neviril.
If you hate fighting, you can go to the Spring.
You would make a most beautiful daughter, you know.
But if you don’t want to go to the Spring, and you won’t fly Simoun, then what…
“…answer can you give me?” Is that what you were going to say?
It’s long past time for you to decide.
Does this mean that Neviril’s coming back?
Hey, Aaeru, now you can be my pair!
I’ve still got my eye on Neviril.
Oh, Neviril’s just sooo popular!
I guess I’ll have to give up on her.
What are you going to do?
I’ll go with anyone.
But no matter who it is, I’m not gonna like it.
If you hate it so much, why don’t you go to the Spring?
I can’t do that!
Most of the other priestesses I knew were sent off to fight and die because they could fly Simoun.
I can’t be the only one to skip out!
If that’s why you’re here, it sounds like you have a death wish.
Paraietta,
I had always hoped that you and Neviril would become a pair.
Mr. Vice Chairman,
I will always protect Neviril.
I’m sorry, Mamiina. I’m still…
Sibylla Aurea,
be my pair,
body and soul.
Sibylla Mamiina,
even if you take my body,
you will never be my pair.
Neviril, understand this:
one way or another,
I will be your pair.
Aaeru!
My goodness!
Did you climb down from your window on that rope?
What a funny girl!
The Dandelion Ri Maajon requires all six Simoun.
Currently, Chor Tempest…
…is at full strength.
Shouldn’t that be enough?
But can they do it so soon after absorbing new members?
The peace conference with the Highlanders is and important occasion for prayer.
We can’t afford to take any chances.
I require Chor Tempest to perform this Ri Maajon.
If they are incapable of doing that…
What would you do then?
I do not intend to let my daughter be sullied any more.
I will not let her be hurt.
Mamiina.
Are you here to challenge me to a Maaju contest, too?
A contest?
For who gets to be Neviril’s pair.
This is no contest!
What are you doing?
In the pool, if you’re wearing one of these suits,
the helical motors will interact with the suit and let you fly.
But take away the suit…
No! You idiot!
Say you’ll give up Neviril!
Stop being stupid!
I’m going to be Neviril’s pair!
That’s what I want, too!
But that’s Neviril’s decision!
You don’t even come from a good family!
You’re only here because you’re good at flying Simoun.
You aren’t worthy of Neviril!
But you’re just the same!
Let go!
Hurry up and—
Why, you…
What’s going on here?
Let go of me!
How can Chor Tempest be of any use if this is how you behave?
But… that was…
When the peace conference is over, Chor Tempest…
…will be disbanded.
Wait, please, Mr. Vice Chairman!
If that happens, your own daughter…
That’s even more reason.
No daughter of mine is going to stay in a choir like this.
I’m sending her to the Spring before she gets hurt any further.
Um… but what about me?
I’m disappointed in you.
Next Episode
Chor Tempest will play host to the Highland Priestess Angulas for a little while.
Next time, on Simoun:
Prayer
Prayer.