Yun!
Pair
Is that… Yun?
Yun!
No way!
But Onashia…?
What happened to Onashia, Yun?
Why are you…?
Oh. I understand.
This is where you decided to be, isn’t it, Yun?
Rodoreamon, what do you mean?
Yun has made her choice.
She has chosen her path.
This is where I am.
Yes! Yun will be there.
Let’s go.
I think… perhaps I should have come here earlier with my friends from Rubor.
Let’s enter together.
Yes.
Paraietta, you’ve been through a lot, haven’t you?
All of us have.
Morinas, did you do everything you wanted to?
I wanted to offer a prayer with one of the ancient Simoun.
No, I wanted to fly one.
I wanted to sit in the captain’s chair of the Arcus Prima, just once!
What?
Cut it out, you two.
But!
I…
I feel as though… I do not truly know everyone here.
Yes.
None of us really know anything about one another.
But in order to understand, we must fall.
We must fall.
While we scream…
Even while we are so afraid that our hearts leap from our mouths.
We hold ourselves together and fall… endlessly.
Endlessly.
And sometimes…
…we get so afraid of the fall that we cling to something along the way.
But… we have to let go, don’t we?
I’ll be there waiting, somewhere in that abyss.
Nee-san…
The priestesses of Chor Tempest…
No, that title is no longer suitable for them.
But yes, they should be returning soon.
I’m looking forward to learning what the priestesses of Chor Tempest have chosen.
Yes, I’m looking forward to that, too.
And what about those two?
I think that they will end up being our final responsibility here.
Yes.
Back there… Yun was supporting us, wasn’t she?
It was almost like being in a cradle.
All of our feelings, all at once!
Huh?
Um, we’re—
This is where I am.
What’s the matter, Aaeru?
Aaeru?
Tell me!
Why does my heart hurt so much?
You know the answer, don’t you?
Yes.
Why?
Why does my heart hurt like this?
It’s because you are in love.
This is… love?
Yes. That is love, Aaeru.
I love you!
And I you, Aaeru.
Amuria… she was strong, wasn’t she?
Yes, she was. She was a strong person.
A rendezvous with a Plumbish priestess…
And in front of Tempus Spatium, no less?
What a scandalous affair!
This will probably be…
…the last duty I can perform for the sibyllae of Chor Tempest.
I hope that Tempus Spatium will forgive us.
I still remember Sibylla Neviril’s words during the hearing.
I’m not trying to lay blame for these days of fighting.
It has been painful and heartbreaking, and perhaps this is fate.
It may even be the will of Tempus Spatium.
But right now, I don’t care what it is.
Right now, I don’t care about “the will of God.”
I just have one question I’d like to ask you all:
In spite of that… am I still a Simoun sibylla?
Guragief.
I think you might still be a sibylla, even now.
Yes?
Hey, Paraietta!
I’m back.
The others are waiting on the observation deck.
Okay.
Paraietta…
I’m back, Neviril.
I think I’ll go on ahead.
You guys can come join us later.
Please, and thank you, Aaeru.
Later.
You too, Paraietta. See you later.
Yes.
Would you… dance with me?
The soldiers are watching!
I don’t mind.
Does it bother you, Neviril?
Well, not really…
There are still two priestesses who have not yet entered the Spring.
Yes. Sibylla Neviril and Sibylla Aaeru.
When do they plan to head for the Spring?
Welcome back, everyone!
How was the city?
The people there were in high spirits.
Yes, I saw lots of smiling faces!
Were you bored, Aaeru?
Well, I did some Maaju by myself, and drank some tea.
You guys didn’t change much, eh? Um…
I chose to be female.
I’m female too.
I…
Male?
Yep!
I chose male too.
Yeah?
They will go as soon as they feel they are ready.
We cannot wait.
This is a very important condition in the peace treaty.
Yes, but there is no mention of any time limit for that clause.
We cannot wait.
The reason I did not choose Aaeru…
It wasn’t because I didn’t want to betray you again.
It was simply an excuse to protect my own feelings.
I just wanted to be a good girl.
It was silly of me, wasn’t it?
Wanting to remain a good girl…
Really, how childish!
“I was chosen as a pair to complete the Emerald Ri Maajon.”
“I am a tool to them.”
I convinced myself that Amuria and Aaeru chose me for those reasons.
But I was wrong.
I was the one who was attracted to their unwavering pursuit of their dreams!
I’ve realized that they are far purer than I.
They aren’t afraid of getting hurt.
Yes, that’s exactly it, Paraietta.
I’ve decided to live true to my feelings.
When you stop living by forcing your feelings upon others,
it feels as though you’re standing in another, larger world.
Because I was always waiting,
I came to believe that everything was the fault of the one I cared for.
I can’t keep on living like that.
I want to feel truly loved.
Paraietta! You…
Yes.
I chose to be female.
We shall make arrangements for them to be taken to the Spring by nightfall.
Our soldiers will accompany them.
I chose female.
Right.
Me too. I chose to be female.
Oh, really?
Welcome home.
Thanks.
What do you want?
Neviril!
Let go of me!
Aaeru?
Neviril!
Sibylla Aurea. Please, wait here for now.
Let go of me, you idiots!
Aaeru!
Let go!
Aaeru…
No! Neviril and Aaeru mustn’t go to the Spring!
Yeah.
They’re our…!
Our present is on their shoulders.
Paraietta, is this really part of the treaty that Simulacrum signed?
Yeah! Is this for real?
Neviril and Aaeru…
I will never let them be taken to the Spring!
The eternal now, eh?
Aaeru…
I love you.
Aaeru!
I want to see you, Neviril!
I want to touch you, Neviril!
Aaeru…
Neviril…
Don’t, Alti!
What do we do now?
Captain!
I don’t believe that title belongs to me any longer.
It can’t be!
We have asked for permission to give our sibyllae a final farewell before they go to the Spring.
It’s the best that the captain of the Arcus Prima was able to do for them.
That’s an unusually barbaric act, coming from you!
Indeed.
Aaeru.
Right.
Let’s go.
Thanks.
Please, hurry!
Aaeru! Neviril!
Paraietta.
Floe. Alti.
Don’t cry, Floe.
But…!
I said don’t cry!
Morinas.
We’re counting on you!
Rodoreamon.
I suppose this is goodbye, Sibylla Aurea.
Farewell, both of you.
You two can do it!
Vyura. Kaimu.
Paraietta.
Farewell.
Aaeru.
Neviril!
Farewell.
We’ll meet again… someday.
Please take care.
Farewell, Eternal Priestesses.
Next Episode
This is the story of what happened to the girls thereafter.
Next time, on the final Simoun:
Their Portrait
Their Portrait.