I was sure it was
around here somewhere…
Hey, Neviril!
This sector doesn’t just cover the approaches from the Archipelago. We’re near the Highland border, too.
The Argentine base ship that we found the other day may well have been in Plumbish airspace.
So to make a long story short, the worst-case scenario is…?
There’s a good chance that Plumbum and Argentum are allies now.
What do Central Command
think they’re playing at?
Nothing.
The Messis will anchor here for a few days
while we work on her engines.
I know how bad the situation is, but I hope this will allow the sibyllae to get some rest.
They’ve been through
a lot of painful things lately.
Right.
And there will probably be more.
That Which Must Not Be Violated
Oh, there’s someone in here.
Sibylla Morinas!
Please excuse me! I’ll leave at once.
Don’t worry about it.
I’m planning to become a man.
Anyway, I was really shocked.
It’s weird to think that the Simoun Gems can understand our feelings.
We hardly know anything
about the Simoun, even now.
Looks like we don’t.
I remember you saying that
when we first met.
Sorry, sorry! That reminds me…
I have a bad feeling about this…
Listen, back then, you told me
that you and Floe…
Actually, Flow and I used to be lovers.
Lovers?
To tell you the truth, I have a hard time imagining the two of you as a couple.
Is that bad of me?
Please don’t repeat what I’m about to tell you to anyone else.
Certainly, I was attracted to Sibylla Floe.
However…
She is a holy sibylla.
I simply couldn’t…
You couldn’t cross the line.
No.
No matter how much
Floe pushed you?
No.
But…
Listen up, Wapourif!
You and I were lovers.
You tell that to anyone who asks. Got it?
I know. Don’t worry,
I won’t tell anyone.
But it’s such a good story!
Can I really keep it to myself…?
Sibylla Morinas!
By the way, you called us “holy.”
Are we really such big shots?
I think, perhaps, that you don’t fully understand that aspect of yourself yet.
Maybe not.
Are you sure this thing is gonna work?
Just wait a minute.
I saw this in a book once!
Sure, but…
Got one!
Wow! That’s so cool, Mamiina!
Hey, Para-sama, this is amazing! Come and see!
Sure.
Kaimu has gone back to calling her “Para-sama”, hasn’t she?
Ah, it’s so good to hear
young girls laughing like that.
Skipper, I remember when we were like that, back in the day.
I guess we were, weren’t we?
Were we ever that young?
You called for me, Sibylla Dominura?
A prayer, before we begin.
I have a private request
that only you can fulfill.
The Simoun must not be violated.
They are the holy chariots
of the gods, aren’t they?
Yes.
But those “holy chariots”
have been shot down.
Why?
You already know the answer.
If you’re not comfortable
saying it, then I will.
Because the Simoun
are just machines.
The Simoun Gem that
sees into the heart…
The helical motors…
Certainly, there are
mysteries left unsolved.
But essentially, it’s just as you said.
The Simoun have lost their absolute superiority over other countries’ forces.
The balance of power between Simulacrum and its neighbours will quickly shift unless we take action.
I want you to take apart
one of the Simoun.
They’re just machines.
You said so yourself.
I hear your words, Sibylla Dominura.
We’ve known the truth
for a very long time. However…
People have long respected these mere machines as sacred and inviolable.
Why do you think they have done so?
Because the Simoun
are all that we have.
I can’t do anything that
would defile the Simoun.
I know you understand this.
Knowing the secrets of the Simoun
would save our Holy Land.
This is weird.
We’ve been searching all day, and we still can’t find them.
Why…
Maybe they moved the base ship after they saw that we spotted them.
We should turn back.
Wait a minute! We need to search some more, just in case—
Turn back!
You’re not going to
listen to me, are you?
Two people cannot
operate by majority rule.
Aren’t we ever
going to see eye to eye?
I’ve never seen a cockpit bent and twisted like that before.
I can imagine the force of the impact, and the pressure that the craft must have been subjected to.
And…
After I dismantled the
twisted wreck of the cockpit,
I found not the slightest
sign of Sibylla Amuria.
However, judging from
the shape it was bent into,
there’s no way that she
could have been thrown out.
So where did Sibylla Amuria go?
Have you made your decision?
I’m afraid I haven’t changed my mind.
We’re out of time.
Our neighbours are allying
with each other against us.
The enemy base ship proves that.
Without our knowledge, they—
“We?”
Who do you mean by “we?”
Sibylla Dominura,
who in the world are you…?
What did Dominura want?
She said that Limone’s
Simoun is out of order.
You’re a terrible liar,
you know that?
Yes, I suppose I am.
Yun.
If anything happens to Neviril—I mean, if anything happens, I’ll need to take off immediately.
I want you to pair with me in that case.
Everyone’s souls are of equal value.
If you don’t understand that,
how can you be an effective leader?
In any event, I would always fly out to help a comrade in trouble, even without orders.
A Simoun is propelled
by two helical motors.
No, to be accurate, we can only say that it’s powered by them.
We don’t know any more than that.
Wapourif, don’t tell me…
You said it yourself that day:
“Take apart a Simoun.”
Flying the Simoun, feeling them, has made me realize something:
they really are the chariots of the gods.
Sacred things…
The Simoun are inviolable,
just as the sibyllae are.
But…
I may… have to defile something sacred.
They still haven’t come back.
It’s just a reconnaissance mission.
I’m sure there’s nothing to worry about.
Aaeru…
Is she still thinking about
trying the Emerald Ri Maajon?
“Liking your pair would help,” they say.
If you like your pair,
Ri Maajons are much easier.
Huh? W-Wait a sec!
That’s what I told Aaeru!
What’s this, Floe? Have you
ever experienced real love?
Real love…!
What?
Quit teasing me! I’m always serious—
Won’t you be quiet?
It may not look like it…
…but I promise you, it tastes good.
What did you want to talk about?
Sibylla Dominura,
I must apologise.
I had to look into
some things about you.
You’re the last survivor of Chor Dextra.
Chor Dextra… nowadays,
its very existence is denied.
The legendary choir formed specifically to complete the Emerald Ri Maajon.
But the Emerald Ri Maajon failed,
and all the other sibyllae lost their lives.
Now you are a sibylla under the direct command of the Defence Ministry.
Even the high priestesses cannot countermand their orders.
Yes, that’s true.
Did you invite me to tea
just to tell me that?
No.
I just wanted to let you know that someone
is watching what you are intending to do now.
Whatever we do, we must believe in something in order to accomplish it.
Believe…
The only things worth
believing in… are the Simoun.
Whether the basis of their mystery is real or not doesn’t matter.
The Simoun are just machines.
They are not “the chariots of the gods.”
It’s done, then.
Yes.
There was nothing in there, though.
At least, nothing we can understand.
The only thing in there is a helix.
All we can understand about it is…
Sibylla Dominura?
It can’t be!
Do you… do you see something?
You do see something!
What? What do you see?
Sibylla Dominura!
That voice just now…
Dominura!
— Let’s go!
— It came from the flight deck!
Bring Sibylla Dominura to my room.
Yes, sir.
What’s happened to Dominura?
She’s fine. Sibyllae, please, stand aside…
Please, everybody, step out of the way.
Huh? I thought I heard
someone crying just now.
Next Episode
The Archipelago’s new fighters are everywhere, and our forces are being pushed back.
Next time, on Simoun:
One By One.
One By One