Leave me alone!
You are meant to fly a Simoun,
even if that means betraying Amuria.
Don’t talk about it
like you understand!
You and Amuria failed at it.
Neviril falls apart in 5
Neviril falls apart in 4
But with me, I bet you can do it. Come on, Neviril, let’s try the Em—
Neviril falls apart in 3
Neviril falls apart in 2
Neviril falls apart in 1
Neviril falls apart in 0
Stop it!
Neviril, what’s going on? Neviril!
Simoun make-believe?
Ah, Para-sama! Enemy to starboard!
Here goes!
You’re incredible, Para-sama!
Not a single miss!
Pa-Para-sama… you’re incredible…
Dangerous love
Please don’t imitate this
Be my pair,
body and soul.
Even if you take my body,
you will never be my pair.
Almost
naked
Completely
S? Or M?
What is wrong with you people?
Such dangerous foolishness.
Limone!
Limone is my pair.
Thinking that she needs a nobody like you to protect her…
That’s damned arrogant of you!
Please don’t imitate this
Hungry beast!?
I was relying too much on everyone else.
The beast
eyes the prey
Rely on me.
Bloodthirsty eyes
of the beast
If you want to see another world,
I’ll show it to you.
Paraie—
Sacred things
I should not have touched
such sacred things.
Sacred things
As you wish. I’ll never let
you touch them again!
Sacred things
Dangerous love triangle
Here I come!
I didn’t understand anything.
So I’ll entrust you to someone who could be
even better for you than Amuria!
Please don’t imitate this
You and I are completely
different in every way.
But in one respect,
we’re just the same.
Stand up, Aaeru.
I am your pair.
In one respect, huh…