Who are you?
What are you doing in here?
Oh!
How did you get in here?
A Simoun really is totally
different from a Simile, isn’t it?
I asked you who you were.
And that uniform…?
Sorry, Wapourif.
She’s our new recruit.
I beg your pardon!
I didn’t realize you
were a Simoun sibylla.
I’m sorry. It was my fault as well.
This is Morinas.
I understand.
Helical motors are always found in spiral-shaped pairs like these.
We attach cockpits and various other equipment to control them.
We call the whole a Simoun
for the sake of convenience.
Yes, that’s right.
We think that this one
probably manipulates—
“Probably?”
Yes. We think this one manipulates
what you might call a spatial force, which exists throughout the universe.
The other one controls what we would describe as a temporal force.
Is that also “probably?”
Yes. Probably.
In fact, we know almost nothing about the helical motors we’ve excavated.
All we know is…
…how to use them.
Also, we can only maintain the parts that we’ve added to the helical motors.
That’s the situation.
I see.
But the Simile were built to investigate the structure of the helical motors, weren’t they?
Yes. But you’ve flown Simile up until now, so you must know how they perform.
Compared to this Simoun, a Simile is nothing but a pale imitation.
They don’t deserve to be
mentioned in the same breath.
Well, I’ve heard that nobody’s ever taken apart a Simoun.
That seems rather strange.
Strange?
The Simoun are sacred craft built to serve Tempus Spatium in holy rituals.
They must be treated
with the proper respect.
He’s right, Morinas.
We are here to offer
Ri Maajons to Tempus Spatium.
We are priestesses
serving Tempus Spatium.
Well, I’m not really a priestess.
Then what are you?
I just want to fly a Simoun.
I’m not a priestess. But…
But what?
I’m not a soldier, either.
Don’t you feel the same way, Paraietta?
Oh, Paraietta. This is…?
Her name is Morinas, Floe.
Oh, that’s right! You’re Morinas.
Mo-ri-nas.
Good morning, Floe.
I’m bad at remembering people’s names.
And…
Sorry, when I first saw you I thought for a second
that you might be Wapourif’s new lover.
But there’s just no way, huh?
My windshield is creaking.
Can you take a look at it?
Certainly!
I’d appreciate it if
you could tell her more
about the differences between the Simile and the Simoun this afternoon.
That won’t be a problem.
If there’s anything you’d like to know about the Simoun,
or about this ship, come and ask us any time.
Thanks.
Wait up! I’m coming too.
So, did you learn much, Morinas?
Hopefully this afternoon I’ll be able to learn something interesting.
Distant War
Neviril,
I’m glad that you came
back from the Spring.
May I take it that you have chosen to remain a Simoun sibylla?
I’m not sure yet. And…
And?
I don’t have a pair any more.
Nevertheless, you have returned.
Huh? What’s going on, guys?
You’re late, Aaeru.
Oh, right! Sorry!
Um, what’re we doing here again?
We always gather in the
ballroom after breakfast.
I see. It’s a habit you picked up when you were flying the night shift, right?
As I was saying, why don’t we all get together to do Maaju in the pool this afternoon at three?
You mean all of us?
Is this mandatory?
So, at three o’clock, then?
That sounds great!
Let’s go in the pool.
Especially since we’re now so— oh!
We have lost three of our comrades.
After that, three more
left to go to the Spring.
During this crisis, we have been relieved from night duty.
We were the elite.
We will regain our honour
as priestesses and as sibyllae.
I’m looking forward to this!
I’ve just joined,
so it’ll be wonderful
to do Maaju with a real choir.
And you want to do this
at three o’clock, right?
Why is three o’clock
such a big deal?
That’s when…
Three o’clock is when Neviril
always practices her Maaju.
Sibylla Aurea Neviril!
I am honoured to meet you.
And you are…?
I’ve just been ordered to join the greatest choir of all, Chor Tempest.
Her name is Morinas.
I see. I hope that you will get along well with the rest of the choir.
Aaeru, please look after Morinas.
Huh? But I thought
you were my pair, Neviril?
Don’t be so presumptuous! You’ve only flown together once.
Don’t imagine that you
can possibly replace Amuria.
That’s enough, Paraietta.
Umm…
We’re meeting at the pool to do Maaju at three this afternoon.
I see.
That’s when you do
your Maaju, isn’t it?
If you haven’t chosen your
pair yet, please consider me!
Morinas, your pair will come to you naturally during the course of a Maaju.
It’s not something you can
simply decide beforehand.
I would be honoured to pair
with you, Sibylla Aurea.
I see.
Don’t be afraid. An attack like that could not possibly harm the Arcus Prima.
Yes, ma’am!
If you want to become Simoun sibyllae, you should walk proudly, without fear.
Understood.
There seem to be quite
a lot of those today.
Should we go out
and intercept them?
Yeah, let’s go!
We’re not allowed to fly
combat duty at the moment.
Their greetings seem
a little too enthusiastic today.
Their long-range shelling is mostly just irritating, but we can’t be certain they won’t get lucky.
I believe we may have to consider doing something about it.
Is Chor Tempest still off line?
They can handle being
without a few members.
But not Neviril?
Yes. No matter what we do,
if she doesn’t come back,
Chor Tempest will remain in disarray.
You’re here early, Aaeru.
You too, Alti.
We’ve still got more than
half an hour before three.
You’re already here then, Nee-san.
I went to your room to look for you.
Since you’re sisters, how come the two of you don’t fly a Simoun together?
Just because we’re sisters, it doesn’t mean we can fly together as auriga and sagitta.
Have you tried it?
We don’t need to try it!
I guess I asked something
I shouldn’t have.
This ship must have been beautiful when it was
a private liner used for viewing Ri Maajons.
But now it’s been converted into a carrier for the Simoun choirs.
There are no more ladies and gentlemen coming and going, bathed in the fading evening light.
We’re the only ones left standing in the square in front of the Grand Ballroom.
Just the three of us.
But I…
I wouldn’t have it any other way.
That looks like so much fun.
I can’t wait any longer!
Can I fly this right now?
The Simoun are different from the Simile.
You can’t fly one on your own.
You need a second person: your pair.
Oh! Of course.
The helical motors are powered by Tempus Spatium’s grace.
If either the auriga or the sagitta is absent, the Simoun won’t receive that blessing.
It definitely requires a complete pair.
Well, can I ask you something?
Of course. What is it?
When did you go to the Spring?
Two years and four months ago.
When I met Floe this morning,
it felt like there was something strange between you two.
Actually, Floe and I used to be lovers.
L-Lovers?
It was out of line for me to behave that way towards one of our honoured sibyllae, wasn’t it?
No, I didn’t mean that.
But things are a little
awkward between us now.
You’re coming to the pool, aren’t you?
I’ve told you already.
I won’t be doing Maaju.
I have no desire
to choose another pair.
That’s—
What?
I’m sorry for what
happened to Amuria.
Amuria was one of our dearest friends.
So I think I understand how the people who went to the Spring after that must have felt.
Neviril! We’re going to be much stronger!
Neviril, don’t look! If you see their eyes,
you won’t be able to kill them!
Listen up, Morinas!
You can choose anyone
to be your pair in the pool.
You don’t need to worry about the pair you fly into battle with.
So basically it’s first come, first served! You can pick the one you like and— ah!
If we’re here, Neviril might not come.
It’s pretty pointless to have
Maaju practice without her.
I’m sure…
I’m sure Neviril will come.
It’ll be too bad for you
if she doesn’t, Paraietta— ah!
As I thought, it doesn’t
look like Neviril is coming.
Should I go and get her?
You can try, but it won’t do any good.
Neviril went to the Spring,
but she came back.
That means that she’s chosen to remain a Simoun sibylla of her own free will, doesn’t it?
Yes, it does.
Then, do you think she’ll come?
What are you doing, Floe?
Watch where you’re going!
There’s no way we can do Maaju with everybody feeling like this.
Can this really be Chor Tempest?
You think so?
Maybe you spoke too soon.
Neviril…
Are you… in there?
Are you…?
No matter how you try to protect those girls, this is reality.
Hang on! Hang on, I’ll get you out!
Firefighting team, hurry!
Next Episode
Limone, don’t be
such a slowpoke! Let’s go!
Next time, on Simoun:
Nearby War
Nearby War.