It would be dangerous to ignore the enemy base ship.
Chor Tempest will fly reconnaissance in order to locate it.
The Messis will serve as your relay station.
And what should we do when we find the base ship?
If you judge that the circumstances—
Under the circumstances, we should completely annihilate it!
Why do you think you were taken off the mission?
I have an idea.
I see.
And you?
There's something that might be the reason.
And that is?
I can't say. I promised not to.
I have to go.
So do I.
Sibylla
Sibylla Aaeru always does whatever she wants.
Sir, are you sure this is okay?
Really, I sometimes wonder what those sibyllae are thinking of.
"Really," indeed.
If only I could follow my passions as wholeheartedly as she does...
Where is that Simoun going?
Captain!
Who is that?
Sibylla Aaeru and Sibylla Yun, I think.
I see. Sibylla Aaeru and Sibylla Yun.
Vyura!
After Chor Rubor was dissolved, these two sibyllae were assigned to the Messis as your replacements.
They've been conducting reconnaissance missions.
Good work.
This is all we can do for now.
I've heard what happened to Dominura and Limone.
But where are Aaeru and Yun?
Those two... won't be participating in this mission.
Um, yes. I'm sure we can discuss the reasons for that later.
Everyone, please, come inside.
We'll go over the details of the operation...
but first you should get something to eat.
I know it's a bit early, but I'm gonna go on ahead, okay?
I'll see you in the dining hall in half an hour.
Right.
I'll be along in a minute.
Oh, hey, Rodore!
What is it?
Mamiina, since you were taking so long...
Was I?
Let's go.
Oh! Mamiina!
Huh? What?
Mamiina, your braids are coming undone!
I'll fix them for you.
I mean, we do have some time.
I wonder if those Simoun from the Ruins made it to the enemy base ship?
Probably.
But don't worry!
You have Morinas as your pair, and she's an excellent auriga.
Yes, that's true!
And on top of that, if something goes wrong,
I'll be there to protect you, won't I?
But...
This is only a reconnaissance mission.
I mean, if we don't fight, nothing bad can happen, right?
Yes, that's true.
That would be best, wouldn't it?
From the information the two of you have gathered,
we've narrowed down the Argentine base ship's area of operations to this region here.
With only those powerless Simile?
Sibylla Aurea,
the two of us will guard the rear, and relay communications to you.
Then—
I understand.
We'll do the rest.
The difference in mobility between the Simile and the Simoun is just too great.
Creating a mixed unit would be... well, impossible.
Just leave it to us!
There you go again, Floe, making promises you can't keep.
What do you mean, "again?"
Cut it out, you two!
But Alti started—!
Calm down, everybody!
Aren't we all comrades, who have eaten from the same pot?
No! Mamiina, you mustn't!
Oh! Uh, nothing...
Please continue, Captain.
Yes.
Well, first, Chor Tempest...
...should divide into two groups...
Wow, Mamiina sure has changed!
By the way...
What was that "No! You mustn't!" all about, Ro-do-re?
Mice.
Huh?
I didn't know that Vyura had been doing recon missions in a Simile.
Yes, we mustn't waste Vyura and her partner's efforts.
We need to stand firm as well.
Sibylla Aurea, we've reached our assigned deployment area.
Yes, we have.
The operation will proceed as planned. Understood?
Yes!
Why is Central Command using Chor Tempest this way?
As Sibylla Dominura correctly pointed out, Central Command doesn't understand a thing!
It will be quite a while before Chor Tempest returns.
This would be a good time for the two of you to get some rest.
"Resting is part of duty," huh?
That's right, Sibylla.
Keep a sharp eye out for Chor Tempest's return!
Set course for the patrol area. All ahead two thirds!
Yes, sir!
Mamiina...
You were forbidden to attend Angulas's funeral, weren't you?
Our country is really terrible.
That's not so, Sibylla Aurea.
As the situation continues to worsen,
people fall back on rules and normality to comfort themselves.
Yes.
Mamiina, I believe you've changed.
Is that so?
What a pain!
She's all "I am going to detach the speaker cable for a while."
That pisses me off!
I guess they're having an "adult conversation" that they don't want the rest of us to hear.
Just leave them alone.
Three o'clock high!
There's a large shadow inside that cloud.
There it is.
Gotcha!
Keep the speaker cable attached, and approach from above.
Huh?
But we found it, so shouldn't we...?
Those Simoun that we saw at the Ruins could be here.
We have to find out for certain.
Yes.
Let's at least confirm that before we head back, Floe.
Okay.
Don't let down your guard!
This area is likely to be heavily patrolled by the enemy.
Yeah.
They aren't here.
We're gonna leave the patrol area soon, Para-sama.
Hey, shouldn't we head back to the rendezvous point with the regina soon?
Para-sama...
We'll search this area for a little while longer.
Yes, ma'am.
I see it!
It's the Messis!
One Simoun approaching from behind!
Approaching rapidly... It's one of Chor Tempest's Simoun!
Who's that?
It's Aaeru and Yun.
Vyura!
I didn't expect to see her on board the Messis!
Yes, that's quite a surprise.
Understood.
To be honest, I was worried about that as well.
Sibylla Aaeru and Sibylla Yun, please go on ahead.
Right.
Be careful.
Thanks!
Captain!
I thought they'd come.
Then?
Yes. We'll go too.
Re-route all power from the helical motors to the engines!
Set course for the patrol area. All ahead flank!
Aye aye, sir!
Hey, Para-sama!
Para-sama!
We'll head to the rendezvous point with the regina.
Got it!
Roger!
We've been spotted!
Withdraw at full speed!
Para-sama, behind us!
Para-sama!
We'd better hurry!
Roger!
Yes, ma'am!
Again!
Shark Ri Maajon!
Roger!
I can't shake them!
Damn, they're freakin' quick!
She...
Neviril just told us... to run away!
What?
Come on!
We have to do what Neviril says!
At this rate, we're both gonna go down!
We have to hurry back and tell the others!
They're following us!
Hand on! We'll be right back, I promise!
Sibylla Aurea!
Neviril!
Sibylla Aurea...
Please do not worry.
I will not fail you.
If you can understand my words, listen closely!
I'm the sort of person to die in a place like this.
Just another nameless sibylla.
I don't care about my own life!
But the one who lies behind me is the Simulacrum Theocracy's most revered sibylla,
Sibylla Aurea Neviril.
She's going to get out of here safely,
and I won't let you lay a finger on her!
No.
She who is behind you and you who are before me are both glorious sibyllae.
The sibyllae of the Holy Land of Simulacrum are the priestesses who dwell closest to God.
In the Plumbum Highlands, we honour you above all others.
It is truly regrettable that we must fight you.
We do not wish to capture an injured sibylla.
You...!
We are priestesses of the Plumbum Highlands.
We are nothing like the soldiers from the Archipelago who man this ship.
Our recent battle is at an end.
We are no longer called to fight.
Please, you must trust us.
If our intention was to capture you,
there would be no need for such complexity.
Mamiina...
Sibylla Aurea?
Their words... contain no falsehood...
Please, hurry!
Here, do this with me!
Quickly!
Yes.
So that's how it is.
If you let us escape from here, you will have nowhere to go back to.
No, if you are captured, you will be put to death.
You all recognized me as a true sibylla!
If you let me escape, you will all be killed as traitors!
Goodbye, Sibylla Aurea.
What are you doing?
Rather than allow yourself to be murdered by these soldiers, please, allow me...!
This is the way things should be.
Yes, this is right.
In your language:
Aa-e-ru.
AA - E - RU ! ! !
Large aircraft, dead ahead!
Sir, it must be the Archipelago's base ship!
It appears to be on fire!
General quarters! All hands, set Condition One throughout the ship.
All hands, set Condition One.
It can't be!
All hands, brace for impact!
We will provide support for the priestesses!
Mamiina!
Quickly! To the Messis!
Yeah.
Noooooo!
Move, Rodoreamon! You're in the way!
Hurry!
Mamiina!
Rodoreamon!
Aaeru!
Let's go, Rodoreamon!
We have to hurry too, Aaeru.
Aaeru!
We have to get out of here! We need to escape!
We can't just stand here doing nothing at a time like this!
Sibylla!
Sibyllaaaaa!
Next Episode
A proud sibylla of the Simulacrum Theocracy,
and a true young lady,
Sibylla Mamiina... is dead.
Next time, on Simoun:
Elegy
Elegy.