They say “home is where the heart is.”
Well, everyone certainly
seems at home here.
Looks like it’s taking some people a little longer, though.
Ah! The girl with the
spiffy new hairstyle.
What’s up, Rodoreamon?
My bed seems rather wobbly.
Might it be Milady’s imagination?
It’s old! You’ll just
have to put up with it.
Still, though, it’s a bother.
Every time I move even
a little, it makes a noise.
Hold this.
How does it look?
Here goes!
Hurry!
How’s that?
You fixed it!
Thank you, Mamiina!
Don’t thank me
for a thing like that!
What’s up with those two?
I wonder.
Does her new haircut
have anything to do with it?
We’re descending.
So this is where we’re headed?
We’ve landed.
United Front
This ship is a piece of crap!
Where’s the bridge?
Can this really be
the priestesses’ ship?
I imagined something better.
Some kind of secret garden?
Those are the sibyllae!
I’ve never seen one before.
Shut up, you maggots!
Let’s go.
What business do you have here?
This is the Simoun sibyllae’s ship.
Yeah, I know.
We made a special trip
out here just for you.
A special trip?
Yeah. And you’re just in time to take me to the bridge, sweet cheeks.
I won’t stand for such impertinence!
We—
Please, everyone. This way.
Yun!
Just a moment, please.
I shall serve as your escort.
If you would come this way?
Neviril…
You apes wait here.
Yes, sir.
Neviril’s really something, isn’t she?
Welcome aboard the Messis.
Please make yourselves at home.
Thanks a lot, Captain.
But is this really a good idea?
These kids on your ship
don’t look like any kind of fighting unit that I’ve ever seen.
If courage in battle were a matter of appearances, you might be right.
But the Simoun sibyllae are our country’s primary defence.
Those are the facts.
Every command is paying attention to this historic operation.
It cannot be permitted to fail.
Our confidence in one another is of paramount importance.
Yes. That’s true.
So  I can expect the plan to move forward smoothly, then?
Of course. I want this, too, you know.
It is agreed, then.
Dominura, explain yourself!
We will be conducting a combined operation with these gentlemen.
I hope we will work
well together, Sibylla…
Neviril.
Sibylla Neviril.
A combined operation?
Yes. There’s some kind of plan
for us to work with them.
What? Us?
With them?
Hey, Sibylla-sama! You’re a cutie!
We just keep getting more
and more defiled, don’t we?
What’s going to happen now?
The problem is just that those guys are making a small ship even smaller.
Well, it looks like
someone’s enjoying this.
What, for real?
So you’re from around here, eh?
Yes. When the war started,
I enlisted right away.
How cool. A real defender of justice!
As your reward,
I’ll show you around the ship.
What’s wrong?
Uh… to be touched by a sibylla…
Nothing’s going to happen.
I just haven’t gone to the Spring.
That’s all.
It’s okay.
I’m going to become a woman.
That—that wasn’t what I meant.
It’s not really proper…
A common soldier like me isn’t even supposed to speak to a sibylla!
Come on!
Stop trying to make
things complicated!
Let’s go, okay?
In the last few weeks, the enemy has been on the offensive,
and our main line of resistance
has been forced back.
We’re going to stop their advance by taking out the enemy headquarters.
They’re based here in this town.
It’s called Ubel, and we’re going to launch an operation to take it back.
This is our battle plan.
First, the Simoun will transport our assault force into position.
Transport? Us?
Yes. Preparations are being made to install special personnel containers.
You’re going to use the Simoun
to transport soldiers?
If there were any other way,
we would use it.
You do understand that, don’t you?
The soldiers aboard the Simoun will be secretly dropped in various places around the town.
When that’s done, they’ll signal the main force to attack,
take the enemy in a pincer movement,
and wipe them all out.
What else are we to do?
Everything after that is our job.
Once you’ve delivered us to the battlefield, your part is over.
The operation is scheduled for the night of the new moon.
We’ll go tomorrow at 2300 hours.
Each of you, please make
all necessary preparations.
Yes, ma’am!
Hey!
Why in the world are you
doing that to the Simoun?
I feel the same way.
These are the sacred
chariots of the gods.
I don’t want to have to do this to them.
No way! Oh, those poor Simoun!
And with those…
they look just sooo uncool!
We were flying over
the ocean the other day,
and there were these
ginormous fish there.
I thought to myself,
“Gee, those look yummy!” and…
She’s paying no attention to what’s happening over here.
She just yammers on, wrapped up in her own little world.
Well, maybe we’re just like her.
We don’t even have time to think about ourselves, let alone anyone else.
I wish that everyone could understand and care for each other, as those two seem to.
Tasty?
Yes, it’s a real delicacy!
A delicacy?
Right. I’m glad!
Somehow, I guess I misunderstood
what a sibylla was.
Misunderstood?
Yes.
I thought sibyllae were untouchably sacred figures who must not be viol… uh…
I thought they would be quieter.
Are you disappointed?
No. Just the opposite!
It means that I’ve been
able to talk with you.
Yeah, I think things are great, too.
Floe!
What is it?
Have you been getting
close to one of the soldiers?
Uh-huh. His name is Mastif.
You need to think about your position.
My position?
We are priestesses
serving Tempus Spatium.
We must refrain from
unseemly behaviour.
That sort of thinking
is just so out of date.
I can’t help it. I really like him!
Floe, saying shameless
things like that is—
Someday we’re going to
go to the Spring.
Then it won’t matter
if you’re a sibylla or a soldier.
Um, Floe…
With stupid rules like that, maybe I should just quit being a sibylla!
Then you wouldn’t be
able to complain any more!
Oh! Floe!
My head hurts…
Sorry to keep you waiting!
Um… is this really okay?
We’re fine! Were you waiting long?
Not at all.
Oh, Mastif! You’re so sweet!
Don’t you like me being snuggly?
That’s not it.
What’s up?
Sibylla Floe, you priestesses
all serve Tempus Spatium.
As sibyllae, you lead sacred lives.
Sure.
What’s with you, all of a sudden?
We soldiers are strong believers.
But more importantly than love and respect for Tempus Spatium,
if I didn’t have my faith,
I couldn’t go on.
So… how do you feel about the war?
I hate it.
But we’d all die if we didn’t fight.
What about killing people, though?
If that’s how you feel,
then why’d you volunteer?
It’s hard to put into words.
All my friends were enlisting.
Tomorrow’s operation… is to take back the town where I was born.
Ubel.
In the morning light,
it’s so beautiful!
Especially the view from the top of the tower in the central square.
It’s the best!
So, I…
It’s all right, Mastif.
I’ll protect you.
Commence the operation!
Let’s go, you apes!
For the glory of Tempus Spatium!
Glory!
Make your approach at low altitude so the enemy won’t see you.
In order to avoid damage to the town,
Ri Maajons are prohibited without special orders.
When the troops are off, drop the containers
and disengage to the northwest.
Is that understood?
Yes, ma’am!
Come home safely, Simoun sibyllae.
These things really
make us look awkward.
I just want to get this
over and done with.
Flying so that they don’t
fall off is a real chore.
I hope Mastif doesn’t get hurt.
Rodoreamoon, your hair looks great!
Thank you, Morinas!
From now on, there will be
more operations like this.
Limone, today’s mission is the key to our future operations.
But I know you don’t need me
to explain that to you.
So this is duty on the front lines.
We’re coming up on the
separation point, Paraietta.
Is that it?
That was an awfully simple operation.
Shall we get rid of the containers?
I knew it! Those were bugging you too, Neviril, weren’t they?
They were.
They make us look so unsightly.
Who in their right mind
could say that it didn’t bother—
— Wait, those are…
— …flares!
Have they found us?
No, with this many flares, it must have been an ambush from the start.
Oh, crap!
Those guys are gonna get slaughtered!
We’re on our way.
Okay, Aaeru?
They were waiting for us.
Everybody fall back!
Hey, those ugly things
really came in handy!
We’ll continue to
give them air support.
Okay!
Look! The priestesses followed us in.
What are you apes waiting for?
Good, Limone.
Keep going just like this.
Just like this!
Just like this.
What are you doing?
Floe, open fire!
Mastif! Where’s Mastif?
Floe!
Please, Alti.
Look for him!
There just isn’t time for that.
Please!
What’s wrong, Kaimu? Fire!
Kaimu!
But, Para-sama…
They’re people!
I can see people down there!
You bastards!
Leave our priestesses out of this!
Neviril! Unless we do something, those guys…
Ri Maajon. We have to do a Ri Maajon!
I know.
But a Ri Maajon would be too powerful!
Are we going to just watch
them all get slaughtered?
Neviril!
Ri Maajon… we’re cleared to do Ri Maajon.
Floe! Iron Ri Maajon!
No!
If we do that… it’s Mastif’s town!
He’ll die if we don’t!
Floe!
Let’s do it!
So that’s the power of the Ri Maajon!
Amazing! That’s better than
a whole company of tanks!
We’re gonna win this one!
Target the enemy command
post in the central square.
Iron Ri Maajon!
— Stop it!
— I…
I want to protect Mastif!
Mastif!
Got ’em!
Those are Tempus Spatium’s
sibyllae… and Simoun.
That’s… Floe.
Okay, the priestesses have cleared the way.
Let’s go win this one, you slugs!
Fighting this way is wrong.
Those are not “the chariots of the gods.”
They are…
The Simoun are…
The Simoun are demons!
Mastif, what are you doing?
Don’t make those kids fight any more.
This is our war!
Next Episode
Kaimu and Alti fly as a pair
and go on a scouting mission.
Next time, on Simoun:
Sisters
Sisters.