Dominura?
You said you wanted to do it for me, right?
The Emerald Ri Maajon?
Simoun are the chariots of the gods.
They won't fail!
That's—!
The Emerald... Ri Maajon?
The Ruins
Hey, come and take a look at this!
Can you adjust the communicator valve pressure?
Hey, can someone help me pull this?
It's great working here again!
Yeah.
All right, people. First of all, we have to go over every inch of every Simoun to check for damage!
— Yes, sir!
— Already on it, sir!
So, how's the old nest?
Sibylla!
You look like you're doing well.
Yeah.
You too.
We only just got back, but you already look as busy as ever.
Yes, ma'am. We were told to get the Simoun repaired as soon as possible.
Hmm.
Um...
Hm?
'Scuse me.
Could you come look over the elevators?
Sure.
Sibylla, I hope I'll see you later.
Me too.
Plumbum and Argentum are allies now.
It's only a matter of time before they launch an offensive.
It looks like we'll have to make another difficult request of the girls.
No, not a request.
An order, Guragief.
Everything we've gone through has been my fault.
Everything has happened because of my selfishness.
Trying to forget Amuria and the Emerald Ri Maajon?
What foolishness is this, Neviril?
There are so many things you mustn't forget, Neviril!
Dominura and Limone...
They're gone, aren't they?
The Emerald Ri Maajon failed, eh?
Seriously, don't you think that those two just ran away?
Thinking that might make it easier to bear.
However, the important thing is not the reason, but the result.
We've lost more of our precious friends.
So, we're finally back on the Arcus Prima.
I don't see how you can be so happy about it, Floe.
What? Are you saying you're not, Alti?
I am happy!
I am, but...
We're roomies now.
We need to get along with each other.
Yeah, you're right.
Welcome back, everyone.
Welcome aboard the Arcus Prima.
As for the many things that have happened to you, I deeply—
Listen!
Twelve Simoun from Chor Rubor and Chor Caput were destroyed in the bombing.
Central Command hasn't been able to find replacements for them!
Right now, the only choir aboard the Arcus Prima is yours, Chor Tempest.
Your Eminence, what about the members of Chor Caput and Chor Rubor?
Most of their sibyllae have gone to the Spring.
Relieved of their posts, eh?
Keep your mouth shut, Aaeru!
Well, it's the truth, isn't it?
They don't need us if we're not flying a Simoun.
Silence!
Everyone, these is someone here who would like to speak to us.
Father!
Welcome home, Neviril.
I'm back, Father.
Sibyllae of Chor Tempest, allow me to welcome you back once again.
Father...
Ah, yes.
I know.
Sibylla Limone and Sibylla Dominura are missing.
Yes.
Right now, we're on a course for the Ruins.
The Ruins?
Why are we heading to the Ruins?
That's not a place you can just—
That is true, Sibylla Yun.
The Ruins are the holiest site in the entire Holy Land of Simulacrum. They are a forbidden place.
We must reach the Ruins before the forces of the Alliance, without fail!
Is this...?
Yes, what is it, Sibylla Floe?
Is this mission mandatory?
You are the only ones in the entire Theocracy who can accomplish—
This is not a request.
Sibyllae, your participation in this mission is mandatory.
Does this mean that we can't even go to the Spring?
I don't think we can.
I don't think there is anywhere left for us to run any more.
We have no choice but to keep going.
I didn't think that I would have the opportunity to speak to you like this again.
Sir.
Neviril is no longer a child to whom I can give orders.
There is nothing more that I can do for you.
Please don't speak that way, Mr. Vice-Chairman.
I am grateful for how much you've looked after me.
I've been thinking that you've changed, too.
Yes.
Boy, you really saved our necks!
If the Arcus Prima hadn't arrived,
the Messis would have been done for.
Thank you for all your hard work. I am glad that we made it in time.
Yes, but Captain...
Yes?
I was unable to safely return all the priestesses you entrusted to my care.
Please accept my deepest apologies.
Captain Wauf.
Yes?
I'll get your full report later, but Sibylla Dominura and Sibylla Limone—?
I believe that they are still alive.
Then, what happened to them?
I don't know.
But perhaps we'll find the answer at the Ruins.
Neviril!
Aaeru, hurry!
Yeah!
— Neviril?
— What?
Um... nothing...
Para-sama! Hurry!
This must be hard on you.
Well...
There are others for whom this is harder.
Wait, that's...!
We will proceed as planned.
Chor Tempest will enter at low altitude, with our speaker cables attached.
Our mission objective is to protect the Ruins from the alliance between Plumbum and Argentum!
Whoa!
So these are the Ruins.
Yes.
This is my first time here, too.
This is Tempus Spatium's holy ground.
Hey, it doesn't look like the enemy's here yet.
Don't lower your guard!
Sheesh, where does she get off talking like that?
Two o'clock low!
Wait, are those—?
Those are Simoun!
I've never seen anything like that before.
Neither have I.
What should we do, Para-sama?
Well...
Para-sama!
Follow them!
Yes!
We'll take the one on the left!
Leave it to us!
Do they intend to attack?
The Shark Ri Maajon?
No way!
It's the enemy!
We have to chase them, Para-sama!
We can't let those things get away!
Who?
Who is operating those Simoun?
Who is praying to the skies with those Simoun?
Yeah, how are they able to fly like that?
Are they the enemy?
I'm not going to let you escape!
They're shooting at us!
I'm not afraid!
Wait a minute! Why are we fighting other Simoun?
Worry about that later, Floe!
Aaeru!
Aaeru, what do you think you're doing?
Come on!
Aaeru!
Let's leave the pursuit to the others, and investigate the Ruins.
What? What are you saying?
My music box—it's playing!
It's closed, but it's playing.
What?
They got away!
What should we do, Para-sama?
Return to the Ruins.
It stopped.
Let's go, Aaeru.
Wh-What? Hey, wait!
What's up? A minute ago, you said you didn't want to!
This place...
What is it, Neviril?
Look, they're trying to get away!
I won't let them!
Huh? Wha—
The Spring?
We hit it!
We finally got one, eh?
Onashia...
Onashia?
Welcome, Sibylla Neviril and Sibylla Aaeru.
Why?
Why is Onashia here?
Sibylla Neviril,
I am everywhere.
And at the same time,
I am nowhere.
I can't catch up!
Who's flying that thing?
Yes, there's something very strange about this place.
Let's head back!
Yes!
Onashia...
Why is this place the same as the Spring?
Tempus watched over the flow of time,
and Spatium placed people where they belonged.
The two became a pair,
and gave the people unending blessings... and terror.
Yun?
A Simoun?
Yun!
What's wrong, Yun?
This place!
What is going on in this place?
Yun!
Here in this place, all of time and space...
...all of it is released from the spell.
Wait up, Yun!
Just what in the world is going on?
They're waiting for me.
Neviril, I don't think this place just looks like the Spring.
What? What do you mean,Aaeru?
This place... this place is the Spring!
It's just like Grandpa said!
Angulas?
AA - E - RU !!!
Next Episode
Aaeru and Mamiina are both refused entry to Angulas' funeral.
Next time, on Simoun:
Funeral Procession
Funeral Procession.