I just wanted you to move on with your life.
You embarrassed a lot of the council members back there.
They won’t just let Chor Tempest
carry on as it did before.
While Arcus Prima is being repaired,
Chor Tempest will be stationed aboard the Messis.
You will fly patrols and reconnaissance missions near the border.
Wait… you mean we’re actually
going to fly on that?
Isn’t it a little…
Don’t get greedy. We’re lucky they’re letting Chor Tempest survive at all.
That’s right!
It’s great. Even the ship.
I’m not complaining at all!
Birds in a Cage
Do we really have to all live in here?
Floe, instead of complaining, you should
hurry up and choose your bunk.
The beds by the window
are first-come, first-served.
Huh? No way!
Looks like we’re neighbours, Floe.
Howdy, Aaeru!
Nee-san, are we going to be
staying here permanently?
Well, we can’t change
what’s already happened,
and we don’t know
what may happen tomorrow.
That’s true.
Kaimu is right.
Yun, where’s Mamiina?
I don’t know.
I see.
It must have happened
during transport.
The speaker cable
mechanism is loose.
Can you fix it somehow
without replacing it?
Yeah, I’ll find a way.
From now on, parts are
going to be harder to get.
Keep that in mind.
Yes, sir.
Seems pretty tough, Wapourif.
For the sibyllae, who come from such a high-class background,
there’s a lot about this ship that will be a rude awakening.
“High-class,” eh?
I guess this isn’t the time
to worry about that.
Anyway, as for me…
“…as long as I can fly Simoun.” Right?
Exactly.
So that is how patrol
duty will be divided.
Understood.
But, Sibylla Dominura…
What is it?
Chor Tempest is the best choir in the entire Simulacrum Theocracy.
This is the ultimate honour
for me and my crew.
But why are you going to the front in an old rust bucket like this?
Captain, the look on your face says “this is all such a bother.”
Oh, no. Of course not!
It’s understandable.
You’re quite correct.
Especially since someone like me, from another command, will be coming onto your bridge.
I understand, Sibylla Dominura.
I won’t bother you
with any more questions.
Sibylla, please stop.
Sibylla, this is beneath you!
It’s okay.
I’ve worked in the
kitchen since I was little.
I’m having fun doing this.
We’re approaching
the border with Argentum.
There have been a lot
of incursions around here.
Even though this is just
a routine patrol mission,
don’t let your guard down.
A “routine patrol mission,” eh?
What do you mean?
“When Simoun sibyllae fly,
they are praying to the sky.”
And flying in a Simoun is
“speaking to the Simoun.”
True. We speak with the Simoun so we can pray to the sky.
Isn’t that right, Para-sama?
We’re scheduled to return at noon.
Stay alert.
Kyaaa!!! A mouse! THERE’S A MOUSE!
Where? Where?
No way!
A mouse? Here?
Aren’t you afraid of it, Aaeru?
I’m a country girl.
We had lots of mice down on the farm.
Hey, didn’t you have them too, Mamiina?
Two o’clock low!
They’re a long way off.
That’s the third time
we’ve seen them.
Honestly, those guys
are just annoying.
Para-sama, we should go back.
Right. They’re too far away to go after.
We’ll go back and report.
I just can’t stand
having to live in that room.
Why does Dominura
get special treatment?
Something’s fishy here!
It was Dominura
who got us this ship.
You shouldn’t say
such things about her.
But…!
I’m sick and tired
of listening to you complain.
Aaeru, don’t mice bite people?
Only when they’re hungry.
They do bite!
Good work. How did it go?
We spotted a few Argentine patrols,
off in the distance.
But they ran away
as soon as they saw us.
I see.
It didn’t feel right.
They were quite far off,
and they disappeared at once.
Give me your report.
Ah, the acting captain graces us
with her illustrious presence.
My position is as I explained.
Shall I go over it again, Kaimu?
Neviril is Chor Tempest’s Regina.
Dominura is acting as a liaison between us and Captain Wauf of the Messis.
And she’s also a member of Chor Tempest.
Paraietta. Give your report to Dominura.
Lunchtime, everyone! Lunchtime!
Mamiina made it!
You look lonely, Guragief.
Yes, that’s it exactly.
Very lonely.
But, Anubituf, I thought you felt the same.
I do.
Chor Tempest are glorious Simoun sibyllae.
But… we snatched their glory away from them.
Whatever it takes, I will try to help them.
I will, too.
I’ll do everything I can
to get them transferred back.
But…
But whether it would be in their best interest to bring them back to the Arcus Prima,
I honestly don’t know.
Itadakimasu!
Please help yourselves!
Looks tasty!
Smells good.
I’m seeing you in a whole new light.
Me too.
It’s nice and hot.
Delicious!
Mmm, tasty!
I made a lot of it,
so you can all have seconds.
Okay!
Mamiina, won’t you eat?
Yes. Itadakimasu.
Um…
What?
What happened before…
I…
Let’s just pretend it never happened,
shall we, Mamiina?
Hey, what are you talking about?
Don’t be so mean.
Can’t you just tell me, Mamiina?
Neviril!
Mm.
Is this seat taken?
Um, no.
What?
Um, Mamiina…
Could I maybe speak
with you after dinner?
Okay.
The new sibylla made it, did she?
Yes. It’s pretty tasty.
Mamiina?
You asked me here,
and you’re late, Rodoreamon.
I’m sorry! I got lost.
On such a small ship.
Oh, well. What do you have to say?
What do you have to say?
If you’re not going to say anything—
I…
Come here, Mamiina.
Please, it wasn’t as if
I didn’t feel anything…
What can I do to be
friends with you again?
“Again?”
You make it sound as if
we used to be friends.
The truth of the matter is that one of us was always meant to be on top, and the other below.
That’s not true!
Sheesh, what were you
thinking back then?
I wanted to be friends…
Stop spouting nonsense!
…and I feel the same way now.
There’s nothing more to say.
I… always envied your braids.
But this…
…was the way your
parents told you to do it.
It wasn’t something that a child
would have understood.
It was just Her Little Ladyship’s hairstyle.
That’s… not true.
All the other Simoun sibyllae love and respect Chor Tempest.
We’re proud of them.
They are the best choir of all.
In the name of all of the Simoun sibyllae,
I request that Chor Tempest remain in service.
Do you mean the Chor Tempest
who act as priestesses,
or the Chor Tempest who
“fight” in “battle” as a unit?
Which Chor Tempest is it
that you want us to keep?
They are twelve sibyllae who form pairs and draw Ri Maajons in the sky.
There can be only one Chor Tempest.
Back at the hearing…
You were there, too, weren’t you?
Yes. I heard part of the proceedings.
Thanks to Vyura and Onashia, Chor Tempest was able to survive.
Your performance was wonderful, too, Neviril.
I’m not trying to lay blame
for these days of fighting.
It has been painful and heartbreaking,
and perhaps this is fate.
It may even be the will
of Tempus Spatium.
Right now, though,
I don’t care what it is.
Right now, I don’t care
about “the will of God.”
What’s she saying?
I just have one question
I’d like to ask you all:
In spite of that…
am I still a Simoun sibylla?
So you heard it.
Neviril. The next patrol assignment, please.
You and Limone will be next,
along with Alti and Flow.
Understood.
Dominura.
You were the one who
really saved Chor Tempest.
You got us this ship, on the condition that we would go to the front,
by negotiating with the Council.
Thank you.
Chor Tempest is the Simulacrum Theocracy’s best choir.
Make no mistake about it.
But how are you able
to do things like that?
Oh! That’s really neat!
It’s a memento from my Grandpa.
Paraietta. Are you in here?
What is it, Neviril?
Something’s bothering me.
I want to talk to you again about the enemy patrols this morning.
Yes. What about them?
How many times did you see
the enemy in the distance,
but have them run away
immediately after?
Exactly three times.
They did the same thing each time.
What is it, Neviril?
Did you really spot them?
Was it actually you
who saw them first?
So, if they spotted us first…
then they wanted us to see them!
Probably.
Paraietta, we’d better hurry.
I’ll go tell the captain.
The rest of you,
get to the flight deck right away.
I’m sorry, Neviril. I didn’t notice.
They must have followed
the route of your patrol.
They might try to ambush
Dominura and the others.
We’re up on the front lines,
near the border with the enemy.
Mamiina and Rodoreamon aren’t here yet.
Understood. I’ll fly auriga.
Kaimu. Be my pair, please.
Yun, you’re my sagitta.
Hurry, Morinas.
Wapourif…
I’ll send Mamiina and
Rodoreamon right after you.
What happened, Sibylla Rodoreamon, Sibylla Mamiina?
Everyone else has taken off.
Mamiina, hurry!
No! I won’t be your pair.
I said it before, didn’t I?
Absolutely not. Impossible!
What are you doing?
What…
What do you think
you’re doing, Rodore?
That’s what you called me
when we were little.
Sibylla Rodoreamon…
Everyone is in danger.
They all might die!
At a time like this, we can’t just waste time arguing! Mamiina!
Let’s go, Rodo.
Yes, Mamiina.
Go to your posts and prepare
for emergency landings.
Yes, sir!
Are you still crying?
We’ve just about reached them.
It’s not that.
It’s just…
I’ve always worn my hair in braids!
There they are!
Now!
With this many of the enemy… Iron Ri Maajon!
That meat we had…
It was delicious!
It was mouse.
Next Episode
It’s our job to take some
soldiers up close to a town.
Next time, on Simoun:
United Front
United Front.