My name is Anubituf.
I am the captain of one of the Simulacrum Theocracy's largest warships: the Arcus Prima.
Three Simoun choirs are stationed on the Arcus Prima:
Chor Tempest,
Chor Caput,
and Chor Rubor.
However, Chor Tempest, which was a tightly knit elite unit that flew the most perfect Ri Maajons,
has fallen from its elite status. Now they are just reserves.
As they were preparing to escort the ambassadors from the Plumbum Highlands
to a peace conference over international waters,
a new recruit with an attitude problem brought discord to Chor Tempest,
and a fight broke out.
It was announced that Chor Tempest would be disbanded as soon as we returned to port.
For those who wished to keep flying Simoun for one reason or another, it was a bitter pill to swallow.
Those who had reached the age to go to the Spring would never fly Simoun again.
And so the peace conference began.
Prayer
I understand that your priestesses understand our language.
But if you need a translator, wouldn't one priestess be enough?
We priestesses are not here only to translate.
We are here to watch over this important conference.
Proper courtesy demands that priestesses be present for this.
Oh, that's a good idea!
We should have some priestesses of Tempus Spatium attend, too. That would be nice.
But your country's priestesses aren't just ordinary priestesses.
Are they not soldiers as well?
When are you going to stop crying?
It's your fault that we're being disbanded.
We're the ones who should be crying.
At least this way, we can finally stop flying Simoun.
Mamiina, what happened after your father died? Did you go back to your mother's village?
Please talk to me.
I have to keep flying Simoun. I have to stay a sibylla!
Oh, you're just like Aaeru!
Aaeru wants to stay a sibylla, too.
You don't mean...?
What?
If I'm a sibylla, then I don't have to go to the Spring.
That's really weird.
Everybody wants to go to the Spring, but we became sibyllae.
Now we have to help with the war effort, and we can't go.
Nothing's stopping you from going.
You can just quit being a sibylla, can't you?
But I went through a lot to become a sibylla!
And I'm proud to be a priestess.
I can't just run away from going to the front.
Everybody has their own reasons for being here,
but this is the first time I've met anyone who's only here because they don't want to go to the Spring.
Is that so?
Take a good look, then! Here!
What are you doing?
Just what it looks like.
This ballroom is Chor Tempest's social area.
It always has been.
Neither the captain nor anyone else decided that.
But that's the way it's always been.
You never came in here before!
You guys are always on battle alert, aren't you?
Go ahead and relax.
Oh, that's hard to take!
Nee-san, won't you come to my room?
Hey! Hey! Hey!
Big news! Big news, everybody!
That kid is just too much fun.
It has been decided that only two Highland priestesses will attend the conference.
That means that this priestess, Angulas, will not be able to attend.
She will stay here with Chor Tempest until the peace conference ends.
Because we're priestesses too?
That's the situation.
I need to go take care of security at the conference.
Take good care of her...
...and try not to do anything rude, okay?
But we can't talk to each other...
I speak your language... a little.
I've heard that many Highland priestesses come from the area near the border with us.
Yes, don't the clans there wander freely back and forth across the border?
It is said that our god was originally the same as yours.
So... well...
So we're like family.
The little kid is Limone.
The two on the right are Alti and Kaimu.
They're sisters.
And that's Morinas.
Limone.
Alti.
Kaimu.
Morinas.
And then, from the right: Paraietta, Dominura, and Rodoreamon.
Paraietta. Dominura. Rodoreamon.
What a beautiful name!
It shows her lineage, doesn't it?
She's from a very old family that has produced Simoun sibyllae for generations.
That was Mamiina who just spoke.
And that's...
I'm Yun.
This war can't be over a day too soon.
A peace treaty with your country would make me very happy.
Mamiina and Yun.
I hope so, too.
I'm Floe.
Floe.
And then, right at the back there is Aaeru.
And then there's Neviril, who isn't here. That's everyone.
How do you do.
So those are the introductions.
Just a minute!
She's the only one whose name wasn't said.
That's right. I'm the only one who didn't get my name said.
She doesn't have to say every name.
She's tired, y'know?
That may be so, but...
So, what do you think?
We're priestesses, but we use the Simoun as weapons of war.
What would priestesses from your country think about that?
It's bad, isn't it?
The Highlands are very cold.
We have many blessings from God, but every year, many people freeze to death.
As a priestess, I pray that those people can live happily with God.
That's right.
When we first became sibyllae, the Simoun were only to be flown in sacred ceremonies like that.
That's what we thought.
Yes, we only used them to offer prayers...
That's easy for you to say.
Becoming a sibylla was just a matter of course for you.
That's why you're so blasé about it.
What do you mean, Mamiina?
If there hadn't been a war,
I would never have become a sibylla.
There weren't many young girls in the village where I lived.
It wasn't hard to become a cadet and work at the shrine.
But...
Um... when I become a sibylla, would you be my pair?
You, a sibylla?
The sibyllae are Tempus Spatium's chosen ones.
For someone from a family like yours...
And then, one day...
A commando squad from Plumbum crossed the border and attacked the village.
Of course, their aim was to capture the Simoun that were at the temple.
There was no room for uncertainty or hesitation.
We had to take the Simoun up to attack them and drive them away.
The sibyllae all said: "We are priestesses. We can't fight."
The dux asked for volunteers from the cadets.
Tempus Spatium won't be happy with this.
Someone like you isn't supposed to fly a Simoun...
So I became a sibylla.
But only because I was an outstanding fighter.
If I hadn't been, someone like me, who didn't have the right family background,
would soon have had her position as a sibylla taken away.
If I became the pair of Neviril, the Sibylla Aurea, no one would ever treat me as an upstart again.
I'd have proven that I was a better sibylla than any of them.
But... now... that won't happen!
Stop.
You shouldn't make a foreign priestess listen to that.
No, that's all right. You must be bored looking after me.
Please just act naturally around me.
Sure. And as long as you don't touch on anything secret, please feel free to look around.
Certainly.
So, would... you... show me around?
Come on! I'm Aaeru!
Call me by my name!
Is it okay for you to pray in another religion's chapel?
Before, I mentioned the theory that our God and your Tempus Spatium were the same.
That idea is widely accepted now.
Then, was your country once part of ours?
Oh, no.
Perhaps, before Tempus Spatium, there was a much, much older belief.
Aren't you going to...?
I'm not a priestess.
Then...?
Oh, just ignore her.
Aaeru's only here because she doesn't want to go to the Spring.
She thinks that gods are irrelevant.
Where do you get off saying that?
You haven't decided whether to be a man or a woman either, have you?
Well, no, but...
When you're uncertain, forcing yourself to decide anyway is just silly.
A Plumbish dictionary?
Go away.
Oh, come on! I'm your pair!
Forget it.
What's that?
I'm gonna go see what's happening at the conference.
Me too!
Hey, is that...?
That flare was some kind of signal.
More to the point, where's that priestess of theirs?
Aaeru-sama! The Sibylla Aurea...!
Why, that...! Give me back my sister!
Why is she doing this?
Neviril! What's going on?
Exactly what it looks like.
They were planning this all along.
The peace conference was just a ruse to get them aboard.
So they could steal a Simoun?
Hey! You can't make a Simoun fly.
That girl is a priestess.
If two of them get together, they might be able to manage it.
Then what are the ones at the peace conference doing?
Wapourif! Seal off the hangars from the conference room!
And don't let any two of the Highland priestesses get together!
You heard her! Hurry! Get to the companionways!
Do you really think this is going to work?
Give up, already!
Nee-san!
Alti, it's too dangerous!
Grab her! Don't let her get to the Simoun!
No way! Tell me she isn't...
What?
If your faith isn't perfectly certain, you will never act.
Run, Floe!
Neviril!
Right! It's a bomb! Everybody run!
It's a bomb!
AA - E - RU ! ! !
What? What's going on?
What are you...?
Why?
Most of the Simoun on this side are done for.
Even the ones that survived need to be checked to make sure they're still working.
Are there any that we can fly?
Only the ones in the port hangar.
In other words, only Chor Tempest's Simoun?
Are you all right, Aaeru?
That girl... she called out "Aaeru," right at the end.
What?
Why?
Why did she call my name?
That wasn't anyone's name.
"Aaeru," in her country's language...
...is the highest form of love.
The love of God,
in the Plumbish language, is "aaeru."
What?
"The love of God."
What the hell does that mean?
How could she do something like that?
Sibylla Aurea! Please be my pair.
I've heard that the only undamaged Simoun are Chor Tempest's.
You never miss a beat, do you?
There's no room for uncertainty any more.
Aaeru! What are you going to do?
I don't know.
I just don't know.
I don't know anything any more.
Aaeru, you came here to fly Simoun, didn't you?
I just don't want to go to the Spring.
Is that so bad?
I don't have any "love of God."
You don't have to give an answer.
I'm still not certain, either.
To be a priestess, but to go out and fight...
Is that really right?
You and I are completely different in every way.
But in one respect, we're just the same.
Stand up, Aaeru.
I am your pair.
Try to level the ship off for a moment! The Simoun are taking off!
But Rubor and Caput are both destroyed!
It's Chor Tempest that's launching!
Next Episode
At the Grand Temple, we will perform our last Ri Maajon as Chor Tempest.
Next time, on Simoun:
The Hearing
The Hearing.