My name is Wauf,
and I’m the captain of the Messis.
The enemy base ship that Chor Tempest discovered in Plumbish airspace…
…is still missing.
Chor Tempest has already
sent out four scouts.
The increasing number of enemy sightings during the past twelve hours worries me.
And there are only two
Simoun left aboard the Messis.
What an awful feeling.
Captain!
All sections are at general quarters!
Dismiss the kitchen staff
and have them report for duty!
Aye, sir!
The Emerald Ri Maajon
Just for you, I want to draw…
…the Emerald Ri Maajon.
What a funny-looking face!
Don’t you think
it looks like its owner?
Rodoreamon?
Or the seamstress, maybe?
How can you be laughing
at a time like this?
Busted!
A-Aircraft silhouettes sighted!
Umm… umm…
Nine o’clock!
Silhouettes! Not Simoun!
We should assume that
we’ve been discovered.
Aircraft sighted at six o’clock!
Decrease altitude!
We’ll hit the trees if we go any lower!
It doesn’t matter! Mow them down!
Find us a place to hide!
There’s a hill at one o’clock!
Circle around it at full speed!
Prepare for landing!
Even if we can fight them with just two Simoun,
it’s all over if the Messis goes down.
A baby bird that loses
its mother will starve to death.
Don’t talk that way!
You’ll scare the children.
Huh?
I…
Limone’s not scared, is she?
Now it’s our turn.
Sibylla Dominura…
The Simoun are the chariots of the gods.
They won’t fail.
What’s the plan, Dominura?
— Should we pursue the enemy?
— No.
Defending the Messis
is our top priority.
We need to split up and
defend the approach points.
Agreed. Let’s hit the ground and use the dirt as a smokescreen.
Roger.
Um, Aaeru?
Limone?
I kinda brought Rodoreamon’s stuffed toy along.
Let go the anchors!
Aye, sir!
Captain, we made it… somehow.
It looks like it.
I was right: it was a trick.
Finally, they’re gone. Aaeru!
Not yet.
They just pretend to leave,
then they circle back for another look.
So, shall we get going?
Okay?
I…
I don’t know anything
about surviving out here.
Well, it’s not like knowing the art of war is anything to be proud of.
The art of war?
Yes, the art of war!
Hmm?
It’s the way to survive.
I have to learn it.
Oh, wow!
Quiet, isn’t it?
Dominura?
You said you wanted
to do it for me, right?
The Emerald Ri Maajon?
I wasn’t trying to force
you into anything.
It’s just that…
Right now, I need to think that I’m doing it for someone else…
…or I can’t get anywhere with it.
I don’t get it.
I understand how you’re feeling,
but I don’t know why I understand.
Because we’re a pair, right?
I should have realized earlier.
You mean we were lured out?
Yes.
They split up Chor Tempest
to divide its strength.
Oh!
Don’t worry, Limone.
They still haven’t found
our exact position.
Sibylla Dominura…
I assume you know this already.
The sun is going to rise soon.
The next attack will be able
to find us quite easily.
Then what options do we have?
One is to wait for the other
four Simoun to return,
hold a defensive position here, and fight off the enemy attack.
The other is to leave
the area at once.
If we did, what would become
of Neviril and the others?
Well…
Captain, is it your
opinion that in that case,
the chance of survival for the Simoun crews who haven’t returned would be very low?
What are you basing this nonsense on?
Chor Tempest is the Theocracy’s strongest choir!
There’s no way that it could be defeated!
Damn straight!
Everyone’s gonna come back.
So calm down!
Paraietta!
I’m going to search
for the other Simoun!
What about defending the Messis?
It’s only the captain’s opinion that the enemy will strike again!
He can’t know that for certain!
Such dangerous foolishness.
Limone!
I want you to come with me.
Together—
Limone is my pair.
Dominura!
And I am Limone’s pair.
Why?
What is wrong with you people?
How can you be so callous?
Our friends are in danger!
I will not abandon my comrades!
Comrades?
Don’t you mean “Neviril?”
Since when are you better than her?
Better? How dare you!
The Sibylla Aurea is
Chor Tempest’s best sibylla.
Thinking that she needs a nobody like you to protect her…
That’s damned arrogant of you!
I get it.
I’ll go with you.
Limone, we’re going, too.
But I have something
to do first. I shall be quick.
As for you, with your
emotions so riled up,
it’s doubtful that you and Aaeru
could make your Simoun fly, Paraietta.
Sibylla Dominura?
Oh? I’m not alone.
Someone who has nothing to believe in has no firm ground to stand on.
To me, the Holy Land and Tempus Spatium have been that belief.
What are…?
The Simoun showed me something
I did not want to know.
Please, tell me!
When you…
What did you see back then?
Wapourif, forget about that day.
But…!
That is my final word.
I knew it!
Report!
Unidentified aircraft at eight o’clock!
They’re earlier than we expected!
We don’t have time to escape.
The Messis will hold position
and counterattack!
Aaeru, let’s go!
Will it work?
I want you.
Without you, I cannot save Neviril.
Sibylla Dominura,
please take care of yourself.
And the same to you.
Limone?
I forgot to put it back!
Over there!
Look how high they are!
Wow, that’s almost like the Simoun!
Dominura! Limone!
Aaeru! Let’s go!
Falcon Ri Maajon!
Aaeru!
Falcon Ri Maajon, again!
Yeah, I’ll do it as many times as I have to!
Limone!
What’s the most destructive Ri Maajon we can do together?
The Ri Maajon of the Raging Sea!
Again, Limone!
Ri Maajon of the Raging Sea!
Why?
How the…?
They’ve improved a lot in a short time.
They still can’t compare with the Simoun,
but with those numbers…!
Fish Ri Maajon!
I can’t do it! They keep interrupting!
The Messis?
The Emerald Ri Maajon!
Now… now is the time!
But y’know…
Are you scared?
No, I’m not, but…
It’s just that…
Aren’t you scared, Dominura?
To think that you know me so well.
What I saw…
It was terrible.
It destroyed everything I believed in, everything I held dear to my heart.
But… that’s not what I’m afraid of.
What?
What I glimpsed beyond the horror…
That’s what I am afraid of.
What was it?
I can’t really put it into words, but…
But if I had to name it…
“Hope.”
They’re fighting for the Messis!
For us!
Captain!
We won’t let the sibyllae’s
prayers go to waste!
We’ll lure the enemy towards us and let the priestesses escape!
Aye aye, sir!
What the—?
Idiots! Do they have a death wish?
For us?
Yes, it must be!
Ready the main battery!
Dominura…
Yes.
I want to do it!
No matter what awaits us?
Emerald Ri Maajon!
Darn. All this time,
and we still couldn’t find them.
Yes.
Wait—what is this feeling?
It feels so dear to me… yet infinitely cold.
Neviril!
Look, over there!
That’s—!
The Emerald… Ri Maajon?
What are they—?
Stop! Dominura!
Limone! Stop it!
That’s the Emerald…
Why?
What the…? Who the heck is doing the Emerald Ri Maajon?
I can’t believe I’m seeing this again!
We have to hurry back!
Yes, that’s the…!
No! They’ll die!
Please! Stop!
STOP IT!
Limone…
Dominura?
I’m not afraid.
No, I’m not afraid at all.
We’re together.
Together.
Together. Always.
Yes, always!
It didn’t change a thing!
Wait, where are Dominura and Limone?
They’re gone.
Damn, they’re persistent!
Neviril!
Captain! It’s the Simoun!
Yes! They’re all okay!
Sibylla Dominura…
What the…? What’s going on? Hey!
Ca-Captain!
Look up there!
It’s the Arcus Prima!
It looks like we’re
just in the nick of time.
Sorry to keep you waiting, sibyllae!
Everyone!
My name is Wauf,
and I’m the captain of the Messis.
We have managed to survive…
…thanks to the Arcus Prima and the returning Simoun from Chor Tempest.
However, as for Sibylla Dominura and Sibylla Limone’s Simoun…
…we were unable to find any trace of it.
Next Episode
Chor Tempest are sent to a forbidden place,
and they learn its secrets.
Next time, on Simoun:
The Ruins
The Ruins.