It's the enemy!
We've been spotted!
Withdraw at full speed!
The appearance of the Simoun among the Argentine forces today...
...was a show of force, to prove to us that they can attack whenever they please.
And that really is what they're capable of doing.
The Eternal Maiden
It's really over, right?
The war, I mean.
Yes.
So we can finally live a life... of simply performing prayers?
Yeah, but...
Why does everything feel so bleah?
I want to see that other world.
The one that grandpa was always yearning for.
The world different from this one.
I became a sibylla so I could go there!
But now...
Then, Amuria...
Huh?
Does that mean...
...that it's possible that Amuria is still alive?
That's rather inconsiderate of you.
Huh?
Mr. Vice-Chairman?
Please, do not call me by that title.
I no longer hold that office.
Even if it falls and its life has ended,
it can at least comfort someone.
Oh!
Didn't you attend the ceremony?
No.
The war is over.
And that's the end of everything.
"It can at least comfort someone," eh?
I can't even do that much.
I can no longer protect Neviril.
What?
What did you say?
Those two conditions are the terms that the Archipelago and the Highlands set for their peace treaty.
I was never informed of this!
Superficially, at least, we are to be treated as their equals.
And who should take the credit for that?
I would like for you to think long and hard about that.
"War is utter foolishness."
Isn't that right, Your Eminence?
The military governors from Plumbum and Argentum have arrived.
Well, for now—
Is this really the way things should be?
Yes.
I...
For the girls' prayers to continue in the peaceful skies...
...that was all I wished for.
But with this decision...
Anubituf?
The way the High Priestess was acting just now...
Huh?
It's nothing.
Why are they still here, even though the peace ceremony is over?
I heard that some of their forces will be staying here on the Arcus Prima.
You know, I'm starting to not understand what this "peace" is all about.
There's nothing we can do about it.
Until they found the ancient Simoun,
their comrades were the ones who were dying.
So this is what their faces look like.
Rodoreamon...
All those faces that we blotted out with our Ri Maajons...
...we didn't even know what they looked like.
Probably...
They probably didn't know either.
Well, the food's getting cold. Let's eat!
Here, Rodoreamon, won't you have some fish?
Excuse me?
You've been getting too thin lately! You need some nourishment.
Yes.
Thank you!
Vyura, it's like you're her mom!
Oh, really?
Hey, your feet are in the way!
Move those filthy legs outta my way!
Not that you guys can understand what I'm saying.
Oh? You at least get that I'm yelling at you.
You...
Huh?
Please, forgive us,
Sibylla Aurea Neviril!
We have committed a terrible sin.
Neviril?
Blessings be upon you.
Blessings?
Neviril...
Oh, you're taking a shower, too?
Yeah.
Hey, lend me your soap?
Sure.
Yours are... pretty big, eh?
What are?
Th-They just get in the way.
Yeah, sure. Because you're going to become a man, right?
Unless I become a man...
Unless I become strong...
I cannot protect what's important to me.
Actually, Neviril told me something once...
To get stronger through someone else's embrace...
That's not the right way, Alti.
Only when both of you are strong can you really embrace each other.
I see.
I see!
I also thought I wanted to be a man, but...
I think I can pull it off right now, without having to change.
Nee-san...
If you accept yourself, life will be much easier.
Onashia!
Onashia, how did you get here?
I know you stayed at the Ruins, so how...
If you thought that to be true, then why are you here?
Well...
This place is extremely unstable.
The Ruins were the training ground for Chor Dextra.
Many incomplete Emerald Ri Maajons collapsed and exploded here.
The Helical Motors...
They are said to manipulate time and space.
Yes.
Because of that, space-time was distorted,
and that caused the Spring to exist simultaneously in two different places.
It's hard to believe all these things.
There are not many things that people can believe...
...when they cannot even believe in themselves.
You were right.
I was struggling to stay close to my fallen comrades.
But at the same time, I was trying to escape to a place far away from their deaths.
How... how did you know?
Because I am the same.
I avoided ever making my decision.
I tried to escape to a place far away from reality.
I believe... that I've been waiting for someone like you.
For someone to listen to me.
To hear...
...my sins.
As one of the terms of our peace treaty with Plumbum and Argentum,
Chor Tempest will be disbanded.
Where the heck is Yun at a time like this?
Yeah...
No, this isn't what I want!
Rodoreamon?
Chor Tempest, disbanded?
But we worked so hard all this time!
Well, the Plumbish priestesses will be taking over our duties, right?
I don't get it. Is this what peace is about?
Perfect equality is impossible.
But... I don't understand!
We know one thing for certain.
The simple truth is that we are no longer needed.
And just when we were finally able to understand the true meaning of our prayers as sibyllae.
Even if Chor Tempest ceases to exist...
...it does not change the fact that we are Simoun sibyllae!
No one will ever defile our prayers.
No one.
If Chor Tempest is disbanded...
What? Whaddya want?
...we will no longer be able to fly the Simoun.
The door to the other world... will be closed to us.
You've always longed to see that other world, haven't you?
If so...
I didn't know you could talk so much.
What?
Never mind.
Aaeru!
It's been a while since we last talked like this.
Yeah.
Neviril...
Eh?
Would you...?
Would you bless me, too?
Huh?
Certainly.
Neviril...
Aaeru?
What's up? Are you sulking?
Huh?
Did something happen with Neviril?
Huh? Why are you asking me about Neviril?
Bull's-eye, eh?
Neviril...
...she's changed.
How so?
She talks a lot.
Well, you know, you could always just shut her up with your mouth...
Man, it's always about kissing with you, Floe.
Huh?
Before you were telling me about wanting to kiss someone when you like them a lot.
Well? Do you wanna?
Not the way Neviril is now.
What, you don't like her anymore?
Hmpf! You're just jealous.
Wh-What? I'm not—
Huh?
Wh-What the...? I feel so hot.
Wow, it's serious!
W-Wait! What do you mean, "serious?"
Maybe it's not just Neviril, you know?
Maybe you've changed too, Aaeru.
Huh?
Sibylla Neviril!
Where is Sibylla Aaeru? Where is she?
High Priestess?
What is it, Your Eminence?
Sibylla Paraietta, you'll do. Please, come with me.
Follow me, please, hurry! Hurry!
Your Eminence?
You must fly, Sibylla Paraietta, Sibylla Neviril!
Excuse me?
There is no time to spare! We must hurry! We must hurry or...
The door will close on us!
And it will never open again!
"The door?"
A long time ago,
I was a member of Chor Dextra.
What?
I dreamt of the Emerald Ri Maajon...
I dreamt of becoming an Eternal Maiden...
"Eternal Maiden?"
A Simoun is like a maiden herself.
The maiden... wavers.
The Simoun Gem reflects that wavering heart.
The maiden... drifts.
Forever escaping from reality,
she paints the sky... with her unending beauty.
Please slow down, Your Eminence!
The Emerald Ri Maajon!
You must change our country's fortunes! We cannot go on like this!
If things continue like this, we will...
Quickly! You must fly!
To the land of hope!
Wh-What?
Hm?
Is there something that you're not telling me?
I want to know.
But...
I... want to hold you.
As your friend.
Paraietta...
Let me show you...
When you run away from reality,
and refuse to decide on your sex,
these are the consequences.
Next Episode
Neviril reveals everything to Aaeru,
and the girls head towards the Spring.
Next time, on Simoun:
Choices
Choices.