Limone!
Limone, the Elder is calling for you.
Okay.
Aira and Hanna are going to try it today.
She has come.
Limone!
Aira.
Hanna.
Are you sure about this?
Of course!
We’ve been practicing for this day for so long!
I’m so glad I was chosen!
I’ve always admired you and Dominura… and the Emerald Ri Maajon!
Sibylla Dominura and Sibylla Limone.
The two of them offered the Emerald Ri Maajon unto us,
and our young girls have taken flight.
Flowers which had never grown before have begun to bloom,
and our blighted crops now bear fruit.
Today, another two girls will begin their journey.
Perhaps they too will bring to us even greater happiness!
Their Portrait
Hurry it up! How long are you planning to keep our client waiting?
Morinas.
What do you want, Wauf?
Listen here.
I don’t care if you’re a man or a woman, or even a former sibylla priesstess!
You’re my employee now.
I’m not gonna go easy on you!
Yeah, yeah. So?
You’re saying I need to move more efficiently or something?
You’ve got to take it easy.
Hmm?
Daddy!
Oh ho! What is it?
Mommy, you know, she said “what does Daddy want to have for dinner?”
Hmm, I don’t know. Everything Mommy makes is delicious!
She said you can’t say “anything is fine!”
Oh, really? Now that’s a problem, isn’t it?
Anyway! This is a very important time!
I don’t want Wapourif to be mad if you push yourself too hard.
They say if you keep moving your body, the baby just pops right out like BAM!
R-Really?
Thanks.
So what should we have for lunch, Daddy?
Hmm, let’s see now…
Morinas!
Hey, good work.
Wait a sec, didn’t you just finish your night shift?
We don’t have much choice.
Plumbum and Argentum are already at each other’s throats.
Who knows when the treaty’s going to be dissolved and we’ll be shipped out?
Another war, eh?
— Erif! Let’s go.
— Right.
Later!
They really saved our butts back there.
Yes.
Floe was crying.
You think it’s gonna work?
The Emerald Ri Maajon?
Yes.
You have stolen a Simoun, and allowed the sibyllae to escape.
Do you realize the gravity of this crime?
If they should rise up against our country—
No.
They will merely be carried away…
…to the Land of Hope.
Paraietta!
Let’s play!
I have a guest right now, so I’m afraid we’ll have to wait until later.
Everyone play nicely now, okay?
Yes, ma’am!
Such energetic children!
Yes. I can barely keep up with them!
Paraietta, I’m very sorry.
I’ve tried to negotiate with the delegates, but…
I don’t think that there’s much more I can do.
Rodoreamon, this place exists because of your help. I’m very grateful.
Please, no. I will find another way.
Once the war begins in earnest, it will only create more victims like these children.
But they’re not victims.
Yes, the war has taken things from them.
But they still have so much to live for!
They are the seeds of hope.
Their footsteps will help to create the Land of Hope.
“Hope.”
“The Land of Hope.”
Long ago, I was a priestess. Those words bring back memories…
I thought it was only a legend.
However, even if the legend is true,
what meaning is there in performing the Emerald Ri Maajon now?
It’s pointless to speak of any “meaning.”
Anubituf?
If we cared to look, we might find a meaning,
but even if we did, those girls would not have chosen it for themselves.
What did he say?
To take our Simoun…
And pursue the Sibylla Aurea’s Simoun!
This is madness! Do you mean to shoot them down?
Chief!
There is nothing more that we can do for them.
— We will return to our duties.
— Yes, sir!
It will be all right, Floe.
It will be all right.
They cannot do anything to them, even if they leave right now.
But…! But…!
I’m sure that Aaeru and Neviril will make it.
Everything will be all right.
Here, your nose is running.
Jeez, since when were you such a crybaby, Floe?
But…! But…!
Floe, don’t worry.
Don’t cry.
Yeah, come on.
Aaeru and Neviril, they’ll—
Huh? What?
Para-sama, your breath tickles!
What? Oh no!
I’m gonna get snuggly, too!
Oh? Then I will, too.
Oh, Para-sama!
Oh, please! Alti, stop it!
Nee-san, was that…?
Yeah.
Nee-san! Hurry! Hurry!
Dad’s—! Alti! Get that!
Aw man! All that time we spent on laundry…
What weird weather.
Guess we’re just gonna have to wash it again, huh?
Nee-san, all you ever do is just sit and watch!
That’s my job!
Dummy.
Dominura…
How are you feeling?
My fever has gone down. Thank you.
I’m glad.
Did something happen?
After all this time…
…I think I finally understand how you felt.
Those girls are going to fly away…
…into an uncertain sky.
They’re flying towards an elusive hope.
I forced everyone to learn the Emerald Ri Maajon.
but I don’t even fly myself.
I…
Limone.
Do you want to fly again?
Yes.
But if you don’t want to…
The only one I’ll have as my pair…
…is you, Dominura, so…
Just for you, I want to draw…
…the Emerald Ri Maajon.
Simoun!
They’re coming after us!
Neviril!
Yes.
We’ve gotta hurry! They’re gonna catch us!
Wait!
They’re gonna do a Ri Maajon!
We have to hurry!
No. That’s…!
What is that?
I’ve never seen that Ri Maajon before.
The Morning Calm Ri Maajon.
The Morning Calm?
I read about it once, in an old book.
It is performed to bid farewell to a comrade about to depart on a journey.
Farewell to a comrade departing on a journey…
That’s…
The Morning Calm Ri Maajon?
This reminds me of my youth…
We were all maidens once.
Let’s do it.
Yes.
We shall.
Let us go forth, Aaeru.
To the place where we can be free.
Yeah. Let’s go, Neviril!
I’m sorry for calling you out here, Limone.
What is it?
Well… I want you to be my pair.
I’ve already told you no.
For me…
I know.
But Dominura… does she have any intention of ever flying again?
Sorry.
But!
Wasn’t that a Simoun…?
Aaeru!
Huh? What’s that?
Is that someone’s name?
The highest form… of love.
Love?
Yes.
Dominura!
The highest form of love.
Which sky shall we travel to next?
Dominura!
Hey! You’re early, Vyura!
Oh, wait, I mean Vyuraf.
Hard to say, isn’t it?
Vyura’s fine.
Okay, Vyura. Anyway, come in.
Yeah.
You got one, too?
Sheesh, and the war hasn’t even started yet.
I guess former sibyllae get to be sent out first, at times like this.
Which side?
I was born on the other side of the border. It’ll be Argentum for me.
So we’re gonna be enemies, huh?
Yeah.
Well, whatever. Here, take some of these vegetables that I grew! They’re a new variety.
I’m aiming to hit the jackpot with these.
I can’t die till I get myself a cute bride!
Becoming male hasn’t changed you one bit, Floef!
Hard to say, right? You can call me Floe too.
The Arcus Prima?
Yeah. I just thought I might as well live in a place where I can see her.
A sunken luxury liner?
She does have a kind of elegance about her.
Well, later!
Yeah, see you later… well, I guess that’s an ominous thing to say.
I really don’t want to see you on the battlefield.
Okay. “Farewell,” then?
Yeah. Farewell.
Farewell.
I wonder why we were all so insistent about it?
About sending Aaeru and Neviril to another world.
Was it because we wanted to fight against the flow of time?
We were frightened about becoming adults.
We wanted to stay as we were, as girls…
Was it because we projected those thoughts onto them?
No, I don’t think that’s it.
We just wanted to carve out our names.
To show that we were really here.
We wanted to shout that to the world.
That we really were there.
We wanted a memorial.
We wanted to make a stand.
Aaeru…
Neviril…
Where are you now?
Our Eternal Maidens.
What a lovely breeze.
Yes.
It is a nice breeze.