Now! Didn’t I say this would be easy?
Is she an idiot?
A Simile Simoun is nothing more
than an imitation Simoun.
It doesn’t have Tempus Spatium’s blessing.
It can’t draw the light
trails for a Ri Maajon!
The Blue Spring
What a beautiful line…
Take a good look.
Maaju isn’t just a practice exercise.
A Simoun is controlled by
your body and mind.
Sibylla Erii?
Your clothes…
This is the last time… that I’ll ever see something this beautiful.
That’s…
…the Emerald Line!
Is this what flying
a real Simoun is like?
Where did you find her?
Among the volunteers.
She’s a volunteer?
Unbelievable.
Deliberately joining
at a time like this,
knowing that she’d be
going into battle…
That’s…
Are you with Tempest too?
I can’t believe nobody
else sortied with me.
I was the only one!
What the hell were you thinking?
But I singlehandedly—
You went out of your way to mimic the Emerald Ri Maajon.
Just how do you think Neviril
would feel if she saw that?
Huh? Did I do some kind of Ri Maajon?
And who’s Neviril?
When a Simoun sibylla flies, we call it “praying to the sky.”
Don’t use words like “sortie.”
Who’s this Neviril?
Neviril is the regina of Chor Tempest.
The Sibylla Aurea!
The “Golden Priestess!”
I want to be her pair!
But that’s…
Why not? She’s the best
Simoun pilot, isn’t she?
“Simoun pilot?”
Right, at least up till now.
But maybe not anymore.
After all, you’re incredible!
I think I’m in love!
Hey, wanna be my pair?
So where’s Neviril?
This brings back memories…
Back when we were cadets, helping you made me so happy I couldn’t stand it.
I still feel the same way.
Those clothes… you’re leaving the ship too?
Yes.
My seventeenth birthday
passed a long time ago,
so I’m thinking about
going to the Spring.
I just have one last request…
What is it?
I’m scared.
I’m scared of going to the Spring.
If you wouldn’t mind…
All right, Erii.
I’ll go with you.
Neviril!
Are you here, Neviril?
Is there someone
named Neviril here?
Please use her title
when you refer to her.
I’m begging you, um… Aaeru.
This is Chor Tempest’s
maintenance hangar, see?
Neviril, are you here?
Are you here?
This is the dining hall.
And this is the ballroom.
Is Neviril here?
This is the forward
observation platform.
Neviril, what are you doing?
Erii said that she’s going to the Spring.
She doesn’t have a pair anymore, so I’ll be accompanying her instead.
Liar.
If that’s true, why are you
taking your suitcase?
I still haven’t sorted out my feelings.
I… may enter the Spring, too.
If that happens, then—
But that’s…!
You can’t! You can’t
enter the Spring!
That would mean having Tempus Spatium make you a man or a woman, right?
This has nothing to do with you.
And you are…
Aaeru. A Simoun sibylla
from Chor Tempest.
I want to be your pair.
You can only be a Simoun pilot when you’re not a man or a woman.
That means only now.
If you go to the Spring,
you won’t be able to be my pair.
That wasn’t going to
happen anyway.
My seventeenth birthday
was more than a year ago.
You are an outstanding Simoun sibylla.
Our country can’t afford to
lose you in its hour of need.
You have Onashia’s permission not to go to the Spring, so…
Please, Paraietta.
Let me go.
Please.
People are all originally born female.
However, for society
to function properly,
it is necessary for half of
the people to become men.
This is how Tempus Spatium
chose to create the world.
When we reach our seventeenth birthday, we can choose our sex in the Spring.
But Simoun sibyllae
can postpone that choice!
Our Holy Land is being invaded by other countries without provocation.
The only thing that can
stop them are the Simoun,
and you, the sibyllae
who speak to them.
Those of you who wish it may postpone your visit to the Spring.
On the other hand, if you truly wish to go, I cannot stop you.
Chor Tempest was terribly hurt for the first time when the fighting began, as was Chor Caput.
Those of you who have reached
the age of seventeen…
…are free to make
the same choice as Neviril.
Well, I’m not going to.
I haven’t decided whether to become a man or a woman yet,
and I don’t want to decide either.
As long as I keep fighting in a Simoun, I don’t have to go to the Spring.
That’s why I came here.
Aren’t you all the same?
Of course not! When you’re old enough to go to the Spring, you should go.
That’s what it means
to become an adult.
It’s just that they
need us right now.
Oh, is that it?
So you’ve all decided already whether you’re gonna be a man or a woman?
Have you decided, Nee-san?
You…
It’s all right, Erii.
For this one last flight,
would you be my pair?
Just until we get down
to the Grand Temple.
I want you to see
my skill as an auriga.
I’ll get the Simoun ready, then!
Well? How’s my piloting?
Don’t call it “piloting.”
You’re “speaking to the Simoun.”
Sorry. I’m just so happy.
This is the first time
I’ve ever touched a real Simoun.
The first time?
I’ve always wanted to fly one!
I see.
I’m sure you understand, of all people.
Everything is… different now.
Because your prayers in the sky aren’t for Tempus Spatium anymore,
but for fighting instead?
Yes.
Doesn’t matter to me, though.
You don’t understand.
The battlefield…
you have no idea what it’s like.
I do know.
I was a cadet on the southern front.
Before the war started,
most sibyllae went to the Spring
as soon as they turned seventeen, right?
Right.
But now the Grand Temple says that we don’t have to go.
As long as we’re winning the war.
Thank you, Aaeru.
What a rude girl.
She flew auriga, didn’t she?
Yes, that’s right.
She made you be the sagitta?
You’re the best auriga
in the entire country!
Is anyone else here
over seventeen?
Or is Paraietta the only one?
Nee-san, next month you’ll be
seventeen too, won’t you?
I guess it’s coming up
pretty soon for all of us…
Aren’t you going to go after Neviril?
You decided you were going to become
a man for her a long time ago, didn’t you?
I feel like I still have
things to do here.
Have you made up your mind, Erii?
About what you’re going
to choose at the Spring?
No. Not yet.
I see.
I’ve always been a girl, so I think staying that way would be the most natural,
but I also feel like I might
want to try being a man.
After all, if I don’t become a man,
it’ll limit my career choices.
I know you must be tired,
Simoun sibylla, but…
I don’t mind.
A Simoun sibylla.
How beautiful!
We beg you, priestess, please lead our country to a bright future.
Please protect us.
So you’re Neviril?
Yes.
I’m sure flying will be fun
with you around.
Sibyllae.
For safely completing your prayers,
we congratulate you.
For protecting us thus far,
you have our deepest gratitude.
What should I do?
I keep trying to imagine myself
as a man or a woman…
What will happen if
I can’t make a decision?
It’s all right.
Don’t worry, Erii.
Onashia…
Grand Oracle Onashia.
My seventeenth birthday is past,
and my visit long delayed.
I deeply apologize.
Sibylla Erii.
Enter the Spring, and pray.
It’s no good…
What should I do? I can’t decide!
Tempus Spatium has
given you a holy answer.
From now on, my name is Erif.
Yes. Congratulations.
She said that little by little, my voice will change and my breasts will get smaller.
But nothing’s really changed,
has it? Nothing at all…
That’s right. Nothing’s changed… Erif.
Sibylla Rodoreamon! This means…
You’re staying too, Milady?
I’ve always been told
that I had to be a sibylla.
If I returned home now,
they’d be angry with me.
Everyone’s got a reason, huh?
Come to think about it, I can’t really make this thing fly by myself, can I?
You didn’t go to the Spring?
I went.
But I changed my mind.
Go higher.
Higher than our ship?
Higher. Please.
Okay!
Next Episode
Massive long-range artillery shells come flying from the Archipelago.
Next time, on Simoun:
Distant War
Distant War.